Previously on
Supergirl...
Do what
Lex Luthor failed to do.
Change the world.
Rip Roar murdered
my best friend,
Russell Rogers.
The DEO caught Rip Roar
and they were able to ID him.
It's Russell.
I sold CatCo to Andrea.
She and I go way back,
since boarding school.
Jack Spheer and I,
we used to be close.
-Until when?
-Just before I moved
to National City.
You have the ability
to incept thoughts
into people's minds.
I want to study your brain,
so I can develop a technology
that can do the same thing.
Alex!
What just killed her?
Thank you for coming
down here, William.
Kara said if anyone would be
able to reach Rip Roar,
it would be you.
Russell's still in there,
I know it,
but he must be acting
against his will.
The man I knew
could've never done
all of those terrible things.
Yes, 18 assassinations,
plus one ecological
terror attack.
-A thwarted terror attack.
Well, we know Rip Roar
is working for someone.
I'm going to find out who
and why they did this to him.
I can confirm that his biotech
is still shielding him
from the power
of our Truth Seeker.
Can't we take that
biotech off?
Whoever did this to him
attached incredibly
sophisticated technology
to his nervous system.
If we remove it incorrectly,
it may kill him.
We've been breached.
Initiate emergency protocol,
secure the facility,
Brainy, I want
that power back up.
Alex, the shadow.
- Where'd she go?
I can't get her.
It's after Rip Roar.
Stay right here.
I don't know who
or what you are.
This is my prisoner
and if you touch him,
I will light you up.
She's gone.
Andrea.
What do you want?
I need your help.
I need to break in
to the DEO.
What's the DEO?
Stop it.
I know you've had
government contracts
with them before,
that's why I'm here.
Okay.
Say we both know
what the DEO is.
Why does the head of
a Fortune 500 company
need access?
I know who was behind
the tidal wave that
almost took out
National City.
I know because
I work for them.
But if I tell who
they are, they'll kill me.
And you too.
The DEO captured the agent
that started the tidal wave.
The people I work for
want me to kill him
before he can talk.
Andrea, you come to my house
and ask for my help
to kill someone,
are you crazy?
You know, I do know
the director of the DEO.
What's to stop me from
calling her right now
and reporting you?
Because I don't want
to kill him.
I want to save him.
He's important to me.
I can breach the facility.
But Supergirl is
guarding him personally
and I can't get past her.
You've worked
for her before.
-Maybe you can.
-No.
Sorry.
Lena...
I'm asking as a friend.
We're not friends.
We used to be.
Hey.
You're Lena,
the new kid, right?
I'm Andrea.
My parents didn't come
for visitor day either.
Why didn't they come?
My father runs
a very successful business.
So he's, you know,
busy.
Mother, on the other hand,
is in Paris.
I don't interest her nearly
as much as her friend,
the baron.
What about your mom?
Let me guess.
-She's off screwing a duke?
-My mother's dead.
Oh.
Hey.
What do you say
we go to a real party tonight?
Van Horne's is
my father's favorite drink.
It's top, top shelf.
He didn't even card us.
Why would he?
We're 21.
-No, we're not.
-Lena...
The key to getting
what you want is confidence.
Act like you already have it
and no one will question us.
Come on.
Favorite movie...
One, two, three.
Titanic.
I saw it eight times
in the theater.
Six times for me.
My brother mocked me
relentlessly.
Screw the haters,
we should all live like Rose.
Do you wanna meet
your soulmate
only to watch him
die tragically?
No, Rose post -Titanic,
-Rose Dawson.
-Oh.
She went out there
and grabbed life,
didn't waste a single moment.
That's my dream,
go everywhere,
experience everything,
all while taking my dad's
company to the next level.
-Those are lofty goals.
-That's what makes it fun.
I have a dream like that.
Lofty?
Impossible.
Well, now you have
to tell me
My mother used to always
tell me this story
about the medallion
of the Acrata.
It's about this girl
whose village
was being ravaged
by darkness,
so she went into the wild
in search of magic
that could help.
What happens?
She finds the medallion
of Acrata
and was bestowed great gifts
so that she alone had
the strength
to bend shadow
to her will.
Did your mom make it up?
She found it
in an old storybook.
She was obsessed.
She'd talk about it
like it was real.
She'd draw the symbol
everywhere.
Is that what you were doodling
in your notebook?
She said when I got older,
when things were better,
that we would go
on a quest to find it.
Together.
It's stupid.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not stupid,
sometimes these legends
are based in fact,
and if this medallion
is real,
I'll help you find it.
-You will?
-Like Rose says,
"You jump, I jump."
We just made
first contact with
an alien race
and even apart from
the existential threat
that he poses
to our entire species,
I mean, how can
we measure up?
From now on, this...
is Luther Corp.
This is insane,
your obsession
with killing Superman.
We're supposed to help people.
I think Spheerical Industries
is hiring.
If I don't help you
murder Superman,
you're firing me?
I am not gonna
let you kill him.
Papa,
you almost ready?
The car's waiting.
The new
T-Pixel 8 will excite...
Papa, you have
to get dressed,
we have Obsidian Worldwide's
new phone launch in an hour.
-The press is waiting.
-No, they're not.
Lord Industry just announced
a new T-Pixel 8.
The chip is four times faster
than ours.
Four times?
That's impossible.
We are going to
lose billions.
We have to let go
of 70% of the company
by Christmas.
If my company is worthless,
my life is worthless.
Why is your
life insurance policy out?
-You promised you wouldn't
do this again, Papa.
You are the best thing
in my life.
I refuse to ruin you.
Go and do something
better, mi cielito.
Consider yourself fired.
Lena.
You're just the voice
I needed to hear right now.
We won't know how bad
things really are for us
until next week
when the board decides
to either push the launch
of the phone
or kill it completely.
Papa's locked himself
away in his lab till then.
I've seen him bad before
but never like this.
The way he looked yesterday,
it scared me.
Oh, how about you?
How are things going
in Luther Corp?
You're not the only one
with family business problems.
Lex is completely unhinged.
His obsession with Superman
is out of control.
He'll stop at nothing
to kill him
and I am very afraid
that a lot of people are
going to get hurt...
or killed in the process.
-Can't you stop him?
-He pushed me out.
I mean,
Lex's latest plan is to seed
the atmosphere with Kryptonite.
What is Kryptonite?
According to Lex,
it's Superman's
greatest weakness.
-Can he do it?
-No, not yet.
First, he has to figure out
how to sublimate it into vapor,
but he has this mad theory
that this ancient alien element
is going to help him do that.
I mean, this element
crash-landed on Earth
millions of years ago.
All I need to do to...
save humanity
from Lex's madness is...
find the element first.
You already found it,
didn't you?
Thanks to you.
Okay, so do you remember
your anthropology dissertation
about the Aztec village
that lived in the shadow
of the volcano
but never got covered in lava
no matter how much
the volcano erupted?
And you think that's
where the alien element is?
I did an intensive
satellite scan of the area
and I found...
this.
It's that symbol
you used to draw.
The medallion
of Acrata.
What are the odds
that my mother's story
would lead me to the one thing
that has the properties I need
to stop my brother?
-It's crazy.
-It's fate.
All right, so that's where
the signature is strongest,
so we need to get to it.
We?
No, no, no,
I can't leave right now,
my father needs me.
I know,
but it's three days, tops,
I promise, and you yourself
said that the board
wasn't going to be making
a decision for another week.
Please.
My brother is in
a downward spiral
and I am the only one
who can save him from himself.
But I can't do it alone.
All right?
You studied this culture,
you know the area
and the language.
Besides, isn't it
what you always wanted?
To go out there
and grab life?
Come on.
What would Rose Dawson do?
"You jump, I jump, right?"
Maybe there's a way around it
or through it.
Wait.
"And when the world around her
turned to stone,
impenetrable by hope,
the girl looked down
to the core
and was shown the winding way."
The snake,
it's an arrow,
we go this way.
That's impressive.
The proverbial "X" must be
around here someplace.
Look.
Aztec serpent-headed flowers.
Didn't the girl
from the book
fight the head of a snake?
No!
Andrea.
Oh, my God,
are you okay?
Yeah, still in one piece.
-I think.
-We'll make a rope ladder
and get you out.
Stay right there.
Lena, wait.
-Andrea Rojas.
-Who are you?
-I am a messenger.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Serpent-headed flowers,
they have psychedelic
properties
and I'm hallucinating,
that's what this is.
Oh, this is very real,
I assure you.
As they are who sent me,
Leviathan.
What do they want?
Your father, Bernardo Rojas,
he's not well, is he?
How do you...
He's a brilliant man.
Things will turn around
for him.
He's not as strong
as you believe him to be,
mi cielito.
He's on the brink
of ending everything,
that is why
you devote yourself to him.
What do you want from me?
Your happiness
and your service,
one for the other.
-What does that mean?
-What matters now
is if you agree, your father
will live and live well.
All you have to do
is take this.
No.
No, no, no, I can't.
My friend Lena,
she needs this.
This is all she's ever wanted.
You want to save
your father or not?
Take the medallion.
Accept your fate.
Keep it on you always.
Never speak of it or all
that you love will be lost.
And remember,
there will come a day
when we will call upon you.
Be prepared.
- Andrea.
-I'll be right there.
Are you okay?
I was so worried.
Yeah, I just wanna
get out of here.
Okay.
This is it, Andrea,
we found it.
It's the medallion.
These etchings, they match
the description in the story.
My calculations were right.
My mother was right.
But where is it? It looks like
it should be here.
Maybe someone
got to it first.
No, it has to be here,
it's supposed to be here,
there should be some
kind of trace, the satellites--
Are fallible.
You could have been
picking up anything.
Okay.
Okay, we'll keep looking,
we'll figure out who was here
and when--
Lena, look, finding this place
was hard enough.
Seeing who came
before or after,
it's impossible.
I was so close.
I'm so sorry.
Papa?
No, no, I haven't.
Lord Industries is blowing up
the market literally.
Their latest smartphone
contains a faulty chip
causing devices
to explode.
But their loss
is Obsidian Worldwide's gain.
Their stock hit
an all-time high today.
Papa.
That's incredible.
Now back to you, Rick.
-Thank you for that...
I think things are only going
to get better for us.
Ms. Luthor.
Why did your brother
turn the sun red?
Superman.
Ms. Luthor won't be answering
any questions
without a lawyer present.
Jack.
I was such an idiot.
I thought I could
save him with what?
-Magical thinking?
-You believed in
the good in him.
That means something.
-Does it?
-Let's get out of here,
out of town for a while.
I have that conference
in London, come with me.
You were right.
I needed this.
It's nice
to see you smiling again.
-Go be charming.
I'll get drinks.
-Right. Okay.
Andrea.
Lena.
I had no idea
you'd be here,
I didn't know that
you were in London.
Wait, what's that?
I knew it.
The medallion was there,
and you're the one that took it
even though you knew
how much it meant to me.
Why?
Look, there are things
I couldn't...
That I can't tell you.
You looked me in the eye
and you lied to me.
I trusted you
more than anyone in the world
and you made a fool out of me.
You know, I expect
this kind of betrayal
from the Luthors,
but not you.
-Lena, please.
-There's nothing you can say.
We're done.
Ever since London,
you've been a completely
different person,
you've barely talked to me
and now you're leaving
Metropolis?
It's my responsibility
to make up for the stain
my brother left on the world.
To do something good.
We were going
to do something good.
Together.
What about our company?
You see this? This is why
I need to be in National City.
There are people
doing good there,
who are trying to help.
If I stay in Metropolis,
I will always be the sister
of the egomaniacal lunatic,
but I go to National City,
I can be the Luthor
that shares her home
with a Kryptonian.
That helps her put the world
back together
instead of tearing it apart.
You know I can't leave, Lena.
I'm not asking you to.
So...
So you're choosing
to redeem the Luthor name?
Over me.
Over us.
Lena, please, look, talk to me.
You can trust me.
I can't trust anyone
anymore.
Going back to the studio.
And the trial of Lex Luthor continues to shock the nation,
painting a vivid picture
of just how far
the once great name
of Luthor has fallen.
I might be mistaken,
but I'm pretty sure
they call that a drink
'cause that's what
you're supposed to do with it.
I guess I'm not in the mood.
Oh.
I usually do all my drinking
when I feel the way you look.
Like you've just lost
your last friend in the world.
Well, I'm sure
you're very busy,
enjoy your drink.
Actually...
I've got nothing
but free time right now.
I've been stood up.
-Ouch.
-That's all right.
I was going
to reject them anyway.
Then it all worked out.
-I guess it did.
-Hmm.
What about you?
What drove you
to a day of heavy non-drinking?
I had a big meeting
and I completely forgot
about it.
It's so unlike me,
I'm usually type A, but...
But the friend thing
got in the way.
Okay, how do you know that?
I didn't, I just have
a best friend too, that's all.
I'm Andrea, by the way.
Oh, I know.
I'm Russell Rogers.
You're the meeting I blew off?
-How long did you know?
-Only since you mentioned
a business meeting.
I swear.
Wait, you said that
you were gonna turn down
Obsidian's offer?
Well, now,
this is awkward.
I'm afraid I can't accept
the position.
I'm starting my own company
focusing solely on
cyber-bionics.
-Oh.
-Which is fortuitous
on many levels.
But mostly because
I'd like to ask you to dinner.
Which could've gotten
very dicey
if you were my employer.
-So what do you say?
Breaking news
from National City.
Lena Luthor, National City's
newest predominant resident,
was rescued from an assassination attempt today
by the Kryptonian duo of
Superman and Supergirl.
Well, if it isn't
National City's
newest hotshot reporter.
-I was just reading
your article.
-That's actually why I'm here,
I have to say thank you
for helping me find
that fight club.
You've been in the city a month
and you've already saved my job
an embarrassing amount
of times.
Well, I am sure you will return
the favor when the time comes.
On that note,
I also wanted to give you this.
Someone hacked into
the emails at L-Corp
and sent them
to CatCo anonymously.
I was able to snag the data
and there are some potentially
embarrassing things in there,
but for the most part,
it's not newsworthy.
I just remember you saying
you want to make a name
for yourself outside of
your family
and I would hate for
some jerk to ruin that.
I knew there'd been a breach
but I thought we caught
everything.
Thank you, Kara.
You know how you could
thank me?
We have this game night thing
and my sister and I dominate
and we are in desperate need
of a worthy adversary.
I'm sorry, Kara,
when I said I wanted us
to have a positive
relationship,
it was because I thought
we could help each other.
But let me be clear, I meant
a business relationship.
I would hate for you
to give me these emails
out of some misplaced
sense of friendship.
I didn't come here
to make friends,
so by all means,
publish the emails.
I would never do that, Lena.
But if you change your mind,
the invite always stands.
Every Friday night.
How can a vegan restaurant
not identify itself?
-It's cruel.
-I know.
Our six-month
anniversary ruined.
You know, I vote
for a do-over.
Barbecue?
Stop talking so sexy.
-See you tonight?
-Yes.
-Ah.
He's very handsome.
Sorry, I don't have
any cash on me.
I don't need your money,
just what you promised.
Your service.
You knew there would be a time
when Leviathan
would call on you.
What do you want from me?
Go to this location,
find the man on this card
and kill him.
-I'm not a killer.
-You are what we say you are.
You weren't successful
and then we said you were.
Your father was suicidal
and now he's not.
Did you really think all of
this didn't come with a price?
I won't do it.
You refuse us, but...
a day from now your father
will be accused of
insider trading,
stocks will tumble,
the company will be decimated.
One night,
while awaiting trial,
your father will put on
his striped pajamas,
he will take the elevator
to the roof
and when he steps up
on the ledge,
his last words will be,
"I failed you, mi cielito."
Listen to me very carefully.
Take the medallion,
tap it three times,
you'll know what to do.
Governor Harper?
Governor Harper!
Last month, Cat Grant
joined the Marsdin
administration
and since her appointment,
she's made a big impact.
Today in technology news...
Lena.
-Kara.
-Hi.
-Hi, it's really good
to see you.
-Are you waiting for someone?
-Not today,
I have a hot date
with some spreadsheets.
Oh.
I'm actually meeting
my sister here, she loves it.
She makes us order
every appetizer on the menu.
Actually, I'm lying,
I'm the one that orders
all the appetizers.
-That sounds like fun.
-Yeah.
Look, I heard you when you said
you didn't wanna connect
with anyone
but I've been
the new girl in town
and I put my guards up too.
But I was miserable.
And if I hadn't let someone in,
my sister,
actually...
I think I would've drowned
in it.
Oh.
And...
I guess my sister has to work.
I... You do, too,
I'm sorry,
I'll leave you alone.
Kara.
Don't be ridiculous,
you can't eat all
those apps on your own.
Why don't you join me.
Really?
Okay, but I'm warning you,
people have been
underestimating
how much I can eat
for years.
Oh, game on.
-You all right?
-Russ.
Hey, you're home early.
What's going on?
Something's been off
with you for weeks.
I'm worried
you're into something bad.
Something dangerous.
It's just, um...
A private family thing.
Look, I'm exhausted,
I'm gonna go take a shower.
What are you doing?
No, stop!
You know Leviathan
required complete discretion.
You were careless,
he got too close.
Our secrets are more important
than any life.
No, no, no,
he's a good person.
This isn't his fault,
please.
Finish it, make it look like
a home invasion.
No, wait!
He can help you.
This is Russell Rogers,
he's working on
medical advancements.
He has a prototype
that can bring soldiers back
from the brink of death
and then some.
He can be very useful to you.
It's okay.
Your friends...
have been lying to you
from the start.
Every last one.
...the last five years.
And we have an update
on the Lex Luthor story.
Lex Luthor and his master plan to manipulate the Kaznians.
The Girl of Steel
saves the day again.
-Supergirl saved--
-Obsidian Worldwide
announced this week
that they will be opening a new branch to be spearheaded
by CEO Bernardo Rojas'
daughter Andrea Rojas.
Obsidian's entrance into
the North American market
marks a turning point
for the company,
which has thus far avoided
the American market.
CEO Bernando Rojas,
once a gallant trailblazer...
I never needed them.
Any of them.
But that doesn't mean
they can't be useful.
I was glad to get
a call from you, Lena.
I've missed you.
It's been a long time.
I thought I'd never
hear from you again.
Well, I was thinking...
that you and I have too much
to offer each other
to let ancient history
get in the way of
a potential partnership.
Okay.
I'm listening.
Well, I'm sure you've heard
of Lex's latest misdeeds.
He's left me with
quite a mess to clean up.
Financially.
So I'm selling CatCo.
-That's a shame.
-I'm glad you think so.
Because I believe
I've found the perfect
person to take it over.
You.
I already run a tech company.
Tech gets you money,
but media gets you control of
the markets.
And CatCo would be the perfect
advertising platform
for Obsidian.
That's an interesting thought,
I've honestly never
considered it.
You should.
And I know you've been
looking for a place
for Obsidian North's
new headquarters.
I think National City
could be a good fit.
It would be nice
to be in the same city again.
Just like old times.
Why don't we discuss
the details?
Every time I look at you,
I'm reminded of all
the horrible things I've done.
Honey, every time
I look at you,
all I remember is pain.
Lena, for so long I wanted
to tell you the truth, but...
I was scared.
That medallion was
the only thing
that could've stopped
my brother
-and you knew that.
-Everything I did,
every decision was to save
my father's life.
My brother was
a homicidal maniac.
A lot of innocent people
are dead because of him,
because of you.
I am well aware of how much
blood there is on my hands.
And I'm so sorry.
Because you say you're sorry,
it doesn't make
everything better.
Okay? How am I supposed
to believe you now?
Because you were right
all along.
It was magical.
Lena.
"And she had the strength
to bend shadow to her will."
It wasn't a metaphor
about overcoming darkness,
-it was literal.
-It came with the ability
to move through shadows.
And you've had
this ability the whole time?
It's not a gift,
it's a curse.
I never wanted to betray you.
But my father,
he was gonna die...
so I did what I had to do.
But it cost me the love of
my life and my best friend.
Taking this from you was
the biggest mistake of my life.
I know I've done
terrible things.
But this is my chance
to do something good.
Please, you have to believe me.
I believe you.
I'm tired of people
hurting each other.
Doing harm.
So you'll help me?
"You jump, I jump, right?"
-Did Brainy say anything?
-Not yet.
But there is an old piece
of Cadmus tech in the vaults
that could help us
remove his biotech
and force an answer
out of him.
So I'll go get it.
William told me about you,
well, he told me about Russell,
how good a friend he was,
how devastating
it was to lose him.
You know,
William sacrificed everything,
dedicated himself
to finding out
what happened to Russell.
So I guess you must've been
pretty special.
The person William knew
is gone.
I don't agree.
I think you're working
for someone
and they're forcing you
to do these things.
I know you feel
you've gone too far
to ever be Russell again
but you're wrong.
It is never too late
to try to make things right.
Or at least better.
Who did this to you?
I can keep you safe.
They're called Leviathan.
Good.
Now here's how this will go.
I'll handle Supergirl.
I have to go, um...
Thank you.
Lena. Lena?
-Lena. Lena.
-Kara.
Oh, thank God you're here.
It was horrible,
it was here one minute
and gone the next,
she's like a shadow.
I'll jam all incoming signals.
I've recently developed
a device
that can incept
a single thought
into the surrounding area,
"Do no harm."
Plant it at the DEO.
It will disable all agents
that get in your way.
I'll control it from here
and then the DEO is yours.
J'onn, is everything okay?
I felt a psychic attack
at the DEO.
It felt like my brother.
That's impossible.
There must be something else.
I just have a bad feeling.
Well, we still have
the psychic inhibitor buds.
-I'll be careful.
-Okay, see you soon.
Supergirl, I think we have
a bit of a situation here.
Supergirl, do you copy?
Director Danvers.
Agent Dox, someone
incepted the DEO,
we're the only two unaffected.
That is an erroneous
assumption.
We must do no harm.
Sorry, Brainy.
I knew I felt something.
Where is Supergirl?
Oh, hell no.
-Make sure the shadow
doesn't get to Rip Roar.
-Right.
Supergirl!
Alex is in trouble,
stay here.
No, no.
If you think
you can hurt my friends,
to get me out of the way,
you got another thing coming.
Please don't fight.
I want to help you.
No!
Lena, I honestly don't know
how I can ever repay you.
You can start by
giving me the medallion.
I can't.
You'd incept me
to give you this.
Much worse.
Russell, pick up the scalpel.
Now hold it
to your carotid artery.
And press. Slowly.
Please, Lena, don't do this.
Then give me the medallion.
This is what
you wanted this whole time.
I helped you save Russell,
now I want what I deserve.
I was desperate,
my father was weak,
he was going to die.
Everything I did,
I did for love.
That's what hurt the most.
I cared about you more than
anyone else in the world
and I never
would've betrayed you.
I told you this thing
is a curse.
Our friendship was the curse.
Russell, put the scalpel down.
-Now go, both of you.
Malefic must've been
working with the assassin.
How else could he have
incepted everyone?
Believe me, I want to know
who is responsible,
but Malefic did not do this.
So we're back to square one.
We're not,
I got something from Rip Roar.
A name.
Leviathan.
We'll start gathering intel
immediately.
Okay, but I have to break
some bad news first.
- Russell got away.
The same operative
that attacked yesterday
came again, they worked
as a team and now he's gone.
I'm so sorry.
I was wrong about him
all along.
No, I don't think you were.
Supergirl told us he's been
working against his will.
I don't think he ever meant
to betray you.
I'm sorry,
if it weren't for me,
they never would've
come for you.
You saved my life.
Even before that,
you made it worth living.
No. Russ, no, no, Russ.
No, no, no!
Somebody help, please.
Russ! Please, somebody help!
You can't escape us,
nor the powers
we bestowed upon you.
I don't even have
the medallion anymore.
What do you want?
The powers never came
from the medallion.
It activated them.
But they came from the darkness
within you.
And that is something
you can never escape.
No...
No.
Not so fast, Lena,
I'm gonna get you.
I got you.
Oh, no, no.
I found it, Mother.
End simulation.
Ms. Luthor, preliminary tests
confirm any properties
the medallion may have had
are gone.
Doesn't matter,
can you translate
these markings?
Now access the memories
of Eve Tessmacher
and tell me everything
she knows about Leviathan.