Previously onSupergirl...
I can't help
thinking that...
if I had done
things differently
with my friendship
with Lena,
maybe things would have
turned out differently.
There's no way of knowing.
Okay, I'm sorry,
I'm confused.
This is your all-powerful
Fifth Dimensional stalker?
No. I don't know who this is.
I am Mr. Mxyzptlk,
just as I'm sure
that you, Kara Danvers,
are Su--
Get in here.
Thank you so much.
I can't just come in anymore.
I have to be invited.
Tell me who you are
and what you want, now.
I'm your one true love,
your soulmate,
your one true ''pairing''
as the kids say.
My name is Mxyzptlk,
and I love you, Kara Zor-El.
Okay. If you...
-Aw, come on.
If you are Mxy,
then why do you look like this?
Okay, I only took on
that other form
and sophisticated accent
to impress you.
But it worked.
You caught me.
Tricked me.
No,
I followed the rules.
You say your name backwards,
you go back
to the Fifth Dimension,
no questions asked.
Ah,
I miss that hair.
I really, really do.
But now, I can't use
any of my powers,
except to help those
whom I have wronged.
Oh, how sad for you.
Yes.
A tragedy
of Shakespearean proportions,
I agree.
But great news.
You're the last one.
What could I
possibly need your help for?
I killed
my brother for you,
for our friends!
Don't you understand
what you've done?
Your best friend thinks
that she is your enemy.
And the worst part...
It's your fault.
You hid the truth from her.
You let her find out
from that sadist, Lex,
and now, you think
she could be capable
of anything.
-What's your point?
-My point, toots, is this.
Careful.
I am offering you a do-over.
Hmm?
I could send you back in time.
Wouldn't you like
to be able to tell Lena
that you're Supergirl
on your own terms?
Wouldn't you like to see...
what the world
would look like...
if you controlled
the narrative?
-Haven't you hurt enough?
-Hmm?
I get it.
You don't trust me.
Okay, but how's this?
Ready? Now,
by Fifth Dimensional law,
I am required
to give you this recording
of me saying
my name backwards,
in case you ever need
to banish me
to my Fifth Dimension,
-which I know that you--
- Kltpzyxm.
I'm not a villain.
You shouldn't have
treated me like one.
Hey, girls.
What's going on?
You're not seriously thinking
of doing this, are you?
What if I could change things?
If I told Lena
that I was Supergirl
before Lex,
maybe she would have
reacted differently.
I mean,
isn't that worth a try?
Changing history
to save a friendship?
-Kara, I don't...
I don't know.
-No.
This is changing history
to save history,
'cause Lex and Lena
are planning
something horrible,
and we are no closer
to finding out what that is.
And when the fight comes...
I don't know if I have
what it takes to stop her.
Kara...
are you sure
you can trust Mxy?
No.
But the tape recorder worked.
I... I could always just use it
to get him to go away.
All right,
listen to me.
If you really think
that this is your best chance
to set things right with Lena
before she hurts somebody...
then do it.
Okay.
Uh... How do I do this?
Um...
- Oh!
- Oh, God.
Thank Zook
you changed your mind.
Yes, I'm still working
on eavesdropping.
That's a problem.
Okay, uh,
before we do this, Mxy,
I need your word
that if things go sideways,
you'll put it all
back to normal.
I am court-ordered to do so.
Boop.
Now, no shade
to the Super Friends,
but it tends to work better
when it's just me
and the subject.
So, do you two
have any plans?
-No. I don't think so.
-No. No, we were just gonna--
What...
Where did they go?
Oh...
They're in their happy place.
Magic rules!
Game on, Danvers!
All right, so,
how does this work?
I will show you
relevant parts of your life.
You'll tell me when to pause,
I will snap,
like thus,
sending you back.
You will change history.
Once you have
confronted Lena,
you will come back,
we will watch from your loft
and the safety of your couch.
If you are comfortable
with the domino effect...
I will then snap again,
at which point,
-it will become reality.
-Okay?
-Okay.
So, three years of friendship.
Where did it go wrong?
Well...
Uh-huh.
When Lena told me
that she knew I was Supergirl,
-she was furious.
-Yeah.
-She said I made
a fool out of her.
-Uh-huh.
She was humiliated.
Okay, so, we're looking for
a moment where you made
your best friend
feel like a big,
dumb idiot. Yeah?
-In so many words.
-Okay.
Well, we have
an embarrassment of riches.
-Get your seatbelt back on.
I'm gonna land this plane.
- Oh, yeah,
this is a good one.
- Oh.
Mmm.
Kara? Kara?
God, I hate flying.
- Oh!
-Ugh. This is awful!
-I'm awful!
-You're awful.
I was just agreeing with you.
I would never say that.
-Uh-huh.
-Okay.
- Oh, okay.
- Ah.
Let's go to
before Mercy attacks.
- Right there?
- Mmm-hmm.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Don't mess it up.
To be honest,
I didn't have much faith
in politicians to begin with.
I just don't think
any of them can be trusted.
Don't look
so scandalized, Kara.
You know how cynical I can be.
Is everything okay?
You shouldn't have to
be so cynical.
You're good and righteous,
and... and the tragedy is,
the world has made you cynical
because you've been betrayed
so many times.
By your mother,
by your brother...
and now, by me.
What are you talking about?
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm Supergirl.
I never meant to deceive you.
I just didn't know
how to tell you.
You stay here.
I'll deal with this.
Lena?
What happened?
Where'd she go?
Ah. Events are unfolding
differently now.
Oh, boy. Um,
I need to catch up.
- Ah,
there she is.
She went to Metropolis.
Oh, my God.
She went to see Sam.
So, Kara is Supergirl?
Yeah, I know.
My head's kind of spinning.
When you were Reign,
and I made Kryptonite
to stop you...
You know, in response,
Supergirl was so horrible.
And then, Kara was the same.
She was so kind and supportive.
But it made me think,
which was the real Kara?
And if the real Kara thought
I was a villain...
then maybe
that's all I really am.
No, Lena, no.
How could you ever think that?
Lena, you made Kryptonite
to split me from Reign
and to save my life.
You were never the villain.
You were always the hero.
Thank you.
I really needed to hear that.
The Lena
in this timeline
might never forgive me.
She might even hate me.
You know what?
If Sam stops her
from going down a dark path,
I can live with that.
Except you literally can't.
What do you mean?
Oh, my God.
This is the night
Agent Liberty poisoned the air
with Kryptonite.
Uh,
you know what?
Maybe we should shut this off.
-Huh?
-No, no, no.
Lena saved me the first time.
She might hate me,
but she'll save me again.
She wants to,
but she'll never
make it in time.
Hey, Kara.
I'm sorry
I missed Thanksgiving.
We're just...
We're so lost without you.
I...
am so lost without you.
Happy late Thanksgiving.
Oh.
Can you please turn it off?
I can't watch any more of this.
Just stop it!
That was horrible.
Obviously, you don't want
to stay dead.
-No!
No, I have to go back further.
I get it now.
My dual identities
made Lena think
that she couldn't trust
either side of me.
I was a hypocrite.
Okay, so, when exactly
did this Kryptonite-fueled
tete-a-tete happen?
Ah... It was... It was, uh,
just after we found out
Lena was housing Reign.
Lena, the Worldkillers
are coming.
-We have to
get you someplace--
-Mmm...
-Skip forward.
-Skip.
You are never going to make
Kryptonite ever again.
-You really do
have a God-complex.
- See, there.
-This fight is what
I'm trying to avoid.
-Mmm-hmm. Okay.
So, go back.
I need you to find out
if there really isn't
any Kryptonite left.
Kara, you're asking me
to betray somebody
that I really care about.
I never should have done that.
-Uh, yeah, it has to
be before this.
-Yeah, hang on, before.
We have to go back further.
-Here.
-Yep.
My friend came to me.
She was alone and afraid.
I had to do something.
I need you to level with me.
Do you have
any more Kryptonite?
-This is it.
-Mmm-hmm.
This is the moment
that Lena started
to distrust Supergirl.
-This is when
I have to tell her, so...
-Okay.
Mmm...
Beam me up, Mxy.
You don't have a catchphrase?
We'll work on that.
''Girl power!'' No.
My friend came to me.
She was alone and afraid.
I had to do something.
That feeling of needing
to protect your friend,
no matter
what the world thinks...
I understand that
more than you know.
You once told me
Kara Danvers was your hero.
I never told you that.
I told...
It's me, Lena.
I've always been Kara.
Kara, how could you?
I'm sorry
I didn't tell you sooner.
Three weeks ago,
I found out that Sam,
one of my closest friends,
was a homicidal Kryptonian.
I went
through that terror alone.
I risked my life
day after day for weeks
because I believed
that I was the only one
who could be trusted
to protect her, to save her.
I could have used your help.
I would have used your help
if you'd bothered to tell me
the truth before now.
If you'd trusted me then,
I wouldn't have had to
go through that danger alone!
I'm so sorry,
but I thought
I was protecting you.
But now, we can...
we can move past it
and work as partners.
You expect me
to be your partner after this?
When all you've done
is prove to me
that you can't
be trusted at all?
Oh, no.
I...
-I forgot.
-Yeah.
-The Worldkiller started
an eclipse that day.
-Mmm-hmm.
-So, you forgot the...
forgot the eclipse...
...and then, you also forgot
the Kryptonite bomb.
You know what
we're not gonna do?
We're not gonna rely
on your memory anymore
for maybe, like,
big, important details.
-Just sayin'.
We got to try something else.
-How about here?
-No! No.
Just let this play out a bit,
-because in the original
version of events...
-Mmm-hmm.
...Lena helped me and the DEO
to fight the Worldkillers.
-Okay.
-I know she's upset right now,
but she's gonna help us.
Welcome to the bizarro version
where she does not
help the DEO,
-right... right here.
-What?
Oh, God! No.
-If Lena doesn't help us
fight the Worldkillers, then--
-Yep.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. You're skipping a lot!
This is all exposition,
so much exposition.
Hold on! Was that Mon-El?
Yes.
-So, he didn't go
back to the future?
-No.
Huh. Of course.
If we didn't
defeat Pestilence,
-then he would have
been there with us...
-Uh-huh.
...when we went
to Sam's mom's house.
Can you...
Can you snap me in there?
I want to get his perspective.
I never understood
what you saw in him.
You need to leave
for your own safety.
I... I won't leave my daughter.
I failed her
when she was a girl.
I refuse to fail her again.
Well, is there
at least a safe place
for you to hide?
There's a safe room.
I'll wait there.
-We should take up
defensive positions.
-No, wait. Um...
I need your advice.
I finally told Lena
I'm Supergirl.
Wow.
How... How did she take it?
Not well.
And I don't blame her.
I mean, I'm supposed to
be her best friend,
and I... I lied
and betrayed her
just like everyone else
in her life has.
So, what do I do?
You know, Lena and I
have a lot in common.
We've both been betrayed
by our own families.
And when the people
who are supposed to
love you the most
let you down,
it just makes you feel so...
so vulnerable, you know?
But my mother and the Luthors,
they betrayed Lena
for their own selfish reasons.
They...
They wanted to
take advantage of her.
You lied to... to protect her.
Because she's your friend.
Now, I know Lena's hurting
right now, but...
once she understands that...
she'll forgive you.
I hope you're right.
But I don't think
I'll ever be able
to forgive myself.
You know it's okay
to mess up, right?
No matter how many
mistakes I've made,
you've always forgiven me.
You should, uh, know that
you deserve
the same compassion
that you show others.
Reign will be here soon.
We should get ready.
Did you miss me?
Sam! Sam, no, this isn't you!
I know you're in there,
I know you are!
No.
You really thought
you could stop me, Supergirl?
You can't even protect
this one pathetic human.
Oh, Sam...
No. But I can.
Because this is the tool
I use to bring Reign out
and bury you down.
Come back to us, Sam!
I will kill...
you all!
No, you won't.
Sam! Sam!
Lena.
What happened?
Sam, it's okay. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Oh, Sam,
I'm so sorry.
You did it!
You saved Sam.
Yeah, and I did it
without Kryptonite.
No!
Fool!
I am a Worldkiller.
And I cannot be stopped!
No!
Sam! No! No! No! Sam!
No, please!
Come back to me, Sam!
Mxy,
they're all dead.
Please, get me out of here.
Lena was never angry
about hypocrisy.
She was angry because
I never shared my identity
with her in the first place.
So, you know
what that means?
We have to go back
to the very beginning.
Give me a date and a time,
I will make it so.
-Um, let me think.
-Uh...
Hang on a second.
It's just, it's buffering.
This happens sometimes.
It's the
interdimensional Wi-Fi.
You know what?
It doesn't even matter.
I've got your entire friendship
on BetaMyx.
So, when did
the two of you
become friends?
Uh... It... It was...
Right after Lena moved
to National City.
You have had
a lot of adventures.
"Lena," please.
It's good to see you again,
Miss Danvers.
-If I'm calling you "Lena"...
-Kara--
- Oh, it's too...
- Anything?
-Too soon.
I wrote a scathing article
about your device.
Mmm... Getting closer. Here.
I would hate for you
to give me these emails
out of some misplaced
sense of friendship.
This was right before
Lena and I
really became friends.
See, she's about to say,
I didn't come here
to make friends.
She didn't wanna let anyone in,
and then, when she did,
I made the mistake
of not letting her in, too.
This time,
I'm gonna do it right.
Bye!
I didn't come here
to make friends.
I wanna show you something.
Listen, I'm really busy,
so, if we could just--
It's you.
-Kara Danvers is Supergirl.
-Yeah.
Can't believe I was fooled
by a pair of glasses.
Don't worry,
a lot people are.
Oh, God,
I have to recall all those
alien detection devices
'cause they clearly don't work.
You're not angry?
No, it's incredible.
I mean, you're incredible!
But...
Why are you trusting me
with such a big secret?
You barely know me.
Because I know that
what you want
more than anything
is to do good.
And I know it's hard
for you to trust people,
but I need you to know now,
without a doubt,
I trust you.
My cousin,
your brother,
they got it wrong.
Imagine what we
could do together.
A Luthor and a Super,
working together as a team.
If we were partners,
we could change the world.
Only months after publicly
declaring their partnership,
the formidable duo
of Supergirl and Lena Luthor
has already cleaned up
National City's
criminal element.
This pair is
literally unstoppable!
Not to mention, fashionable
after Lena convinced Supergirl
to cut the hair of steel,
and gave her
a new suit to boot.
But their next adversary
is Lillian Luthor herself,
and this time,
their battleground
is a courtroom.
Emotions. Drama.
Will they persevere?
Mxy, can you please
take this seriously?
Take it seriously,
because every party
needs a pooper,
and that's why
we invited Kara.
Really?
If we're gonna take
the fun out of stuff,
let's really do it.
And what is
Supergirl's real name?
I hardly see
how that's relevant.
Citizens have the right
to know the name of the officer
that arrests them.
If Supergirl is gonna act
like judge and jury,
we should know
her name as well.
I plead the Fifth.
Powerful testimonies
in the trial
of Lillian Luthor today.
But will they be undercut
by Lena Luthor's refusal
to give up
Supergirl's identity?
Well, nothing so trifling
as the laws of man
could stand
in the way of Supergirl
and Lena Luthor's
divine victories!
Where I once thought
that true power was
the Kryptonian
walking amongst us,
but that power is nothing
compared to the might
of a Kryptonian
paired with a Luthor!
This is incredible.
The last time
Lillian was on trial,
the whole world suspected Lena
of working with her,
-but having Supergirl
as a partner...
...it gives Lena
the credibility her last name
never could.
-This is it.
-Yes.
This is the timeline
where I truly
do no harm to Lena,
and the world sees her
for the hero she really is.
Of course, I'm more than happy to donate.
Okay.
- Miss Luthor.
- Oh, no.
Is that Lockwood?
You knew my father,
Pete Lockwood?
You're Ben.
We were sourcing our steel
from his factory,
and then he abruptly closed it.
No, he didn't close it.
He converted it to a church.
The Cult of Rao.
I'm so sorry, Ben.
If Supergirl and I
can do anything
to help your father--
You can't.
Because he's dead.
My father, my wife,
my only son, George,
they jumped off a roof
because they believed...
that she would save them.
And she didn't.
I'm so sorry, Ben.
If there's anything
I could do to help--
Well, you could tell me
who Supergirl is.
She parades around as a god,
but she hides in plain sight
as a human.
Miss Luthor, if...
if people knew who she was,
if they knew
that she bought a coffee
in the morning
or that she rode the bus
or that she worked a job
just like the rest of us,
then they would stop
worshipping her.
So, I have to know who she is.
And you are going to tell me.
It's never gonna happen.
And if you have issues
with the Cult of Rao,
I suggest you take it up
with Coville.
Oh... I already have.
Hiya!
Thomas Coville
wants you to believe
that National City's
resident Kryptonian
is someone worth worshipping,
worth dying for.
Is Supergirl a god?
I'm not sure about that.
Not sure about that.
When she goes home at night,
did you know
that she lives
a secret human life?
Until today.
Until today, because today,
Supergirl will reveal
her identity to the world,
or... Coville
and Miss Luthor will die.
No. Supergirl, don't do it!
So, Supergirl, one hour
of breathable oxygen left,
the clock starts now.
What're you gonna do?
Uh... No spoilers.
I'm loving this.
Uh, I mean...
I can't trace
the signal.
Look, some lone wolf
shouldn't have the resources
to thwart our trackers.
He must have powerful help.
Yeah, help spelled L-E-X.
If that's the case,
then we are
never gonna find her.
Stay here, I got it.
Every morning
when I wake up...
I imagine this moment.
The moment where
being Supergirl gets
someone I love killed.
And I have push that fear
so far down...
...or I... I can't
get out of bed.
But now, here it is.
My greatest fear,
just staring me
right in the face.
I have to save Lena.
I... I have to,
but if I tell the world
who I am,
then I put everyone else I love
at even greater risk.
Alex, J'onn, James, you.
What if one of you gets hurt?
Don't worry about
the rest of us, okay?
We're gonna be fine.
No, Lena is the one
that needs your help
right now.
We can take care
of ourselves...
because you taught us how.
We're here
at National City Hall,
where Supergirl is set
to arrive any minute,
and announce her human identity
to the world.
-Oh, sorry.
-Jeez. You're strong.
Hello.
I am Kara Danvers.
Some of you may know me
as a reporter
for CatCo Worldwide Media.
-But I am also...
Kara Zor-El, of Krypton.
I am Supergirl.
Good stuff, my dude!
But we should kill
the hostages anyway, right?
No.
No, we keep our word.
Send them the location.
Are you okay?
Just breathe, Lena. It's okay.
Maybe it's time
the world knows.
I've always been
so afraid to reveal
my identity to the world,
but look, it saved Lena.
Maybe...
Just maybe, this...
this is the timeline
to stick with. Let's...
I see why
you would think that,
but, um, maybe
we should skip ahead
to the ending?
Oh, no, what happens?
After Supergirl's identity
was released to the world,
Agent Liberty
and his followers targeted
each of Supergirl's friends,
including her former
employer Cat Grant...
-No.
-...one by one.
There were no survivors.
-All right, all right,
enough. Stop.
-Alex Danvers, Winn Schott...
-I don't wanna see anymore.
Please turn it off, please.
-...J'onn J'onzz...
It doesn't matter
when I tell Lena the truth.
It always makes things worse.
I think I've been
too scared to admit it
to myself, but...
I think Lena would
be better off if she and I
were never friends.
Is that the world
you wanna see?
No.
Please just show me anyway.
What happened?
Where are we?
Where your loft used to be.
Uh...
You know what? No thanks.
-Nope. I don't need to see it.
-Yeah.
-Can you just
snap us out of here?
-Yep. With pleasure.
What's happening?
I can't feel
the Fifth Dimension at all.
Without my powers--
We're stuck here?
We should get out of here.
You think?
Citizens,
you're out after curfew,
in defiance of Luthor Law.
This world sucks!
You don't know the half of it.
Look who I found.
Oh, Kara,
thank God you're here.
Who's this?
Oh, this is
my friend, Mxyzptlk.
-Mxyzptlk?
- Yeah.
What, you thought
with the new face,
we wouldn't recognize
the same old you?
This is the guy who tried
to make Kara marry him.
It's fine, Mon-El.
Because he is reformed...
and he's actually helping me.
Uh, no... You know what?
No, Mon-El is right. Okay?
It was despicable of me
to pursue a woman
who so clearly
was not interested in me
from the get-go.
I misread the room,
and I'm gonna be better.
It's tough to be an imp.
And I'm gonna try
for the rest of my days.
So, maybe we can let
the past be the past, huh?
Come on.
Wow. Okay, you won.
We'll need all the help
we can get.
All right, well,
look... things are not
as they seem,
and I will explain, but...
First, will someone
please tell me
what's going on here?
People of National City,
I regret to inform you
that the terrorist
known as Supergirl
-is at large.
-Terrorist?
She's working with
a Fifth Dimensional being,
capable of mass destruction.
H.O.P.E. Robots have
been deployed throughout
the city for your protection.
Please, report to them any
and all suspicious activity.
And remember...
My goal is,
as it has always been...
to protect you from harm.
No.
When Lena first came
to National City...
to take over L-Corp,
Lex tried
to have her assassinated.
He failed,
but she was seriously injured
in the attack.
She disappeared for two years.
When she came back,
everybody said that
she was different,
that she had changed.
The trauma,
the loneliness...
it drove her mad.
She retaliated against Lex,
killed him.
Took half of National City
along with her.
Now, she rules what's left
with an iron fist.
-Reign is her enforcer.
-And Brainy, too.
She captured him. Aligned him.
Now, he has no emotions...
and does whatever
Lena tells him to.
Oh, no.
This, this... I have made
a terrible mistake.
This world
is my responsibility.
Okay. Okay,
we can still fix this.
- I need
my powers.
- Mmm-hmm.
But since we've been here...
They've disappeared.
That must be because
Lena tapped into
the Fifth Dimensional energy
to use it to power
her police robots.
And as long as she's
harnessing the Fifth Dimension,
then you can't access it.
I worked at L-Corp
for about two years
before Lena found me out.
Uh, we caught a criminal.
He didn't have a name,
but he had a hat
that he could
pull anything out of.
Old drinking buddy of mine.
I lost that hat to him
in a poker game.
That hat contains a lot
of Fifth Dimensional magic.
So, if we get you the hat...
Get me the hat,
I can make all of this go...
-bye-bye.
Surrender the imp or die!
Get the hat!
We'll hold her off!
Come on,
I'll show you the way!
And I've got your back!
Brainy, it's me.
It's Nia.
You don't have to do this.
I know I don't have to.
But I think I will enjoy it.
Go to Lena, I've got Reign.
Lena?
It's me.
It's Supergirl.
It's Kara.
Who's Kara?
Just a friend.
You don't know me.
Not really.
But you and I want
the same thing...
to do no harm.
Supergirl wants a world
without harm.
That's rich.
Where were you
when my brother blew
my helicopter out of the sky?
When my mother dragged
my broken body to a laboratory
and experimented on me
instead of fixing me?
Where were you
when this world was
ripped apart by the seams?
Where were you?
I'm sorry I wasn't there
when it mattered.
So am I.
The hat's in this room.
I can feel it.
It's J'onn.
-He needs our help.
-No, he needs this.
Time to face justice,
Manhunter.
J'onn! Catch!
Dreamer, do it now!
You don't know
the first thing about pain.
But I do. I can show you,
make you feel what I feel.
I won't fight you, Lena.
Then you'll die screaming.
Found it.
We're home.
Holy cow!
That was the most
emotionally draining
experience of my life,
and let me tell ya,
I've had some doozies.
Okay. So, it ain't over
till it's over.
So, now,
we've gotta find a time
for you to go back
and tell Lena the truth.
-You ready for one more go?
-No.
No. Absolutely not!
I realize now
that it doesn't matter
when I tell Lena the truth.
There will always
be consequences.
Huge ones.
And if I can't go back
and snap my mistakes away,
I'm just gonna
have to live with them.
-Oh...
Oh...
-Oh, boy.
Okay.
I know it didn't turn out
the way we expected,
but you...
You still helped me, Mxy.
You freed me
from my burden of guilt, so...
-Go, be free.
-Ah.
Use your magic to do
whatever it is you do.
Thank you.
Um...
And I should say, uh...
Before I met you,
I was, um...
I was pretty lonely.
You know, and in that pain,
I... I would tend to sort of,
force myself...
on people, and, uh...
Out there with you today,
saving the world,
I felt like, um...
I felt like I was liked,
for being me.
I felt like I had friends.
And, uh...
it's true
what you said, Kara.
That magic...
can't be forced.
It has to be found.
I'm proud of you, Mxy.
Thanks for everything.
You're welcome.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to Mardi Gras
in the '80s.
The 1780s.
Let me guess...
You're here to
tell me once again
that I should forgive you.
Or maybe that I shouldn't
work with my brother?
Not this time.
I recognize I made a mistake
in hiding my identity
from you for so long,
but the past is the past,
and I can't change it.
Forgive me or not,
that's your choice.
Just like it's your choice
to work with Lex.
I'm done blaming myself
for your bad decisions.
Then why are you here?
To tell you that
from now on,
you're accountable
for your own actions.
If you decide to forgive me,
I will be there for you.
But if you continue
to work with Lex...
If you go through
with whatever it is
the two of you are planning,
I will do everything
in my power to stop you...
just like I would
any other villain.
This is an extraordinary
amount of food.
A parting gift from Mxy.
Well, I think
we should have Mxy
here more often.
I hear
Fifth Dimensional interventions
do wonders
for one's perspective.
You know what?
Actually, they really do.
Seeing all those
alternate versions of reality
made me realize,
second-guessing myself
doesn't do any good.
No.
So, if I make a mistake,
I just have to move on.
What is that smile?
You guys.
Guys, you've been
with me from...
the second I became Supergirl.
In my best moments
and especially
my worst moments.
That means the world to me.
Sames.
Back at you.
El-may-arah.
-Aw.
"Stronger together."
-Potato.
-Po-tah-to.