Previously on
Supergirl...
Dark Kryptonian witches want to resurrect Reign and use her to terraform the Earth,
turning it into a new Krypton.
Leviathan is coming.
You can go, Margot.
When we restarted the universe,
our worlds combined.
The DEO, CatCo,
all of National City is
on this Earth now.
Lex Luthor has
the Book of Destiny.
We thought destiny could use
a little rewrite.
- People think
Lex is a good guy?
-He's the boss!
He owns this place.
We live in a world
on the cutting edge.
And as mankind advances,
so too does the danger
it faces.
For years, we protected
America in secret.
But now, we want you to know
you're in good hands.
Hope, help
and compassion for all.
-That's our motto here at...
-The DEO.
Call us for all
your extranormal needs.
Duh! Gag me with a spoon.
I don't care what
world we're on,
I can't ever see a version
of myself agreeing to do
that commercial.
Well, on this planet,
you and Lex were
excellent collaborators.
No, stop! This is literally
my nightmare.
Okay, well,
how do you think I feel?
I've been totally in the dark.
Thank God J'onn gave me
my memories back.
Yeah, I know, I wish he could
do it for everyone.
Well, according to him,
restoring the world's
collective memories
would reconfigure relationships
on such a massive scale
that everyone's minds
would literally be blown.
Ugh, gross.
Well, the DEO is
a hellmouth now,
so there's that.
-Has CatCo changed?
-Still a tabloid.
But everyone's on
the Lex Luthor train,
which is great.
Including Andrea.
He's getting some
Man of Tomorrow award,
and she sent me
and William to cover it.
I... uh, I can't believe
even William is drinking
the Lex Kool-Aid.
Well, you gotta give him
a little break, okay.
The only people that know
the truth are the ones whose
memories have been restored.
So it's Brainy, Nia, Kelly...
All the heroes
who helped at the Crisis,
including you know who,
which just makes my blood boil.
Well, the Luthors are a breed
of their own.
Yeah, speaking of which,
I have to talk to Lena.
Look, on this Earth,
Lena and Supergirl
are partners.
And as far as I'm concerned,
she's not trying to
mind control the planet.
Plus, she doesn't hate you,
so maybe Lena not having
her memories
is a good thing.
No, no.
As much  as I would
love to have a clean slate
with Lena,
I owe it to her
to tell the truth.
I made that mistake once,
I'm not going to do it again.
- Hey, there, sleepy head.
I fried a couple of eggs
for you.
Methohexital hangovers
are no joke.
You must be ravenous.
This can't be real.
You're dead.
So, you remember everything?
Of course I remember!
I killed you!
Yes, that's right,
you killed me.
But that is all in the past.
-Because I'm back now,
and I forgive you.
What are you talking about?
What is happening?
Well, it was, uh...
sort of a Crisis.
It was an...
antimatter wave.
-Ah, yes.
-Alex and I worked together.
-Mmm-hmm.
-We built a portal...
The wave still came?
Yes, and billions were lost
and the multi-verse collapsed,
and it was all
very interesting.
What matters now
is that a very powerful person
brought me back
to life to help.
But I refused to do so,
unless he promised
that you would
make it through okay,
and you have,
with your noggin intact.
You gambled the fate
of the entire multi-verse
to get your own way?
It gets better.
In this new world,
we work side by side
at Luthor Corp and the DEO
to make the world
a better place.
So I'm in hell.
No, no,
you're in a new reality.
To the outside world,
we're billionaire
philanthropists.
It's the perfect cover.
-I want nothing to do with you.
-Ah, yes, you want to
fix humanity
with your project Non Nocere.
And using Myriad to broadcast
the Q-waves. That was smart.
But you should have known
the moment you decided to steal
from a Kryptonian,
the Non Nocere was doomed.
Kara Danvers will never see
things your way.
She'll always work against you.
Right, so you'll be
my friend now?
The world is ours now, Lena.
You don't need a robot
and you don't need friends.
You need a partner.
Imagine what
we could accomplish together.
Why not give it a go?
So you think
this is your world now?
You were a puppet on a string
for Leviathan before.
What makes this time
any different?
What the hell is Leviathan?
I want you to know
I'll be doubling my efforts
to calibrate my emotions
with my actions.
To wit, your favorite
breakfast smoothie.
And despite every urge
in my corporeal being,
I ordered only two.
Thanks, Brainy.
My good man,
I'm picking up a to-go order
for Barney Fife,
-if anyone asks...
-Halt.
Oh, my.
What?
What is the meaning of this?
-Meaning... I don't--
-Who are you?
-I'm Brainiac-5.
-What?
-Liar!
-You, sir,
are the larcenist
and pretender. How did
you accomplish this ruse?
Could it be an image inducer?
-The question of pretending
is to you, sir!
What are you, huh?
Martian, Durlan?
Is your face made of clay?
Unhand me, you charlatan!
Okay, that's it. I'm taking you
into the DEO for questioning.
Okay, that's rich!
Guess what,
I'm taking you into the DEO
for questioning.
Oh, that's rich...
Citizens arrest!
I've been looking for you.
Here I am.
So, uh, there's something
I have to tell you.
I know you think
Lex is a good man,
-that he's your partner--
-Save it. I already know.
What exactly do you know?
The Crisis, what Lex did.
-What you did.
-Lex.
That you took the punch.
What did you think would
happen when you came here?
That you'd tell me everything
in a fit of selflessness,
even if it meant that I knew
how you betrayed me,
and then I'd just keel over
and forgive you.
Lena, I hurt you. I--
I know I hurt you.
And I'm never ever going
to do it again.
And I know how much good
you want to do in the world.
Just think of what we could do
together to help people.
Funny.
Lex gave me the same pitch.
He asked you to help him?
You're not seriously
considering it, are you?
Please, just be careful.
Director Danvers!
What is going on?
Exactly the correct question.
Paradox to be sure.
There must be a reasonable
explanation.
And we will get one,
once you confess.
Uh, I know I'm gonna regret
asking this question,
but which of you
is my Brainy?
How can you
seriously ask that?
Well...
Get an interrogation
room ready.
I'm sorry,
who the hell are you?
I'm Director Brainiac-5
of the DEO.
I am the Director of the DEO.
Why is everyone yelling!
Oh, you have got
to be sprocking me!
You're all in grave danger.
Don't let him open...
the bottle.
Someone killed him?
He was targeted,
which means any of the
others could be next.
No,
you weren't kidding.
No. Thank you.
DNA doesn't lie,
so you are all Brainiac-5.
This reminds me of a situation
with some crabs on Helven.
Terrible experience.
He seems to have been killed
by some sort
of biosynthetic virus.
The Anti-Life Equation.
The... sorry, what?
It's a techno-organic poison.
It's targeted and transmitted
through the big brain.
It's really scary, man!
I've never heard
of such a thing.
We're supposed to believe
that you're the Brainy Prime?
Well, it's true. He's ours.
Well, then this can't be
our world.
Which means we must have
stumbled through
some sort of...
Dimensional wormhole.
From our different universes.
Wormhole... Universes, yeah.
I'm sorry, guys,
there's a slight crisis--
The only logical path forward
is to find the nexus point
of our arrival,
if we're ever
to ascertain how it is
we came to be here,
why our deceased
comrade warned us
we're in grave danger?
What that bottle was
he urged us not to open?
After which, we can
all safely return
to our respective Earths.
Agreed.
Yes, except you can't return
to your Earths because
the multi-verse is dead.
-So.
- Brainy.
Oh, uh, all right.
That is insensitive.
What? The multi-verse,
it's dead?
Unless there's a vibrational
frequency henceforth
unknown to man, then...
our universe is
the only one that's left.
- Apologies
for the interruption,
but would Director Danvers
and Supergirl, please report
to the conference room
immediately?
What do you want, Lex?
-Peace.
-It's never gonna happen.
Look,  I get it,
feels icky, but why don't
we think about it
in another way?
Why go to war
and make things messy,
when we could all play
a comfortable game
of chess?
You could keep an eye on me,
I could keep an eye on you,
and in the meantime,
the world would have
its favorite heroes
standing shoulder to shoulder
to keep threats like
the Anti-Monitor
and Leviathan at bay.
Say, what's happening
with those guys anyway?
Any rumblings?
The Anti-Monitor is gone.
And we haven't found a trace
of Leviathan since the
multi-verse collapsed. So...
So the only threat
to this world is you.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Look, take a day
to think it over.
And if you choose peace,
I'll expect you by my side,
publicly, at the Man
of Tomorrow ceremony.
But if you don't,
I suppose we'll have
a little more apocalypse.
Eighty-two percent
of customers with cell phone
plans have purchased
our VR add-on.
But we can still do better.
We need to get Obsidian into
every American household,
and we are so close.
Quite close, indeed.
Wha-- what a pleasant surprise!
-Hi!
-Hello!
Team, this is Gemma Cooper,
one of our board members
and my beloved college mentor.
-That's all. Thank you.
Okay, it took some
technical doing,
but I believe
I've confirmed that--
We are the only Brainiac-5s
that came through the wormhole,
which you've now traced
to Al's Bar.
Yeah, we, too, deduced that
several moments ago,
but hey, Al's bar,
I do love
their margarita mocktails.
Perhaps we should go...
Oh! No, no, no, no, no.
Prime, help me
root out the virus.
How? Uh, I don't...
Okay. It's okay. That's okay.
I got you. Here we go.
-Okay.
You know, I could have
died just there.
Thanks to your hesitancy.
We're supposed to believe
that he's a Brainiac-5!
Friends, friends, focus.
The virus is transmittable
from anywhere.
Any one of us could be next.
You, stay here.
We'll head down to Al's bar.
We'll get to the bottom
of this.
-Okay.
-There he goes.
Handsome. Look at him go.
I'll go get Supergirl.
Hey, what's going on here...
Als.
Everybody just showed up
out of the blue last night.
Business has never been better.
I had to open up the back room.
Has this place
always been here?
-Yup. I closed it in '79
after disco died.
-How old are you?
-Shh.
-These guys brought a ton
of stuff with them, though.
-You guys missing anything?
- What fun!
Look, whatever caused
that wormhole
didn't just drag us through,
it dragged everyone
from Al's bar
in each of our universes.
Oh, dear.
Are those...
Don't make
any sudden movements.
Those are the witches
that created Reign.
And tried to terraform
our entire planet.
Those aren't your witches.
They come from my world.
They came
to National City as tourists
and never left.
I let them run a little
side hustle out of the bar.
Come forth, my children.
Have your fortune read.
I prefer to avoid such
unreliable forecasting
mechanisms.
Crystals balls! Ha-ha.
A lot more real
than fool's gold.
Allow me to read your stones.
Please, forgive my sisters.
Palm reading is the
fastest path to your fate.
Five dollars, ten minutes.
Hmm, no thank you.
-Uh, suit yourself.
-Typical.
No one on this Earth
values our gifts.
Everyone in this bar
came from an Earth
that was destroyed.
They're all orphans.
That's terrible.
No, Supergirl!
The entire multi-verse
was destroyed.
An accident of fate kept
us and these people alive.
This isn't a tragedy.
It's a, you know,
it's a miracle.
Okay, we need
to divide and conquer.
And please, try to blend in,
because there is still
a murderer out there
and both of you are
still in danger. Okay?
Good.
I never thought I'd
live to see the day
my mother wore petal pink.
Technically, you didn't.
We all died. We all came back.
And we both know it.
Lex restored
your memories, too.
He told me everything.
But, evidently,
the only person he makes
deals with gods for is you.
I'm glad
he told you everything.
I have no one else.
I hope you're
not looking for a hug.
No. But it occurred to me
I could use a partner.
If Lex told you everything,
then he told you my goal was
to fix people at their core.
I tried to do it alone.
I closed myself off,
made myself an island,
and I failed.
You pushed people away
and put all your faith
in that robot.
Reminds me
of little Miss Pizzly.
Your teddy bear
from when you were four.
Cute and useless.
We both know your ideology
is of no use to me.
I've got
a good thing going here.
Well, in that case...
Supergirl wants
to partner with me.
Part of me wants to do it.
You can try to only be
partners this time,
but in a moment of weakness,
you'll let your guard down,
you'll become friends
once more,
and you'll be vulnerable
when she hurts you
all over again.
And yet,
you don't want to be an island.
No.
I will never trust Lex again.
If you choose
to partner with Lex,
you won't risk your emotions,
because you already know
you can never trust him.
I report to Lex Luthor.
This is worst-case scenario.
I don't know how I'm supposed
to work for him,
and yet we all know
that he's this bomb
that could just blow
at any minute.
So, I mean,
can I even really leave?
You know, long before
I recruited you,
an alien named Izzy was held
captive by her co-worker.
Now, he'd found out
what she really was
and couldn't control his rage.
Izzy was naturally terrified.
But because
her attacker was human,
the DEO didn't have
jurisdiction.
Things were different
back then.
I felt so helpless.
So what did you do?
What I knew I had to do.
I disobeyed orders.
Ran in there and tackled
that man to the ground myself.
Sometimes there's nothing to do
but listen to the truth
inside you, Alex.
The honor comes in running
toward the bomb.
Seven hundred
and sixty-two bottles of beer
on the wall.
And they're all completely
lacking in clues.
Talking to yourself.
You can talk to me
instead, if you'd like.
I'm you, after all.
Ignored us all day,
and now you want to talk.
I see you.
You've been one step behind
the rest of us at every turn.
What is making you different?
It's not a big deal
or anything,
but I do wear...
Personality inhibiters.
I knew it.
Why would you wear those?
-For protection.
-Protection?
Personality inhibitors
block you from engaging
with the big brain.
They stop you from accessing
your true self.
Your true potential,
your true happiness.
Don't you ever
feel inconsistent?
Uncertain?
Unable to balance logic
and emotion?
I mean, look at you,
you're not even green.
Okay, sure.
And what about the anger?
Hmm? The rage?
I don't wear these
to protect myself!
I wear them to protect
the people I love.
Where I'm from, I was married.
I was stronger, smarter,
better, every moment
I was with her.
-You lost her?
-No.
She's with me.
She lives on in the big brain.
Just as I will,
when my work here is finished.
What I'm saying
is love is not meant
to minimize you.
It makes you more.
More capable.
More compassionate.
And the people
who really love you,
they don't want this for you.
I appreciate the chat, Kor-El,
but I feel very capable
as I am.
Suit yourself.
A hologram, this whole time.
Now I see how rude that is.
I always thought
my Brainy was one of a kind.
I'm sorry, I'm Nia.
My Brainy filled me in
on everything
and I just had to see
you all for myself.
I brought lunch. You hungry?
No, I...  sorry.
I just wanna
be alone right now.
He also said something
about a bottle.
A bottle.
Alas...
You have caught me in the act.
But I'm glad.
The act was
emotionally exhausting.
What's in the bottle?
Seven billion souls
on my Earth.
All here.
Bottled at the source.
Moments before
the antimatter wave came.
No more waiting.
Sweet release.
You bottled your world.
I saved them.
Prevented genocide.
Now, stuck in stasis,
is that truly life?
Or is it just
some hideous form
of distasteful death?
Why don't we take it upstairs?
We can hash out the
philosophy there.
There is nothing to hash.
There is only life.
And death.
Take the other Brainiac-5.
He tried to prevent me
from opening this bottle,
so I killed him.
Death!
But once I find the device
with which to open
this bottle,
life...
Brainy!
Nia.
No!
He was piggybacking off
Brainy Prime's
personality inhibitors
to confuse the big brain
and disguise
his true intentions.
What were his intentions?
He shrunk his entire Earth.
He bottled it.
The shrinking and collection
of worlds is distinctly Coluan.
It's a terribly common practice
among our ancestors.
But this Brainy bottled
his world to protect it?
Yeah, but if he releases
his Earth,
both Earths will be destroyed.
But he couldn't
open the bottle.
Indeed, all bottles are sealed
beneath the quantum level to--
Prevent escape.
Bottles can only be opened
using a device that harnesses
Argonium 44.
He must have known the Argonium
Saber would be held here
at the DEO.
That saber is the only one
that I am aware of
in the solar system.
And I destroyed it,
so that bought us some time.
Brainy.
It's incredible.
It's like being
on the moon.
Except for the lack
of gravity.
We're still figuring that out.
But we're making
incredible progress.
Progress isn't just Obsidian
being in every household.
It's about every household
being in Obsidian.
-What do you mean?
-Tell me something.
If you never had to work
for your father,
what would Andrea Rojas
want to be right now?
An anthropologist.
Oh, I love it.
You can live on
a sprawling hacienda,
close to your latest
Aztec dig site.
-It's a pleasant dream.
-Not a dream.
A reality.
In a true virtual world.
When someone holds
an artifact that you found,
they feel its weight
in their actual hand.
Imagine a whole new world,
a whole new reality for
harmed and damaged people.
They can live
their dream lives.
And eventually,
they could stay there.
Indefinitely.
A collective of being.
A true virtual world
will change the game.
What do I always tell you?
You gotta move the needle.
And with this...
Our share prices could double.
Brainy, stop.
You don't have to...
When I was eight years old,
my family went on...
what humans might
call a vacation.
This was the first time
I had seen the snow.
It was incredible.
Why are you telling me this?
'Cause my mother saw
how much I loved it.
How badly I...
I wanted to stay there
in the snow.
And so, she bottled it for me.
-The entire planet.
-Brainy...
My father was horrified
at what she had done.
He freed the planet.
I was so young
and angry with him...
for taking away my planet.
My planet!
And that anger terrified him.
He feared that I, too,
could hold such
darkness within me.
That I could become my mother.
So he placed three
personality inhibitors on me.
The same ones I wear
to this very day.
Your three dots.
When I wear them,
I'm not fully calibrated
with the Coluan network
of minds, the big brain.
If I hadn't been wearing them,
that bad Brainy wouldn't
have been able to fool us.
And you're afraid
to take them off?
Because I might be worse.
And Nia, she...
She might not care for me.
Brainy, you are good
to your core.
You will never be your mother.
-How could you be sure?
-Because you're loved.
And the people that love you
will always fight for you.
Thank you, Kara.
Your ability to instill hope
and comfort with
your words is...
is nothing short of magic.
-Magic.
- The witches
can open the bottle.
He's going to Al's.
We have to tell
the other Brainys.
No, I, I need to do this alone.
-But you should come, too.
-I'm coming.
Why are you helping him?
You could have
a peaceful life here.
The Crisis brought us
to a strange world.
If the Coluan is successful,
he will return us home.
Opening that bottle
isn't worth the risk.
Yes, it is.
You could kill everyone.
Why should this Earth live,
when every other died?
'Cause it's the only one
we've got left!
Enough talk.
It's been ages since we had
a good bar fight.
Wait!
We can't undo the past.
Watch us.
-Brainy.
This is all my fault.
Brainy, it's okay.
You can take them off.
But what if I turn...
No matter what happens,
I love you.
No, don't!
I know you lost
your whole world,
your friends, your home.
I miss what I had, too.
I know what
you're going through.
How responsible you must feel.
You don't know anything!
But I know everything
because I'm you.
I feel the darkness, too.
You've made some bad choices,
but they don't have
to define you.
I lost everything.
It's not too late
to make a different choice.
Let us help you.
My friends and I,
we're pretty smart.
Together, we can find a safe
place to open your bottle
without hurting anyone.
The suave one
is right.
It is too much of a risk.
But if we give these people
a chance,
they may find a way
of returning us home one day.
All we can do
is wait for that day.
But you don't
have to wait alone,
we can wait with you.
Supergirl and Dreamer are
bringing the bottle to
the fortress for safekeeping.
Which solves the problem
of one errant Brainiac-5.
We were thinking that, too.
Life projectors.
Our worlds may be gone,
but the big brain remains.
A digital cloud where
Ms. Dox and I can relinquish
our corporeal forms
and live amongst the Coluan
knowledge aggregate.
-You don't have to do that.
-We want to.
We may have lost our worlds,
but existing inside
of the big brain
will feel like...
like going home.
Thank you.
Both of you.
For everything.
Thank you, Brainiac-5,
and, uh, sorry for trying
to take your smoothie.
What a strange sensation.
There's something
you need to know.
The reason I left the two
of you to face today's
threat alone
is because I've been tracking
Lex Luthor's every move.
He's been calling the archive
for information on only
one thing, Leviathan.
Leviathan is defeated.
Leviathan is everywhere.
The timeline of our worlds
is closer than any other.
Events progress
on the same path.
You must not make
the same mistakes I made.
I fought against Lex Luthor,
and it led to catastrophe
beyond imagining.
It endangered the entire world.
If you're gonna save
your world,
you have to work
with Lex Luthor.
I'll show you everything
you need to know.
I'll show you everything I did
wrong in my world,
how bad things became.
But Kor-El.
Kor-El, you must do this alone.
No one can know
that you're doing this.
You must give up everyone
and everything that
you hold dear.
Even Nia?
Till the world has been saved.
I'm sorry.
Kor-El,
you'll never truly be alone.
-I will be with you.
Aren't you supposed to be
at a ceremony or something?
Success isn't worth much
if you don't have anyone
to share it with.
I always wanted to share
my victories with you, sis.
Even last year,
with the Kasnians,
I brought you in.
Doesn't that count
for anything?
One moment of thoughtfulness
to make up for
years of betrayal? No.
I know you have plenty
of reasons to distrust me,
but you don't know
what it's like to...
die.
The sickening desperation
when you see it coming for you.
It made me want to lash out.
It made me want to hurt you.
Like I hurt you.
Killed me.
But that's exactly my point.
Death truly has changed me.
The old me would be dreaming
of the myriad ways I could
exact my revenge on you,
but the new me can see
how pathetically pedestrian
that is.
I'm finally ready to be
a true partner, Lena.
How am I supposed
to believe you?
You were a sociopath, a liar.
What you need is the truth.
The Truth Seeker will prevent
me from lying.
So, sis, what do you
want to know?
Can you help me
achieve Non Nocere?
Better and faster
than anybody else.
Will you truly be
on your best behavior?
No homicides?
No unnecessary homicides.
This is about doing no harm.
But I won't. I have everything
I want except for
your partnership.
When will you turn on me?
As soon as this partnership
inconveniences me.
Just like you'll use
Non Nocere on me
as soon as you get the chance.
Good. As long as we're clear.
You don't need me.
Why do you really want
to work with me?
Truthfully,
I don't want to be alone.
-Hey.
-Hello.
How do you feel?
-Uninhibited?
-Something like that.
You know, I'm really glad
to see you so comfortable
in your own skin.
It's all I ever
really wanted for you
was to be able to be yourself.
And now I am.
I can feel it,
all through my body.
The tips of my fingers.
And now, some things
are gonna have to change, Nia.
Of course. Look, Brainy,
whatever you need,
we'll work it out.
Together.
Together... that's...
That's what has to change.
-What?
-I can't be with
you anymore.
I don't understand.
Who are you?
For the first time, ever,
myself.
Welcome, everyone.
It gives me great pleasure
to be here tonight.
Hey, what are
you doing over here?
I just, uh...
Look, I know you're gonna
think I'm crazy,
but I'm not so sure Lex Luthor
is what he says he is.
-What?
- ...with the deeds
of just a few people...
I thought you loved him
like everyone else.
While I was still
at The Timesin London,
Lex tried to buy my friend,
Russell Roger's company.
Russell refused
and ended up dead.
I think Lex Luthor
was behind it.
Do you have
any concrete evidence?
Not yet.
That's why I applied
to work at CatCo,
to get closer to Lena Luthor,
but then she sold the company
to Andrea,
and now, I could use your help.
But someone has to protect
the world from the Luthors.
Not the Luthors, Lex.
I know Lena. She's in just
as much danger
as everyone else.
The guest of honor and I
have already accomplished
so much in the past.
And I'm looking forward
to seeing what we will
achieve in the future.
She was leaning towards
the Kryptonian.
-You're welcome.
-You're too good to me.
We were partners
when we took over
the last world...
Ladies and gentlemen,
allow me to introduce...
...why shouldn't we be partners
in this one, too?
...my brother,
my partner,
Lex Luthor,
the Man of Tomorrow.
Oh, how can I help you,
Agent Dox?
My friends
will work against you.
You know it. I know it.
But they're shortsighted.
The true threat. The...
The only threat that matters
is Leviathan.
I'd like to help you
defeat them.
Well...
that's good to hear.
But no information
about Leviathan exists
in this new world...
at this time.
I need knowledge
from the future.
I have reason to believe
a particular doppelganger
came through the wormhole.
He's already been arrested,
but if we play our cards right,
we can bring the future to us.