Come with me if you wanna live.
-Ta-da!
- Oh...
- You okay?
Your candy tray awaits,
milady.
Okay, guys.
I appreciate the breakup feast,
but I'm fine.
And deny us a night
of guilt-free chocolate?
I don't think so.
Really. I think it's good
Brainy and I broke up.
Right.
I'm being honest.
Look...
Brainy clearly has some...
emotional complexities
that I wasn't aware of.
And whether that's because
of the personality inhibitors
or not,
it's better to know now.
Well, I will be honest.
I am a bit worried
about Brainy.
Yeah. I mean,
it must be so strange
to have your whole self
just shift like that.
So, how's it been at the DEO?
Can't believe Lex owns it
in this universe.
Employees get stock options
and four weeks paid vacation.
But no beach vacation
can mask evil.
Just wish we knew
what he was up to.
Ooh, you're welcome
for the breakout,
by the way.
You know, I figured
I would save my thanks
until after I heard
your proposition.
Hmm, that's a bold stance
from a guy who
got himself arrested, what,
16 hours after coming here
from another Earth?
So, I'll give you
the benefit of the doubt.
Aw, that's very kind of you.
And since you know
so much about me,
why don't you tell me
who the hell you are?
The name's Lex Luthor.
That's a weird name.
No weirder than Toyman.
That was your father's name,
wasn't it?
You need to think bigger.
Like your dad.
He was gonna be
the biggest toymaker
of all time.
Just moved
into virtual reality, but,
mmm, his partner
stole his patent, right?
Right, and then he snapped.
People say he went
on a rampage.
I say that they had it coming.
And then,
he killed himself.
Wouldn't you like to show them
how wrong they were?
That's what I was doing.
What you were doing
was getting caught.
But with my resources,
you could make the Schott name
synonymous with genius
and chaos instead of failure
and... who?
I have something for you.
The National City
Toy Convention.
And, as a bonus,
I believe an old friend
of yours,
Chester Dunholtz,
will be there.
Well, it has been a pleasure
doing business with you,
Winslow.
Oh, and one more thing,
whatever you do,
make it splashy.
If we're gonna build you
a legacy, it's gonna need to
survive well into the future.
Lena.
Just the Luthor
I was hoping to find.
Did you look for me
in my office?
Where I said I would be,
working on Non Nocere,
waiting for you.
Ooh, right, sorry.
Something came up.
This new universe has shifted
the frequency of Q-waves.
I'm back at square one.
I needed your help.
I understand,
but we have bigger problems,
like Leviathan.
You undersold them, sweet Lena.
He's right.
Leviathan is the greatest
threat of our time.
-Brainy.
-Agent Dox is assisting me
with a project.
You know he's friends
with Supergirl, right?
There's no need
for concern.
Since I removed
my personality inhibitors,
I run on logic only.
And my calculations tell me
that, at this time, Lex Luthor
is on the right side
of history.
Can you promise me
no one will get hurt?
I promise no one
will be harmed.
Especially
if you help us.
As with the Q-waves,
the recent fusing
of the universes
might have shifted
what Andrea Rojas knows
about Leviathan.
If there was some way of
-finding out--
-You want me to talk to Andrea?
It won't do any good.
She's not gonna
tell me anything.
We're not friends.
The Lena I know wouldn't let
a little thing like friendship
get in the way
of saving the world.
And as a thank you,
I can guarantee you
a source of Q-waves
by the end of tomorrow.
Well,
if you will excuse me,
I have to get my beauty sleep.
They're unveiling
my new action figure
at National City Toycon
tomorrow.
I anticipate many photo ops.
There are so many.
I expected to be
a collector's item.
-Kara Danvers?
-There he is.
How did I get so lucky
that CatCo would send
their Pulitzer winner
to cover the unveiling
of my little trinket?
We are the lucky ones,
Mr. Luthor.
And who is this
new cub reporter?
-William Dey.
-Mmm.
I covered your Kasnian victory
for The Times of London.
I remember that piece.
You called me fat.
I believe it was bloated ego,
and in reference
to your victory parade.
Oh, yes!
That was a good parade.
Oh, shame Supergirl
couldn't make it.
-Ah...
-I bet your editor would
have loved a twofer.
Say, she's a friend of yours,
isn't she,
Ms. Danvers? I mean,
how would Supergirl feel
about these action figures?
-Two heroes saving the world.
You know what?
I'm more interested
in how you feel, sir.
Uh, in a word,
valiant.
Mr. Luthor,
is it true you plan to develop
Shelley Island
as an energy source?
This planet is in
an energy crisis.
I'm just trying to do my part.
Is that why you attempted
to take over
Rogers Engineering?
You wanted to get
into biomechanics,
but Russell Rogers
refused to sell,
and he disappeared.
You don't know what happened
to him, do you?
No.
And this has been a delight.
I have a very busy day.
Why don't you take
one of these, on the house?
-Uh, Ms. Danvers,
a quick word, please?
-Yes, I'll be right back.
This was supposed
to be a puff piece.
Why did I just get
Frost/Nixoned by a Boy Scout?
Since I have been
on this Earth, I have done
nothing but protect and serve.
Judging me for the crimes
of another Earth's Lex, well,
that's not fair now, is it?
I'm gonna find out
what you're doing at the DEO.
So much moxie!
Let me make myself clear.
If young Woodward decides
to proceed with his Lexpose,
it will prove very,
very dangerous for his health,
off the record.
-Have a nice day.
Kara Danvers is Supergirl.
-Give me that.
Supergirl, there's an armed
sniper at the toy convention.
-I'm already there.
-Great, we're almost there.
I'll look for him.
We need this place evacuated
and locked down.
We do not wanna cause a panic.
Does this feel like...
Like Toyman.
They're bombs.
He's got a gun!
Up there! Up there!
-Wait, that looks just like--
-Winn! But how?
Oh, no!
What?
Winn?
What are you doing here?
Saving Chester Dunholtz
and my future.
Have you seen Toyman?
-Uh...
-The shooter! The guy
wearing my face!
-I've got him.
Oh, come on, come on!
Damn it. Brainy,
I need you to lock on
to every traffic camera
in National City,
and please,
please find this guy.
Winn, stop.
Okay, just breathe
for a minute, okay?
We're gonna find the other you,
-and then we'll stop him
before he hurts someone.
-We always do.
-Yeah.
-I came back to this moment
to catch him.
You should have.
Brainy.
He's right.
I should've caught him.
By now he could've
hurt someone,
and if he hurts someone,
I don't think you understand.
My life is over.
Everything!
I will lose everything.
My wife, my daughter.
Wait.
You have a wife?
And a kid?
Oh, my God, yes.
Yes. Uh...
That's my wife, Aila.
Mary is gonna be two in April.
They're beautiful. I...
- Oh.
-It's so good to see you.
-I mean, I might've missed you,
like, just like a little bit.
-Yeah, me too.
-But just...
-Yeah, well, I missed you,
like, a lot.
-It was really hard
leaving you guys.
So, what happened?
Well, I'd just finished
putting Mary to bed.
And then somebody's knocking
on the front door,
and I'm thinking,
please don't wake the baby up,
and then Aila is arguing,
suddenly, with whoever it is,
defending me.
So I run down there
to see what's happening,
and...
it's the time cops.
Accusing me of killing
Chester Dunholtz on this date,
at this time.
But you didn't do it.
I told them that.
But they had my DNA
to prove it, so I'm thinking,
"Okay, this must be
some type of,
you know, doppelganger person
with my father's sick,
twisted brain.
And now, if this Toyman
kills someone, I will never
see my family again.
They'll put me in jail,
or worse, it's gonna affect
the timeline.
And I will have never met Aila.
Or my daughter.
Okay, all right.
We'll just... Okay.
Well, there must be something,
right? I mean...
okay, this person.
This person was found
lurking near Dunholtz,
so maybe they were
working together.
You know? I mean,
we've got a face.
Can we get an ID, Brainy?
Yeah, I'll, um,
I'll go to the DEO
and start cleaning up
the image to ID it,
tracking it.
I'll, uh, also put Winn's ship
in the DEO hangar
for safekeeping.
No, no, no, I do not want
the Legion ship
anywhere near Lex.
You know what?
I've got an idea. I'll just
have to call an old friend.
Lex as in Lex Luthor, the hero?
Why would you not want
the Legion ship near him?
Uh, Lex is not a hero.
We're just gonna have J'onn
just bring you up to speed
on exactly what happened.
Thank you
for seeing me today.
I wanted to apologize to you
for how I treated you
after you took
my mother's medallion.
After all these years?
Why now?
Andrea, I know about Leviathan.
Oh.
Lena...
I wanted to explain everything
to you for so long.
I know how dangerous
Leviathan is and how terrified
you must've been.
And I understand now
that you never wanted
to betray me.
No, it's been so hard.
I knew I had to protect you.
I'm so relieved
that you know the truth.
So am I.
And anything Leviathan
has asked you to do,
we will figure it out together.
They've never asked me
to do anything.
All these years,
and not a word?
They said
they would call on me,
but they never came.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, it's you and me again,
okay?
You jump, I jump.
If Leviathan calls you,
you come to me, okay?
I can't lose you again.
Okay.
Andrea knows nothing.
Seems on this Earth,
post-Crisis, Leviathan
hasn't activated her yet.
But don't worry, if they do,
I'll be the first person
she calls.
J'onn?
We're here.
Oh, this is nice!
Very Sam Spade.
-Never realized J'onn was
such an avid reader.
-Where is he?
I'm up here.
Is that a secret elevator?
Don't push.
What is this place?
In a minute. First...
I am so sorry.
But we will find this other you
and stop him.
Yeah. You always give
the best hugs, papa bear.
Okay, J'onn. Just...
-You gotta tell us
about this place.
-Yeah!
Well, in the wake of Crisis,
Kara, Kal-El, Barry, Kate,
we established a headquarters
from which to fight crime.
Oh, in the future
they call it a Hall of Justice.
I like that.
I thought since Luthor Corp
now owns the DEO,
National City could use
its own collective.
A headquarters
to keep this city safe.
-To work outside of corporate
and government oversight.
- Huh.
Whose interests might not
always side with justice.
-So, like S.T.A.R. Labs?
-Or the Arrow bunker.
Place for my super friends
to work, whenever
they should need it.
What are you gonna call this?
I was thinking The Tower.
-Cool!
-Absolutely.
So, tell me what I missed
with this whole Crisis thing.
Not tell you.
-Show you.
-Ah.
But I must warn you.
The truth of the old Earth
could be quite upsetting.
Uh, not more upsetting
than what I'm already
dealing with, so
how bad can it be?
-Okay, get it out.
Get it all out. It's okay.
Whoa! Uh, so, wait,
Lena killed Lex?
And then he came back to life?
And James runs a small town
newspaper and mentors children?
That's adorable!
And you!
-You were, what,
you were Russian?
-Yes.
Kasnian.
But that wasn't really me.
And so evil Lex
now owns the DEO?
Yeah.
Oh, but let me tell you
about the doppelgangers
who came through a wormhole--
Not a bad picture of you.
I don't understand.
In every simulation I ran,
we always apprehended Toyman.
-He never got away.
-What I don't understand
is why you're here
and the Legion ship is not.
Director Danvers thought
it would be safer to
secure the ship
at a government black site
three miles south
of the National City border.
Thank you.
And once I get there,
how do I access
what the ship knows
about Leviathan?
There is a panel
on the right quadrant.
You have Winn Schott's DNA
from his hair.
That's all you'll need.
Now, our mission is over.
Call off Toyman.
Does he look like
my personal attack dog?
He's underground.
Toyboy is smarter
than we gave him credit for.
-Toyman will strike again.
-Then get out there
with your little do-good crew
and take care of it.
Hello, National City!
Well, by now
you might've heard that my splashy show at Toycon
caused, well,
a little bit of ruckus.
J'onn, can you track
his location?
He's blocked his IP address
and signal.
Whatever technology he's using,
it's something
that I've never seen before.
And I have got
a bigger bang in mind.
Now, tell me.
Have you ever been
so unfairly wronged
that it just made you wanna
burn it all down?
Well, I have.
And I'm angry.
Someone hurt my family
and they destroyed
my father's good name.
-Look at that.
People are supporting him.
-He's collecting followers.
- So,
I have the target,
I have the method,
and what I need now...
is you.
Give me the will.
Like me, subscribe, share,
follow me, and once I reach
one million followers,
you will see
a fireworks display
like never before.
So, let's play to win!
Huh?
Until next time.
I am hashtag
Toyman.
Uh, guys?
If he wins, I'm dead.
I can't believe
all these people
are rooting for violence.
Well, the anonymity
of the internet
brings out everyone's
basest instincts.
Sure,
but how would those people feel
if they were the target?
Unfortunately,
this is a distinctly
21st century problem.
By, what, 2126,
anti-trolling legislations
are in place around the world.
-Stopped World War Three.
-Huh?
I should not
have told you that. Whoa.
I'll go sweep the city.
See what I can find
in the real world.
If you need me, just call.
J'onn, that's genius!
Director Danvers,
I got your call.
Yes, this place is genius.
Brainy, I'm glad
that you're here.
Look, the Toyman is using
some sort of IP address blocker
from his world,
-and we just can't--
-I know. I've been trying
to track him from the DEO.
Have you had any luck
identifying Toyman's accomplice
from that image?
The image was too obscure
to get a clear ID.
Well, we might have something
on board the Legion ship that
can help enhance the image--
-I said I'd do it.
And I will.
Andrea needs me.
I have to go to CatCo.
I'll call you if anything pops.
-Kara.
-Huh?
I think there's a connection
between Lex and Toyman.
Actually, yeah. Um,
-I need to talk to you
about that--
-When the DEO put Toycon
on lockdown,
Lex had just slipped up.
Okay, I believe that Lex
is not who he says he is.
But...
that means we have to be smart,
because
if he's dangerous,
we can't just go around
making baseless accusations--
Kara, we're reporters.
We dig into hunches,
no matter the risk.
Kara.
When I call you in
for a meeting, I expect you
to come directly to me.
-Mmm-hmm.
-William, I need you
with me today.
My father's alma mater
is honoring the family
for our advancement
in tech and entertainment.
I'm going to announce
the next phase of
Obsidian VR at the event.
Obsidian Platinum will be
like nothing anyone
has ever seen before.
William, I want you
to cover it.
-I'd rather not--
-That's a great idea.
-Thank you, Kara.
-It's a good idea.
And I have something special
for you too.
Okay.
You were friends
with Winn Schott
when he worked for CatCo,
before disappearing
two years ago, right?
Uh, yes.
Mmm, bet you never thought
he'd reappear with
such an evil splash.
I'd like an exclusive.
Immediately.
No!
Um,
I'm sorry. No!
That is not
the Winn Schott I know,
and I will not give a platform
to a madman.
Toyman already has a platform.
His video went viral
across five continents
in under an hour.
We have to capitalize
on that kind of traffic.
We don't have
to promote bloodshed for
the sake of your bottom line.
Actually, according
to your paycheck,
yes, you do.
William, be ready in an hour.
Kara,
get me that exclusive.
You should see me now, Father.
Ha! On our Earth,
they called you a psychopath,
but here,
they cheer for me.
And yes, it may be too late
for you, Father, but soon
I will accomplish
what you could not.
What you always dreamed of.
I will live forever.
Wait, this is
the superhero-level stuff
I have been waiting for.
Wait, Nia, Nia,
wait, come here.
Sorry.
Winn, this is Nia.
-Hello.
-Whoa, Nia.
As in Nia Nal?
Yeah?
Wow, wow.
This is incredible. Holy...
-Hi.
-I'm sorry, your great,
great, great, great, great...
bunch of greats granddaughter,
Nura Nal, is, like,
one of my best friends
and, like, the most
kick-ass Legionnaire.
-That's crazy.
Tell me everything.
Does she look like me?
Okay, wait.
Let's save story time until
after we catch the bad guy.
Right. Well, anything to help.
Okay.
Once he's hit
a million followers,
he's promised to strike.
So, you'll have to work fast.
She can do it.
Um, right. So,
are there any markers,
any specifics I can keep
an eye out for?
All we know
is that he wants attention.
Attention. Okay.
Not you. Get out
of my head, jerk.
- It's okay.
-It's okay.
-I'm sorry.
What did you see?
-Nothing.
- Literally nothing?
That seems unlikely.
Fine.
I saw a tiger.
Wildcat.
Um, let me.
Hi.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
It's just...
my mind's been
a little messy lately.
It's okay.
Do you mind telling me
exactly what you did see?
It's just that Nura taught me
how to interpret dreams.
I'm kinda like her Watson.
I saw my ex-boyfriend
turn into a tiger
and attack me.
Wildcat was my nickname
for Brainy.
-Oh, I know.
I just thought
I was better
than letting him get
in my head.
You know,
I can't tell you a whole lot
about the future,
but I can tell you
that you,
Nia,
are a powerful woman.
You see this?
So, I'm the only human
Legionnaire,
so when I got my Legion ring,
they had to soup it up
with, like, some cool powers.
-Is that dream energy?
-Yeah.
So, Nura and I,
we fashioned the ring's
abilities after her and
your powers.
Never let anyone
make you question
your own worth.
Okay.
And that is patented Nura Nal
advice. She would kill me
if I didn't give her credit.
Thanks, Winn.
-You're right.
-I know.
I'm gonna try again.
You must be such a great dad.
I try.
-Oh.
It's, like, the hardest thing
that I have ever done.
-I bet.
-I'm not kidding.
Yes, it's like, I became a dad,
and suddenly my heart
was just...
on the outside of my body.
You know?
She's also my greatest
accomplishment, my little Mary.
She's my legacy.
Did you name her
after your mom?
Well, it was either that
or Winifred.
Kara was an option.
-What?
-Yeah, Aila pushed for it.
But if I'm being honest, um,
in the future,
Kara isn't exactly
what you would call
an original name choice.
What are you talking about?
Parents naming their children
-after the legendary
Kara Zor-El.
-Oh, my gosh.
-No, I like Mary.
Yeah, me too.
Besides, I'm not too hot
on my own
legend right now.
Lex threatened to kill
one of my co-workers
if I don't stop him
from investigating Lex.
So, either I go against
my journalistic ethics or...
or I put William in danger.
Don't know how
to tell you this,
but you put me in danger,
like, every day.
-No, no, don't say that.
- No, you did.
No, listen, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter though.
Because I knew that
you were always gonna be there
to protect me.
You're Supergirl.
Being in your orbit, it's...
inspiring.
Oh, oh,
oh, why didn't I think
of this before?
Toyman!
He said that he is doing
everything for his father.
But his father didn't exist
on this Earth.
But mine did.
And so, if I was gonna go
be inspired by my father,
where would I work?
We're too late.
If Toyman was here,
he's gone now.
Guys.
I think I found something.
Andrea and her father?
My dad had a board
just like this for Dunholtz.
So, on Toyman's Earth,
the Rojases must've had
something to do with the fall
of Winslow Schott, Sr.
We have to get to CatCo.
We have to warn Andrea.
She's not at CatCo.
She's at...
National City University
with William.
Home of the Tigers.
Wow! Aren't you handsome?
We're connected now,
aren't we?
Precisely.
I'm now directly linked
to your consciousness.
Then you know what I want.
Give it to me.
Hold.
Enhance.
I know you.
How do I know you?
Search for this woman.
Oh.
Of course.
At Obsidian,
we staked our reputation
on pushing technology
to the limits.
Imagine a world
where, after you've come back
from work,
you slip on your Obsidian
Platinum contact lenses,
and suddenly
you're on a Tuscan villa,
surrounded by
your beautiful vineyard.
You set a large family table
out on your verandah
where you let the wine
from your own label flow.
Later, you can bottle the wine
from your vineyard and sell it
for real money.
With Obsidian Platinum,
you will never again
have to choose between
your life and your dream.
-You can always have both.
Smile!
Kitty number two!
Will, where are you?
I got him!
My powers can do that?
Go after Toyman.
I've got this.
Here, kitty, kitty cat.
Are you trying to tame
a robot tiger?
If the chair fits.
Stop!
Says who?
Whoa, where did you come from?
Yet another Earth?
Actually, no,
this is my Earth.
-This is my life, and you are
really messing it...
-Whoa!
Give me the trigger.
Uh, well, that would be no fun.
Is the bomb in the van?
-Hmm.
-Listen to me,
I know what it feels like
to wanna protect your family.
Believe me, I do.
But you have also got to
create your own legacy.
This is my legacy.
You've seen the people.
They adore me.
Dude, this isn't love.
No, you're just a cheap thrill
for them, all right?
Give me, give me the trigger.
Can't. It's a dead man's switch
for a dead man, like me.
Just stop that.
You could still change.
All right? You are not Toyman.
You say that name Toyman
with such disdain, but you,
you do not understand.
Toyman is eternal.
Have you seen William?
He was supposed to be here.
I ran diagnostics.
We lost no civilian lives
to any of Toyman's attacks.
Well, that's good news.
Speaking of news,
I wonder what the news
is like in the future.
Hey!
It's all over.
Have you looked at
the wanted poster?
It's gone.
I know.
Will, where are you?
You're not gonna believe
what I saw.
You were supposed to
be at the university,
and you weren't.
I know how important
this story is to you,
and that you won't let anything
stand in the way of
you getting it, even me,
but I also know
that Lex would sooner
take someone out
than let a headline be run
that threatens his reputation.
-And I'm not--
-Which is why
I have been thinking,
we should investigate
Lex together.
There's safety
in numbers and...
and if we share information,
we have a better chance
at exposing him,
once and for all.
You mean we'd be like...
-partners?
-Exactly!
Yes, who would have
each other's back.
Well then,
partner,
I think you need to see this.
My sister showed me
this hangar before, it's
-high government security.
How did--
-Lex get in?
-He paid off the guards.
- He's got a plan.
- And we need
to find out what it is.
Well, he didn't see you,
did he?
-Of course not.
-Good.
I was careful.
So, do you wanna take a look
at the rest of my notes?
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.
I totally forgot
what time it is.
I have to go.
-Big date?
-The biggest! It's game night.
You should come.
Uh, nah.
-You know, I'm not very good
at games.
-That doesn't matter, it's--
-Besides, I have dinner
waiting for me, so--
-No!
-Mmm-mmm?
-Uh-uh.
Under no circumstances
will I let you stay here
and eat that...
-Well, that's the saddest
sandwich I've ever seen.
Come on.
-No! That stays.
-Okay.
Is there not a game night
that you should be attending?
Oh, there is.
But I don't really stand
much of a chance without
my Trivial Pursuitpartner.
Sadly, I cannot partake.
J'onn has asked me to upgrade
the diagnostic system.
No, he didn't.
Brainy.
What is going on? Hmm?
Dude, I saw the way
that you looked at Nia,
when the tigers attacked.
That fear of losing someone
that you love. I've had
that same look on my face
since I got to this time.
So, tell me the truth.
I...
have lied...
to everyone...
because I'd...
I've had to work
with Lex Luthor.
I helped Lex
bring you back
for the sake of the future.
-That was you? You--
-Winn--
-No, no, you risked my life.
-I...
-Brainy, my family!
-I had to, I...
It was imperative
that Lex get information
from the memory cube
on your ship.
I did the calculations.
I knew no one would die.
That we would catch Toyman,
the...
The one thing I didn't account
for was Lex himself.
He's, he's...
chaos incarnate.
He's completely unpredictable,
and I...
I don't know
if I can control him.
Winn, I...
I'm so sorry.
Another Brainiac told me
that it was absolutely critical
that I help Lex
in complete secrecy.
But I hate it.
I hurt Nia.
And all I want is to be
close with her again, but...
I have to be cold.
And...
I'm terrified
that I'm becoming the bad guy.
You must hate me.
You're right.
I should hate you.
But...
everything worked out, so...
I guess I don't.
In fact...
In a way, you kinda helped me.
Growing up,
I was constantly burdened
by my father's crimes.
You know, son of a madman.
Pretty sure everybody
judged me for it.
Everything I've done in my life
has been in defiance of that.
Joining the super friends,
running out to the future
with Legionnaires to
fight your cousin and stop him.
But all that kinda...
pales in comparison to
saving my own future.
Plus, I got to see
some old friends.
You still consider me a...
an old friend?
Yes,
Brainy. I do.
Oh, shoot.
I'm running late. Uh, you sure
you don't wanna come?
I have work to do.
Pick it up.
Press the button.
Now, think of what you want.
Q-waves.
As promised.
They do exist on this Earth.
All we had to do was
bring them to this time.
Happy birthday, Christmas,
and New Year, little sis.
-Thank you for going to Andrea
today.
What are partners for?
If only Mother could see
how nicely we're playing
together now.
Let's not ruin the streak.
- Ohh!
I don't know how
she's doing it,
but she's cheating.
- Check her sleeves.
I saw something.
-Wait.
Aw, there's our girl.
She's feeling better.
But, like, for real this time.
A lot better than you
at Jenga.
-Okay, well, wait,
'cause it's my turn now.
Ready, set...
- She's terrible.
- Go!
She's terrible.
Ohh...
-Dude!
The point is for the tower
not to fall, am I wrong?
Marty, is this how you play
in Metropolis?
- No!
-Love your glasses, by the way.
Thank you! These,
they're prescription.
Yes.
And those are the rules, but,
uh, we play that if it falls,
we take a shot,
so I'm just gonna...
Wait, wait, wait.
A toast, a toast.
To new friends.
- Aw.
- Welcome.
And to old friends.
May they always find their way
back to us.
-Aw!
- Cheers!
That's the last
of Toyman's evidence.
Let's lock it up
for the night.
Let's play to win!