Previously onSupergirl...
This Earth-Bender
has been spotted
at the scene of the crime
throughout history.
Pompeii, even as far back
as Noah's flood.
He literally manipulates
the Earth.
You won't survive me again,
Kryptonian.
No! No, Russ!
Please, somebody help!
I beg your forgiveness
by submitting myself
to the bond.
With his dying breath,
he told me
that you were Supergirl.
You reassured me, ad nauseam,
you would never lie to me.
And all the while,
there wasn't a single honest
moment in our friendship.
Please, don't leave
the fortress
with Myriad.
Please don't let my mistake
push you to do
something terrible.
Intruder!
- I'm not a villain.
You shouldn't have
treated me like one.
Kara.
It's the Fortress's defenses.
Someone's turned them
against Supergirl.
We couldn't reach you on comms.
What happened?
Are you all right?
I traced Rama Khan's
energy trail here.
-I have to find Lena.
-What did Rama Khan do?
It wasn't him.
It was Lena. She knew.
She knew what?
My identity.
She's known for months.
Lex told her,
and she hates me for it.
Lena's in Mount Norquay.
Mount Norquay is one
of Lex's old hideouts.
-Where are you going?
-To fix this.
Get Myriad online
and operational.
Non Nocere launches
within the hour.
And, Hope, excellent work
preparing the move.
Our Q-wave generator
is ready to integrate
with Myriad.
Supergirl?
Don't worry.
The bunker's lead-lined.
She can't find us.
These are Lex's
countermeasures.
What do we do?
Ms. Luthor?
Deploy.
That should keep her at bay.
- What's happening now?
It appears to be re-arming
the cannons with Kryptonite.
-Cancel it.
-It's on an automatic override.
-Shut it down.
-It's not responding.
Shut it down now!
Lena, don't do this.
We must stay true
to our mission.
We don't kill people...
no matter how much
they've hurt us.
I'm not gonna give up on you.
What happened?
How did Supergirl and Luther
beat you again?
It doesn't matter how.
I just need to explain to her.
I wouldn't do that.
They're whispering about you.
That you've lost your edge.
Earthquakes
with no death counts,
floods with the ferocity
of a leaky faucet.
They're saying that the Elder
may put Tezumak in charge.
Tezumak?
His tactic of war
is without limits.
He could accidentally
burn down the earth.
I agree.
I have been in charge
for two million years.
And you've been losing lately,
and he'll hold that
against you.
Tezumak is a snake.
Oh, and let me guess.
Next is your advice
about how your way
is so much more efficient.
Tezumak isn't the only
manipulator around here.
Look, what I said
yesterday was unfair.
Yes, I believe
my technology would work.
But I agree.
Your way is more efficient.
This isn't about ego,
Rama Khan.
It's about saving the earth.
The world is
at a tipping point.
There's no turning back.
The humans
will destroy this planet
unless we destroy them first.
But how?
The Kryptonian won't stop.
She will die
to protect these humans.
Then let Supergirl die trying.
The planets are coming
into alignment
for the first time
in nearly 2,000 years.
But only for tonight.
The last time this happened,
I wiped out Pompeii.
A masterpiece worth repeating.
If a little on the blunt side.
Not even Supergirl
can stop a massive volcano.
The Staff of the Shadow World
is worthless
without the Medallion.
You need the Medallion's power,
not the Medallion itself.
And you know
where that power is.
Acrata.
Supergirl.
Hey, did you find Lena?
What was she doing
in Lex's bunker?
Brainy, can you get some line
of communication to a bunker
three miles below
the Norquay mountain range?
Yes, but depending
on the processing power--
Okay, stop.
Just tell me right now,
when did Lex tell Lena
your identity?
And why was she attacking you
in the Fortress?
-What the hell is going on?
-It was after Shelley Island.
-But Lex died there.
-No, he didn't.
He portaled somehow
to a safe house
where Lena shot him.
She killed him to protect me,
to protect all of us.
But before he died,
he told her.
She's been lying to us
for months.
Okay, so why attack you now?
So she could steal Myriad
from the Fortress.
Lena stole Myriad?
It's how I tracked her
to Norquay,
but I don't think
this is what it looks like.
She saved me from Rama Khan
in the Fortress.
And even at Lex's bunker,
the cannons were loaded
with Kryptonite,
but she didn't use them.
I can still fix this.
I can get through to her,
if I could just talk to her.
Brainy, can you
get me in there?
We could harness the Kryptonian
cache crystals we have here
to covertly project
a hologram beam
into her bunker.
-Great.
-Okay, if not for mind control
over the population,
then why would
Lena need Myriad?
-I think I might know.
Malefic.
Engage Psychic Inhibitors.
-Alex, please.
-Agent Dox,
apprehend the suspect.
Alex, please!
Malefic and I mind-melded.
I know his true intentions.
He is here to help.
He has some information...
about Lena.
I was her prisoner.
Okay, first, how did you escape
the Phantom Zone?
I didn't escape.
I was never there.
When the Phantom Zone Projector
hit me at the planetarium,
I went directly
to Ms. Luthor's lab.
Lena was the one
who helped Brainy
fix the Phantom Zone Projector.
She must have changed
the end coordinates.
But what did she need you for?
Mind control.
She was experimenting
with my ability to incept.
If Lena can harness
Malefic's Q-waves
and merge them with the power
of Myriad's distribution,
the results
would be unprecedented.
World-wide total control
in an instant.
But we don't know
her intentions.
She's trying to make
people less violent.
You use Myriad to impose
your will on the world
population, not save it.
She's hurting.
All she's experienced
are people hurting each other,
the same way I did.
-Clearly, she thinks
she's doing good.
- It's true.
I had long planned
to destroy my brother,
but Ms. Luthor said
it went against her morality
and stopped me.
Alex, she's not hurting anyone.
Not even Malefic, her prisoner.
I can still save her.
-You don't know that.
-Yes, I do.
I'm the one who hurt her,
so I'm going to fix this.
Brainy, get the
hologram online.
-Acrata.
-I have a job for you.
-And I have one for you.
You can tell them to stop
sending agents like you
with jobs for me.
After everything
Leviathan has done to me,
taken from me...
you can tell them that I quit.
-What are you?
-What am I?
I am Rama Khan,
guardian of this Earth,
the one who endowed you
with your powers.
I understand the pain of loss.
Obey me and I will
offer you a way out.
Tell me what you want.
One last job,
then you will be released.
And my father?
Your father
can keep his riches.
For what little they're worth.
Hologram online
and ready to commence.
Good luck.
-It's almost ready, Ms. Luthor.
-We are so close, Hope.
I'll finish
consolidating the data.
We can save them.
All of them.
Lena.
Supergirl.
-Please, just hear me out.
-Save your breath.
You showed me
who you really are,
and I believe you.
You have every right
to say that,
but don't do this.
Do what?
Whatever it is you're planning
on doing with Myriad
and Malefic's Q-waves.
Did it ever occur to you
that I was gonna do something
good for the world?
With Myriad,
people won't understand.
Of course,
you assumed the worst.
I'm not the bad guy.
I know. You spent years
trying to be open and trusting,
even when everyone expected you
to be like your family.
Even when everyone in your life
let you down.
Even when I was weak
and lied to you,
knowing that all you
ever asked for was the truth,
you were always better.
Lex took advantage
of my weakness
and he used it
to manipulate you.
He wanted my mistakes
to change you.
He wanted you to become him.
But you are nothing like him.
Nothing.
Don't let my mistakes turn you
into something you're not.
I am good.
And I always was.
Lex didn't change me
and you didn't
change me either.
You just exposed me
to the ugliness of humanity.
You did me a favor, Kara.
I learned what kind of
deceitful person
you really are,
and that's what
inspired me to do this.
-Lena--
-Your words mean
nothing to me anymore.
Spare us both the drama.
Leave me alone.
Wait.
Hey.
You okay?
No.
I couldn't get through to her.
Sorry.
You know, a part of me
always knew that this
couldn't be that easy.
And I get it.
I fully understand
why she feels betrayed.
It's so hard for her
to trust people.
But I made her trust me.
Over and over again,
I made her believe
that I was the best friend
who would never ever hurt her.
And then she finds out
in the most horrible way
that our entire friendship
was based on lies.
Look, you were damned
either way, Kara.
Your choice to
conceal your identity,
it wasn't born out of a place
of maliciousness.
It was born out of love
and compassion.
And you were just trying
to protect your family.
And you were
trying to protect Lena
from people who could use
that information to hurt us.
And look, I love Lena, too.
I am deeply upset
by what is going on.
But this...
This isn't just two friends
that are in a fight.
This is someone
who has turned a corner.
No, but this is not her.
This is not our Lena.
Well, who is our Lena?
I mean...
She knew that Lex
was out of prison,
and she said nothing.
She kept Sam Arias locked
in a subbasement at L-Corp,
knowing that she was Reign,
and she said nothing.
She knows
how to make Kryptonite,
and she kept that
hidden from us.
Lena is leading her
own double-life.
You are making her sound
like a Luthor.
Maybe that's because
she is one.
We can't put our faith
in some distant hope
that she's gonna
do the right thing...
...when every single action
that she has taken up until now
points to the contrary.
Okay, we have
to stop her, Kara.
The safety of the world
depends on that.
She is not Lex.
I will not treat her
like a villain.
I know you won't.
That's why I have to.
What are you talking about?
When you went to speak to her,
we used the hologram
to piggyback a virus
into the bunker's mainframe.
Alex, you used me?
In a few moments,
Lena's defenses will be down
and Myriad will be stalled.
By then, if we have to take
more drastic actions,
Claymore 3 is positioned
above Mount Norquay.
-What? Oh.
-And I will give her time
to surrender.
Kara, we have to
start thinking with our heads,
not with our hearts.
It's ready, Ms. Luthor.
Supergirl caused you
a great deal of pain.
I can see it in your eyes.
After my family
and after Andrea,
I knew better than to trust
in friendship anymore.
All of the anguish that
you're going through,
it doesn't seem worth it.
It inspired Non Nocere.
It inspired you.
Who needs friends
when you can save the world?
Myriad is ready to launch.
Ms. Luthor,
this is your moment.
Shall I activate?
-Three, two...
-One.
-What's happening?
-It won't lock
onto the satellite.
Something's interfering with
the dishes' ability to move.
It's a virus. It's working
through our mainframe.
-Ms. Luthor, the hologram.
-It was a Trojan horse.
Of course.
How could I be so naive
to think that Supergirl
wanted to talk?
If the virus spreads, the DEO
will be able to deactivate
our security defenses
in 20 minutes.
We need a workaround
before then.
We could manually
unlock the arrays.
No, Lex has booby-trapped
this entire place.
There'll be a lethal failsafe
if I try to tamper
with the dishes.
Then I'll go.
No, you can't.
You're too great an asset.
Ms. Luthor, one of my
prime directives,
as you programmed,
was to ensure the
success of Non Nocere.
If that means self-sacrifice--
No. Even if you could
manually reset it,
there's no telling the extent
of the virus's damage.
All right, we may need you.
It'd be short-sighted
to lose you now.
If we could
replicate the virus,
we could reverse-engineer it
and override the
shutoff remotely, okay?
I'll need some help.
Very well.
Accessing files.
J'onn, you don't
need to stay here.
I deserve to be locked up.
We both shoulder the blame
for the transgressions
of our past, Malefic,
but together,
we will move beyond them.
-J'onn, J'onn.
-What's up?
Alex, she thinks Lena
is past the point of no return.
She's got Claymore 3
pointed directly at the bunker.
But you can talk to her, right?
Show her that she's wrong?
You know people can change.
Look at you and Malefic.
I can still save Lena.
I just need more time.
I was in Alex's position
back on Mars
when I banished Malefic
to the Phantom Zone.
I did so because I thought
I was protecting my people.
But I banished him
because I was afraid,
because there was no other way.
Right, and look
at the two of you now.
The only reason Malefic and I
were able to
come through the other side
is because
we can see each other's pain.
You've already talked to Lena.
I'm not saying Alex is right,
but what other option
does she have?
No. There has got
to be another way to stop Lena
that isn't blowing her up
in a bunker.
Malefic.
Malefic, you said Lena was
analyzing your Q-waves, right?
Yes.
She isolated a frequency
which allowed her
to replicate my ability.
Maybe you're the key.
If we could harness
your Q-waves--
We could use them
to counteract Lena's.
But she's launching
a worldwide attack.
The amount of energy
Malefic would need
to counteract hers...
It could kill him.
It's worth the risk.
No, I am not trading
one life for another.
Please.
If I can stop Ms. Luthor
from making the same
mistakes that I did,
then all of the turmoil
and pain that I've caused
will be worth something.
Let me help.
Let me make amends.
Who's the target?
You're looking at it.
A supervolcano?
No. You can't be serious.
You'd be killing all of them.
Extinction level events
have been happening
since the beginning of time.
I should know.
I was here to make them happen.
What have these people
done to deserve this?
Existence is their sin.
Don't think of this as the end.
Think of this as giving
the world a second chance.
For years I've worked for you,
telling myself
there was a just cause.
No more.
Maybe I can't beat you...
but you don't think
Supergirl will?
Supergirl is not a god. I am!
-What's going on?
-There's been
a perimeter breach.
-Do we have a location?
-Negative.
Help! Rama Khan is coming.
He's gonna destroy the--
You fool.
I'm saving this planet.
Now I will remake the earth,
as I should have done
a long time ago.
It's a pity you won't be here
to see it.
But Leviathan thanks you
for your service.
Brainy, I need a status update.
Eleven minutes until the
bunker's defenses are down.
-Alex, about the bunker--
-And Rama Khan?
I've analyzed security footage
of the appearance of the Shadow
and of the object
she was carrying.
It's called "The Staff
of the Shadow World."
It is an artifact associated
with ancient Mesopotamians,
but can also be found
in Herculaneum.
I juxtaposed our image
with historical images
of Rama Khan and voila.
The two were last seen
in the ancient city-state
of Pompeii.
-That's concerning.
-Indeed.
Especially as it seems
the energy given off
by the Staff
can be found in one other place
in National City.
The building where we assumed
Leviathan was hiding.
That's across the street
from the Tar Pits.
Also the site of
a dormant supervolcano.
The last eruption
was in the early Cenozoic Era,
and was 10,000 times
more powerful than Pompeii.
Rama Khan's an Earth-Bender.
So he's trying to recreate
Pompeii in National City.
Pompeii times 10,000.
Okay. We need to divide
and conquer.
Supergirl, J'onn, I want you
to get to the Tar Pits,
find Rama Khan and stop him.
You said the Sonic Cannon
defeated him the last time,
so go to the Fortress
and get that.
-Brainy, I need an update on--
-Alex, wait.
I have to tell you something.
You don't have to use Claymore.
We think we can use
Malefic's Q-waves
to counteract Lena's,
stop her using Myriad.
Theoretically, he is correct.
Okay, you want me
to use a known threat
to stop an imminent one?
Handing over a global
Q-wave projector
to a terrorist?
What if Malefic just decides
to change his mind
once we free him?
-He's changed.
-But you don't know
that for sure.
And between Lena and Rama Khan
gearing up for Pompeii 2.0,
the last thing that I need
is a third catastrophe.
We are running out of time.
You need to go.
Alex, please. I know you think
what you're doing is right,
but she is our friend.
If you use Claymore, there's no
turning back from that.
I'll get the Cannon.
I'll meet you at the Tar Pits.
She doesn't understand
how hard this is for me.
I mean, Lena is my friend, too,
and now all of a sudden,
I'm supposed to decide
whether I should risk
everybody's lives
just to save hers?
And Malefic,
he invaded my mind.
He threatened Kelly,
and now I'm just
supposed to trust him?
You know what's on the line.
You're the one who taught me
how to do this job,
and you're the one
who's had to make
really tough decisions
so that people don't die.
You have every reason
to fear my brother.
I can't promise you
that Malefic
has changed for good.
People make mistakes
and they do terrible things.
We have to let them do better,
bring them back into the light.
Otherwise...
what's the point
in trying to save everyone?
The DEO
has sent another warning.
In nine minutes,
our defenses will be disabled.
-Do you want me to--
-Delete it.
What was that?
That felt like
a residual aftershock.
Yes. A 5.4-magnitude earthquake
right in the heart
of National City.
It's knocked the entire
satellite array offline.
There's no way I can
reverse-engineer anything now.
I can still try
a manual override.
I can reposition
the dishes myself.
We discussed this.
Absolutely not.
You could be killed. Both
Hope and Eve gone, forever.
But it would be worth it
for both of us
because I believe in you.
Eve did, too.
I have seen
the depravity of humans.
the betrayal and the pain.
Let me help,
so that we can stop them
from committing any more
of these horrible acts
once and for all.
No. I will not allow it.
We will find another way.
Your partnership has meant
the world to me, Hope.
You're the only friend
I can count on.
But, Ms. Luthor,
I'm not your friend.
I'm something you created
to serve a purpose.
You're right.
This is the only way.
Anything on your psychic scan?
Nothing.
Could Brainy have been wrong?
Apparently not.
He's using something more
than earth-bending powers.
You're right.
I see the Shadow and the Staff
in an underground chamber.
-It looks like she's stuck.
-I've got her.
Has Lena responded
to any of our warnings?
None so far. She appears
to be deleting them.
Her auto defenses will be
disabled in five minutes.
If Claymore is launched,
what are our odds?
98% chance Myriad
will be neutralized
and a .01% chance
Lena will surrender,
which makes it
a virtual certainty
Lena will not survive.
-And if we use Malefic?
-Our odds shift slightly.
86% chance we will stop Myriad
and a 0% chance
Lena will be harmed.
Lock Claymore in position,
and prep Malefic.
But, Brainy, you let him know
that if he so much as smiles,
I will have a dozen agents
and their guns
pointed directly at his heart.
It's useless.
The Staff holds me
and it needs me.
Together you're fueling
what he's doing.
I'm not gonna
let that happen.
-I'm here, Ms. Luthor.
-Okay, careful.
Now, at the base of the
nearest dish, there should
be an access panel.
It's locked, and the keypad's
rigged to blow.
Damn it, Lex.
We only have three minutes.
Well, it's a group of
satellite dishes
aimed at the sky.
Lex loved symbolism.
Perhaps the code has
something to do with Heaven.
-Or Hell.
-John Milton.
What was Lex's favorite quote
from Paradise Lost?
"Arise or be forever fallen."
It worked.
Manually positioning
the dishes.
Elevation, 14.9.
Azimuth, 253.1.
Ms. Luthor, we are locked
and ready to launch Myriad.
Amazing, Hope. You've done it.
And now, so will I.
Myriad has launched!
Of course it has.
We have 30 seconds until
the first Q-waves reach Earth.
Launch the interception.
Malefic's intercept is working.
Wait.
No, no, no.
No, it's not working.
Malefic's Q-wave energy output
is just shy of the power
we need to stop Myriad.
Is there any way
to up the power?
We can turn off
our Psychic Inhibitors.
-Don't even joke about that.
-I'm not joking.
The Inhibitors absorb
6% of Malefic's energy output,
or 4,000 terawatts.
If we want to increase
his power by the necessary 6%,
we have to remove
the Inhibitors from
the equation. It's basic math.
I will not expose
my agents to that risk.
That assumes there is a risk.
J'onn said
his brother has changed.
Two minutes
until the volcano explodes,
and ten seconds
until Myriad reaches Earth.
Do we turn off our Inhibitors
or do we activate Claymore?
Seven seconds, Director.
Five. Alex!
All agents,
Inhibitors off, now.
What's happening?
See, that's the problem
with you superheroes.
You align yourselves
with the weak.
You fight for these humans,
but time after time,
all they do is destroy
everything around them.
You're one to talk.
Oh, I admit, I destroy.
But with a cleansing fire.
That's the only way to deal
with the scourge of humanity.
I have been here
for millions of years.
It's how it's always been...
and how it always will be.
Supergirl?
Can you hear me?
Mal stopped Myriad.
Where are you with Rama Khan?
Don't you see?
People never change.
No, Rama Khan. You're wrong.
People can change.
That is what is so beautiful
about this world.
You did it.
-You stopped the volcano.
-You knocked his block off.
-No!
They stopped Myriad.
I don't understand.
There's nothing to understand.
I lost.
This is a life lesson to learn.
Sometimes
the good guys don't win.
Enough.
It's over, Rama Khan.
What are you
talking about, Gamemnae?
The planets are still aligned.
There's still time!
Not for you.
Not anymore.
I can still finish this.
You've had your last go.
Your reign is over.
She'll have
something to say about this.
Who do you think appointed me?
This is not over!
I'm sorry I failed.
I wish there was more
I could do for you, Ms. Luthor.
There is.
I see.
Lena Luthor? Hands in the air.
It wasn't her. It was me.
I did all of it.
Drop the gun.
You're surrounded.
Eve, please.
Take her away.
Ms. Luthor, you all right?
You okay?
I'm gonna be scraping mud
out of my cape for a week.
No, I mean, are you okay?
I don't know.
Me neither.
When the FBI went
to arrest Lena,
Eve Tessmacher was there.
She confessed
to the whole thing.
Had proof that
she impersonated Lena.
Had proof for all of it.
I wish that were true.
Well, we recovered Myriad,
but you know Lena.
-She's not gonna stop.
-I know.
She's alive, thanks to you.
Well, and to you.
I mean, you were right
about saving Lena, and Malefic.
He changed.
Well, thank you
for trusting him, and me.
You had a lot more faith
about that than I did.
Well, if we can
save Malefic's soul...
Maybe we can save Lena's.
But that is for another day.
Kelly and I are gonna
get some sushi.
You wanna join?
No, no, you go ahead.
Okay.
I'm Andrea, by the way.
Oh, I know. I'm Russell Rogers.
See you tonight?
Yes.
It's over.
I finally did the right thing.
I'm just sorry
that it's too late.
I wish I could have saved you.
You saved us, Mal.
But how can I ever make up
for what I've done?
If only things were different.
There is a way.
And there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
Her name is M'gann.
She's a friend of mine.
And she's a White Martian
resistance fighter.
She can help you
when you arrive.
Can't believe
the war still rages.
-The war that I helped fuel.
-But you can go home now.
You can help
extinguish those flames.
But what if I can't?
I'm not strong like you, J'onn.
-H'ronmeer never
had a role for me--
-This is your role.
You know the White Martians,
you understand them,
you know how they think.
You can appeal to them.
Malefic, you can
bring peace to Mars
for the first time
in hundreds of years.
We can start anew.
You were never meant
to be the pariah, Malefic.
You were meant
to be the promise.
Thank you, my brother.
I will strive
to make you proud.
And to end what I helped start.
Not without this you won't.
Not a scratch on it.
I'll do my best.
Well done, J'onn J'onzz.
-You passed the test.
-Test?
You released my brother
from the Phantom Zone?
You brought my brother here?
When I saw you fight
in Elseworlds,
I could see that
you were a great warrior,
but one plagued by his past,
and that made you vulnerable.
You believed it was
because you had left Mars,
but it was something
far, far greater, J'onn.
Your brother.
But now that you have
faced those demons,
you have come to learn
your vulnerabilities
are your strengths.
And now you are ready.
Ready for what?
A crisis.
Checkmate. Again.
Finally, you've returned.
I don't know
if anybody's told you this,
but the feng shui of this place
is a bit stale.
I brought you back
because the universe
will need a mind like yours.
Someone who can
checkmate anyone?
The time has come
for you to fulfill
your destiny, Lex Luthor.
You can now become the hero
that you have longed to be.
I've always been the hero.
Happy to help.
But first,
we have to discuss my sister.
For so many years,
I've travelled across worlds,
across the multi-verse,
to do one thing.
To kill you.
And now, we're here.
You saved my life.
Submit
and begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is within you.