Previously on
Supergirl...
People use our VR
to cope with trauma
they experience.
Your failsafe failed.
I assure you,
this glitch will be fixed.
You just rest easy, Mr. Bates.
I've got you now.
They found Dad.
He's dead.
I still can't believe it.
Of all the places for Jeremiah
to hide out,
the Peruvian Andes.
Yeah. It's where he found you.
Clearly, that place
meant a lot to him.
He was doing humanitarian work?
In a refugee camp.
Helping displaced aliens.
After everything
that Jeremiah endured,
it's hard to believe
he died of a cardiac arrest.
It's surreal.
Hey, how are you,
uh, how're you doing?
I'm sad.
It's painful to know
he's really gone.
But you know what?
I'm also relieved to know
he was a good man that...
That brought me some peace.
That's one thing
I never doubted...
is that Jeremiah
loved his daughters.
That's what Eliza
said to me this morning.
Kara.
I'm so sorry.
Thanks, Kelly.
I'm so glad Alex has you.
So where is she?
Are you guys ready?
I'm not going.
Uh...
And you can spare me
the big accusing eyes, Kara,
I'm not changing my mind.
Excuse me.
Um... Alex,
I don't understand.
You were with me last night
when we made the arrangements.
I never said
that I was participating.
I... I know you're in pain.
-I'm not in pain.
-Of course you are.
Okay, stop telling me
how I feel.
Okay, then you tell me
how you feel.
Tell me why you're refusing
to go to your father's funeral.
Because I don't feel the need
to bury a man
who has been
dead to me for years.
Jeremiah
was changing his ways.
He was helping people,
making amends.
Well, not to me.
He had to live in secrecy
for his safety.
Right.
After leaving Cadmus,
did you think
he was just gonna be able to
call us whenever he felt like?
I am the one
who held out hope for him.
I am the one that said
that he was good,
and that Cadmus was forcing him
to kill people.
And he helped you escape.
And then he disappeared. Again.
Just like that!
Alex, he's still your father.
You should be at his burial.
Look, the man that I loved
hasn't been a father
to me in years.
And... and, yes.
Yes, we were so close
that we could just...
we could finish
each other's sentences.
But his obsession
with keeping you safe
changed all of it.
Nothing else mattered to him,
the least of all me.
That is not true.
Come on, Kara.
He treated you like
you were some golden girl,
and of course
you have love for him,
and I totally respect that.
But he treated me like
I wasn't even worth his time.
Okay.
So, what do you
want me to tell Eliza?
-I don't care.
-You don't care.
You don't care what I tell
our grieving mother?
I have spent my entire life
protecting this whole family,
and I will not do it again.
She is all yours, Kelly.
I'm not dealing with this.
People
grieve differently,
and Alex is reeling.
Okay, you guys go to Midvale,
I'll talk to her.
-There's still time.
-Call me if you need any help.
Okay, thank you.
-It's a bit early for that.
-Don't.
Look, I get it.
You know I have had
a lot of loss.
I know how you feel.
You have no idea...
how I feel.
I have mourned
the loss of my father
multiple times.
You have no idea
this stabbing pain here.
I'm losing him over and over
and over again.
And I really...
I really can't tolerate
being psychoanalyzed
by my girlfriend right now.
-I'm sorry.
-So rather than your apology,
what I want
is to be left alone.
Okay.
I will give you space.
But just know
that I love you
and I'm here
for you unconditionally.
-And when you're ready,
just call.
You got it.
But now
we want you to know
you're in good hands.
Hope, help
and compassion for all.
- Call us--
Let's go punch things.
Hey, Kelly.
Will.
I heard about Kara
and Alex's dad.
I'm sorry for all of you.
Thanks.
Hey, shouldn't you guys be
getting on the road
for the funeral about now?
Yeah, we should.
But things are complicated
with her and her dad.
So she says she doesn't
wanna go to Midvale today.
-That's rough.
-Yeah, but there's still time.
So I am giving her space
and hoping
she changes her mind.
Which leaves me here
with nothing to do but worry.
Well, if you are looking
to pass the time,
-I could use a favor.
-Yeah.
In the past three weeks,
Lex Luthor has rushed
32 satellites
through approval by the FAA
and launched them into space.
Each of their orbits
placed them directly
above a city
that Lex himself is visiting
on this Obsidian world tour.
So you're wondering
what the satellites have to do
-with the Obsidian
Platinum's launch.
-Mmm.
Nothing, as far as I'm aware.
Platinum operates off
of booster towers.
So, whatever Lex's business
is with the satellites,
it has nothing to do
with us.
But you're still
skeptical of him?
Yeah, I worry about what
Lex is doing with our platform.
And Alex is skeptical, too.
So I'm keeping an eye
out for anything
that might prove that
Lex isn't the hero
that everyone thinks.
Still, you don't think
he's doing anything wrong here?
Not that I can tell.
Since Luthor Corp came aboard
the only glitch
involved a failsafe.
And that was a fluke.
A lone hacker, Richard Bates,
exploited it for his own ends.
You don't think there's
any chance this Richard
was working with Lex?
What would Alex say?
That with Lex,
anything is possible.
Man, this guy's really great.
Hey, Supergirl,
I haven't seen you
in VR before.
Treasure Hunter Tilly.
I'm a participant like you.
Oh. Oh, cool.
Most of these people are bots.
The simulation maps your brain,
so it'll populate your world
with things that feel
familiar to you.
People you know,
places you've been.
Well, they do look
very, very real.
All you gotta do
is check the neck.
If you see three stripes,
that means they're
a non-player character.
The ones without stripes,
we're the realies.
Right. Well, thank you, Tilly.
Call me Bonnie.
Alex.
My sister Jill is Supergirl's
biggest fan in real life.
Oh, that's great.
So are you blowing off
steam playing hero,
or working something out?
You know, I'm just taking
a break from the real world.
Yeah,
the real world sucks.
Yeah.
Jill was just diagnosed
with stage four cancer
and I can't even afford
the flight to go see her.
I'm so sorry. That's terrible.
It is.
But in here,
it's all good, right?
Even if it's just
for a few hours.
So, who's this rock starman?
His real name
is Derek something
and he's in here all the time.
Word is his wife passed away.
If you ask me, he stays in VR
way longer than is healthy.
And that's my ride.
See you around, Supergirl.
That was metal!
Thanks, Supergirl.
Sure.
It's amazing how real
all this feels.
All this...
Virtual reality.
What's she
talking about?
One, two, three, four!
Okay. Dragon at the fountain.
What would Kara do?
Heat vision.
Okay.
Kara makes this look so easy.
All right.
Okay.
Supergirl, how does it feel
to defeat a Dracokardosian?
Uh, I'm just glad
that I could help.
So what are you
going to do now?
Well, does anyone know
where a girl can get a bite
to eat around here?
That settles it.
Uh, there's nothing
that connects Lex
to the failsafe hack
or to the guy that did it.
But if that guy was able to
hack that part of your system,
who's to say
Lex won't target it, too?
What is it?
Did Lex do something?
No, not something he did,
something we should
have done and didn't.
The failsafe error I found,
it wasn't patched after all.
You mean the back door's
still open?
Yeah.
But that means that
there's a chance other people
could still be in there.
I need to find Andrea.
Kelly, what's going on?
The failsafe glitch
Richard Bates exploited,
it hasn't been fixed.
-What?
-Yeah,
I thought maybe it was
a slip-up with the records,
but I checked.
The order for the patch
was put in,
but the work funds
haven't been released.
Look...
we have to do something
about this right now.
Kelly, I understand
your concern,
but what happened last week
was because of the hacker,
not a flaw in our system.
And since then,
there have been no reports
of anyone being affected,
have there?
No.
This withholding
of funds is just
corporate bureaucracy
with the board.
I'll handle it.
But there's nothing
to alarm our users about.
You don't think our users
deserve a warning
that the lenses
might be problematic?
All that would do is make them
worry about the platform,
and then they wouldn't be able
to use the platform
to get over their worries.
And when it comes to veterans
and sufferers of mental trauma,
do we really wanna stop giving
them what they need?
I would never let our consumers
engage in anything that
would put them in jeopardy.
Still, I'll call into Gemma
and get the funds released
and that glitch fixed.
Okay. Thanks.
Thank you.
-Well, if it isn't Supergirl.
-Hmm.
Hi.
These blueberry pancakes
are absolutely insane.
I mean, they're just like
from when I was back home.
It's, like,
crispy on the outside
and a little bit gooey
on the inside.
Oh, my God.
Kelly could come here
and eat these without dying.
Don't tell me, is Kelly
one of your Super Friends?
Uh, no.
No, no, no.
She's my girlfriend.
My very smart, and kind,
and wonderfully
supportive girlfriend
who I was a complete
jerk to this morning.
-We all have our bad days.
-Hmm.
This is a little bit
more than that.
I just found out
that my father passed away.
He kind of treated me
like I was an equal.
Especially when it came
to taking care of my mother.
And definitely when it came
to taking care of my sister.
And, uh, I don't know,
I thought it was really cool
that he would give me
that kind of responsibility,
but I look back at it now,
and I'm... I just...
Like it is totally unfair
that he put all of that on me.
I mean, my sister,
she can be a handful.
So I thought
if I came in here, um,
I could just feel some
freedom for myself.
I could fly around
and I could knock things down
without anybody being
able to stop me.
And then I would...
I would feel better.
But I don't.
I mean, not really.
'Cause, I mean,
my dad's still dead.
My girlfriend, she's right.
I have a lot of things
to work through.
Anyway, that was... wow.
Um...
I, uh...
I think it's about time that
I go back to the real world.
What do you mean?
Uh, just that
this has been a lot of fun,
but I think it's time
to get back to reality.
"Reality"?
Are you okay, hon?
How about another round
for my favorite customers?
Works for me.
Have you heard any more
about your sister?
-My sister?
-Jill.
Okay, how long
have you been in here, Bonnie?
I'm Tilly.
Treasure Hunter Tilly.
Supergirl.
J'onn?
We need you
at the DEO right now.
You're in the DEO?
Supergirl, don't worry
about your friend.
She's working through things.
Like you.
I'll see she gets
to where she needs to go.
Keep 'em coming, Mac.
Hey, um...
Good luck with everything.
You, too.
Oh, it's just
like the real DEO.
Maybe even better
than the real DEO.
-Supergirl.
-Director J'onzz.
We've just had word that
a short-range ballistic missile
was stolen from
Thompson Marine Base
by unknown terrorists.
Paired with the right tech,
an SRBM like that
has the capacity
to wipe out everything
within a 20-mile radius.
Can we track it?
We're sweeping
the city for its signature now.
This is the part where you say
you'll circle the city
and track these guys down.
Right, yes.
Uh, sorry, I was just...
You have no idea how good
it feels to be here with you.
Supergirl,
-this is Hank Henshaw.
-There's only one thing alive
on less than four legs
that can hear this frequency.
And that's you.
Are you okay?
-It's Henshaw.
- What?
He's speaking to me in some
sort of high-pitched frequency.
My God. It is Henshaw.
As I'm sure you've discovered
by now,
I've stolen a missile
from a nearby base.
What you haven't discovered
is that while the DEO
is focused on my larceny,
-I kidnapped your sister.
-Kara?
Sprock! It is true. Look.
How?
The only way he could know
Kara is your sister
is if he found out
your secret identity.
There's
a nuclear warhead
at the Tamaki Air Force Base
south of the city.
Get it and deliver it
to the abandoned warehouse
on Waterfront Road
within the hour.
Do it, or I'll reveal your
secret identity
-and kill your sister.
Alex, I know your history
with Henshaw.
Promise me you won't let
feelings cloud your judgment
as we bring him to justice.
I can handle it.
Where's Kara?
She's safe.
For now.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Your father...
infiltrated my organization,
ambushed me.
Left me for dead
in the jungle.
So this is what I want!
You didn't think I'd come
unprepared, did you?
You didn't think I'd bring
an active warhead, did you?
I still have the missile.
And I still have you.
That's enough to get the DEO
back to its former glory.
By blowing it up
and starting over.
And now the DEO, your sister...
and everyone you love will die.
No one will be able
to save them... or you.
I don't need anyone to save me.
Because I am Supergirl!
Supergirl.
-J'onn.
I've got Henshaw,
but I don't know where...
We have Kara.
She's safe.
You should not
have come back.
And now you'll never
hurt my family again.
-Hey.
So...
Andrea said the failsafe patch
wasn't addressed
because of bureaucracy
with the board.
But...
Ever since Luthor Corp
partnered with us...
...the board
has a new member...
Lex.
So maybe he was behind it.
He could have pressured
other board members
to ignore the glitch
so he could exploit it
for his own ends.
Maybe trap people inside the VR
and lock in subscribers.
Yeah, but we don't have
any facts to back that up.
Well, there has to be
something we can do.
This is a list
of almost 500 users
who have been using our VR
non-stop for 48 hours or more.
No one's called
about them, but...
-They could still be trapped.
-Yeah.
How do you feel about
helping me
make a few hundred
phone calls?
Hey.
Good job today.
-Henshaw's in containment.
-Good.
-How's Kara?
- Back at CatCo,
finishing her article
as we speak.
Oh, and she, uh,
wanted me to remind you,
it's your turn to pick up
the dumplings tonight.
-That's my sister.
I know that look.
Is something on your mind?
Yeah, I just, um...
I don't know, everything just
feels so... so good.
Hmm.
But I keep having this feeling
that I've forgotten something.
Kind of like the
"Did I lock the front door?"
-kind of feeling.
-Hmm.
But still, I...
I know that I'm doing
what I'm supposed to be doing.
I've got my team,
I've got my family...
Everything, it feels...
Right?
Alex, you saved your family,
the DEO, and the citizens
of National City today.
That feeling you can't
quite pin down...
it's called happiness.
Now, come on,
let's go celebrate.
Brainy's buying.
-You're right.
-Let's celebrate.
-Yeah.
♪ Feelings
♪ Nothing more than feelings
♪ Trying to forget my...
Thank you,
President Lincoln.
Hey, I'm sorry
about that abomination.
If he'd read a history book,
he'd know
that Honest Abe belongs
in the audience of the theater,
not on the stage.
Do we have a John Wilkes Booth
in the house?
- Come on.
-Boo!
What? You don't think
that's funny? Hmm?
Now, back to our show.
Who's next?
Ah, I see a sister Kryptonian.
To Supergirl!
Oh, silence.
Sorry, Vita,
I got carried away for a sec.
Well, you're spared,
but you're sent
to the back of the line.
And no more Britney Spears
songs if you want to live.
-I'll go get the drinks.
-Okay.
You happy?
Never happier.
Yes, I understand.
Very sorry to bother you.
Yes.
Wow, so that's 100
phone calls to 100 users,
none who are trapped.
Maybe I've taken us both
down a conspiracy rabbit hole.
-There any word from Alex yet?
-Uh, I texted,
and, um, no response.
Maybe she still
needs space.
You know,
sometimes people
need a shoulder to cry on
even if they won't admit it.
You should go to her.
I'll keep on this.
Saw you looking at it,
I'll keep on it.
In fact, I have a contact
at the NSA
who might be able to help us
speed things up.
You go be with
the woman you love.
Thank you.
Well, well, well, if it isn't
my favorite customer.
Want a drink
on the house, Supergirl?
Why not?
Well, if it isn't
my favorite customer.
Want a round
on the house, Supergirl?
Heck, yeah.
Hey.
Supergirl.
Hi. That's a...
That's a really great costume.
Black.
Now that is cool.
Um... Sorry, what are you
talking about?
Oh, I love this place.
They just never make the drinks
cold enough, though.
That... How did you...
I've come here
to escape reality.
Not have subpar drinks.
This... This isn't real?
What, you think all these
drinks would be on the house?
Are you okay?
This is impossible.
You look like
you are bugging out.
I'll just get someone.
Supergirl. Are you all right?
How can there be
two Supergirls?
Perhaps it's the result
from Kryptonite poisoning.
Should we head to the DEO?
Perhaps we should go
back to the medbay.
No, this isn't real.
I have to get out of here.
I have to go.
That was weird.
Alex. Are you okay?
-Alex?
-J'onn?
Psi just launched
a psychic attack
on National City.
She's making everybody
doubt their reality.
Don't tell me
she got to you, too.
-We need you here.
-No, I'm all right.
And I'm on my way.
Hello?
Alex?
What's wrong with your lenses?
You wanna come out? Hey.
Okay, babe.
It's time to wake up.
Don't worry.
I'm coming in
to get you.
Well, I guess some villains
are all thought and no action.
-Alex.
-Kelly.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I just... I didn't know
if you had tried to get out,
but your failsafe
isn't working.
What?
The glitch that
Richard Bates hacked,
it wasn't fixed.
Um, and I think you might
have been affected.
I can't eject you, so I need
you to wake yourself up
and end your simulation,
and then I'll tell
you everything.
End... end my simulation? I...
You need to exit
your virtual reality.
I can't do it for you.
You have to do it for yourself.
Oh, my God.
Psi must have
gotten to her, too.
What? No.
I'll make sure
she gets to the medbay.
I don't need to go
to the medbay.
You have to end this.
This isn't real. You know that.
A-ha! She was
assaulted by Psi.
That never happened.
Hey, Alex,
can't you see
that this virtual reality
is just giving you
what you want?
Supergirl.
There's a theft in progress
at National City Bank.
NCPD is on their way,
but they won't make it in time.
Kelly, I have to handle this.
You go with J'onn and Brainy
to the medbay.
They'll take care of you,
I promise.
Let's go.
End simulation.
Okay, slow down, Kelly.
Are you sure that this is
a failsafe malfunction?
I don't know.
That is why I called you.
Alex's lenses
are practically red.
And she's not responding to
any of my methods of ejection.
I tried adrenaline,
but it was like
she didn't even feel it.
What about going into the VR
for direct contact?
Yeah,
I tried that, too,
and there was no sign
of a failsafe button.
She wouldn't even listen to me.
Before she went in,
she was grieving.
I don't know, maybe because
of her emotional state,
she was more
susceptible to our AI
and had a mild psychotic break.
I've seen this
with some of my patients,
but still...
I'm still able
to bring them out.
Okay, Kelly, look.
We need to think this through.
It was like
she was lost in there.
Then we need a way
to shock her out.
We need to show Alex that
she is not in the real world
by confronting her with
something that's unexplainable,
but also absolutely undeniable.
Something like Alex herself.
I hope this works.
Thanks, Supergirl.
These guys sure chose
the wrong bank to rob.
Speaking of bad choices,
there's still time enough
for you
to turn your life around,
young lady.
Hi, Alex.
How do you know my real name?
Because I'm you.
You can feel it.
How?
I've been sent to show you
something that you need to see.
Please.
Please listen to her.
-What do I need to see?
-That none of this is real.
Yes, it is. Of course it is.
Supergirl, is everything okay?
Come with me, and I'll show you
the truth you've been avoiding.
Come on, Supergirl,
the NCPD can take it from here.
Supergirl, let us help you.
Or are you afraid
of facing reality?
I remember this place.
That...
That bomb,
I planted that bomb.
This is the Cadmus facility
where I last saw Dad.
-Is that--
-Jeremiah.
We didn't face him before,
but we need to now.
Maybe now he can explain
why he never came back.
- Hey!
Supergirl, get away from her!
She's a shape-shifter.
-No.
-Come on. I know another way.
Okay.
There he is.
Dad?
This is what
you needed to see.
The truth in the real world.
The real world?
The real world
where we're not Supergirl.
And where even if we were,
nothing that we could have done
would have saved him.
We always hoped
that he'd come back to us.
And if he didn't,
we hoped that
someday we'd find him.
That's why you took on
the role of Supergirl.
She stands for hope.
But now that Dad's dead,
we know that there's no chance
of that ever happening.
And even if we were Supergirl
and we did find him,
it wouldn't change anything.
His life was a result
of his choices.
Not ours.
But it's gonna be okay.
Because in the real world,
we still have people
who love us
and who wanna help us
make the changes we can.
Unlike here, where everyone
is trying to lock us in.
Don't listen to her, Supergirl.
You're leaving us no choice.
Hey.
Alex.
Get away from her, please.
She's dangerous.
Don't let her put
crazy thoughts in your head.
-She's not--
-This is your home.
We are your family.
You belong with us,
not with her.
That thing needs
to be destroyed.
If you can't... we will.
Not in my reality.
Hey.
End simulation.
Wait, no, no, no.
Hang on. Hang on.
How do I know
if I'm not in the VR still?
Because we had
a fight this morning
that was never resolved.
Because your dad
is gone for good,
and you're sad.
But it's gonna be okay.
I know.
Yeah, I know that now.
I love you.
Thank you
for not giving up on me.
I would never.
I'm so sorry.
I was such a jerk.
And I pushed...
J'onn and Kara and you away.
You know, I've been so angry
at my dad for so long,
for abandoning
Kara and I,
for never reaching out,
you know?
But as hurt as I've been,
I just... I kept thinking
that he would come back
into our lives someday.
And then, you know,
I get the news
about his death, and I just...
I just got so mad at everyone.
But the reality...
is that I was just
mad at myself.
'Cause I couldn't save him.
And so I...
I felt...
I felt hopeless.
You are not hopeless.
You are a warrior.
What's wrong?
I think there's a lot
more going on
in the VR than we know about.
Because I don't think
I was the only one
that was lost in there.
There... There was a woman
named, uh, Bonnie,
and there was a guy, Derek.
And... and I think
they were stuck in there, too.
And if there was
three of us...
then there could be
a lot more.
Um...
Okay, I... I... I'm on it.
Um, but first, we need
to get you to Midvale.
Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, we do.
Lex Luthor
arrived in Madrid today
to a sellout crowd
to discuss Obsidian North's
new Platinum...
Cocky bastard.
Pre-orders are so high,
the phone lines have
currently shut down.
-People are hailing
Lex Luthor
as the innovator
of the millennium.
Nice work, Arnie.
Promininant tech giants
are leaping onto the VR scene,
each driving forward new
and upcoming product lines.
However, nothing will
come close to Platinum VR.
If you think you kind of
understand what's going on
in tech today...
Thank you, Kelly.
I'm glad that Alex was okay.
Yes. Bye.
You've reached
Gemma Cooper's office.
Miss Cooper is not available
right now. But if you
leave your name--
I need a full
diagnostic write-up
on the failsafe error code.
And I want a patch
worked up immediately.
Nothing else moves forward
until this is done.
-Do you understand?
- Yes, Miss Rojas.
Lex Luthor.
What are you up to?
Jeremiah was a loving
and caring man.
It's what made him
a great partner,
a great friend
and... a great father.
He was brave
and compassionate.
He knew just what to say
to make your life brighter,
how to pick you up
when you were feeling down.
In spite of all
the twists and turns
that Jeremiah's life took,
the kindness,
compassion and love...
that was real.
I'm sorry for all the things
that I said.
It doesn't matter.
You're here now.