Previously onSupergirl...
I helped Lex bring you back
for the sake of the future.
Another Brainiac told me
that it was absolutely critical
that I help Lex
in complete secrecy.
Yes, it may be too late
for you, Father,
but soon I will accomplish
what you could not.
I will live forever.
Forty-two!
What? They don't have these
in the 30th century.
I can get Al
to make you up a bunch
and you can take 'em with you
if you like.
Or you can just keep eating
until the kitchen runs out.
Then you'd be able to stay
for one more song.
Once the Legion ship has power,
I gotta go.
Speaking of which,
you never told us
what your Legion call sign is.
-I didn't?
-No.
It's not a big deal.
Are you kidding?
Uh, according to Brainy,
before every Legion member
puts on his vestments,
he must have a call sign.
"Computer Lad."
-Huh.
-What?
-You know, it's a hop,
skip, and a jump
from Cat Grant's IT guy.
-Wow.
-Why is "Computer Lad"
your name?
It's not "Martian Manhunter"
or whatever, sure,
but Legionnaires' names speak
to who they are, right?
So, Chemical King has power
for chemicals,
Lightning Lass controls
electricity.
One day,
my brother-in-law decides
to call me "Computer Lad,"
and it kind of stuck.
And, I don't know,
I kind of like it.
- Okay.
-It's nice.
-Kara.
- Yeah.
You invited William.
It... It's nothing.
After game night,
I couldn't not.
Karaoke's all night,
so come on up, guys.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Kara, you didn't tell me
it was karaoke night.
Is karaoke your thing?
Clearly, you've never heard
my rendition of "Africa"
by Toto.
Oh! Kara has been threatening
to do that one for a long time.
-I haven't.
-So, we're gonna
do it together?
♪ He turned to me
as if to say ♪
♪ Hurry, boy
It's waiting there for you ♪
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you ♪
♪ There's nothing
that a hundred men or more ♪
♪ Could ever do
♪ I bless the rains
down in Africa ♪
♪ I bless the rains...
Yeah, Kara!
♪ The things we never had
♪ Ooh, ooh...
Oh, yes. The piano.
Yes!
♪ The wild dogs...
Act it out.
♪ Cry out in the night
♪ As they grow restless Longing for some solitary... ♪
I heard about Lex sneaking
past the government security
to probe the Legion ship.
He must be driving you crazy.
I mean, not even Winn
could find anything unturned
on the ship.
I know that
he is up to something.
Which is why
I uploaded some spyware
onto my DEO intranet.
That way, whatever he does,
I will see.
Alex, I'm proud of you
for staying to fight
the good fight,
but I do worry.
Well, you don't have to
because I can handle myself.
And, plus,
Brainy's got my back.
Mr. Luthor.
I uploaded you the file
on Gemma Cooper.
Excellent. Now you're free
to help with
the Alex Danvers problem.
Problem?
She's been spying on me.
She hasn't interfered
with our work,
but if she does,
it might require
more permanent actions.
Help her control herself.
Now, is everything
quiet there?
Of course.
No disruptions
or technical difficulties?
No.
Good.
Keep me posted.
I'm on my way.
911 at the DEO.
-I'll track it.
-Oh. I... I'll join you.
I thought you were leaving.
You guys bailed me out.
No, I'm not leaving
this century
without repaying you.
What don't you do well?
Are you kidding me?
With those harmonies?
Where did that come from?
With a partner like you,
it's easy.
Would you, uh...
Would you like to
go out sometime?
Just us.
Like a date?
A date.
What do you think?
Hey, Super--
-Kara.
-Mmm-hmm.
She is super.
-Sure.
-Um,
Alex needs you at...
your grandmother's house.
You know, your D... ear...
Old Gran Gran's house,
like, immediately.
Is everything all right?
Yeah. She's just been feeling
under the weather.
I should really go.
-Yeah.
-I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
How is that coming
through our comms?
I used to listen to this song
in the shop when I was a kid...
with my dad.
Okay, wait, so you're saying...
I think Toyman's back.
What do you mean,
not a bug from Toyman?
What else could it be?
Initially, I thought
the drone outburst
was just some bad code
in our surveillance software,
but this,
this is in our whole system.
So, it's a virus?
More like
artificial intelligence.
Whoa, that's why
he was playing the song.
This is my dad.
The last thing that
he was working on was
a version of this.
A way to put his whole mind
into the digital space.
He... He wanted to
become hyper conscious.
If he could become immortal
in the World Wide Web,
he would be the ultimate player
in the ultimate playground.
Once there, he could commit
any act of violence.
Any time, any place,
air traffic, hospitals,
US Nuclear Command.
But you said your dad
was still working on it, so--
And, plus,
this Toyman isn't him,
okay, so how could he
be doing what your father
was trying to do?
Lenses. This Toyman has
the Obsidian Platinum lenses.
Storage vault.
Bring up item 906016.
I noted something
on this video of our
final meeting with Toyman.
There.
See, Toyman uses
the Obsidian lenses
to download himself
onto a laptop.
Didn't we confiscate a laptop
and bring it back here?
The hardware's clean
but there's
a compartmentalized drive.
That would make it appear
to be off while still working.
Toyman found a way
to leap into our Internet
and bypass the DEO's firewall
to the outside.
-Okay, so do we have
a fix for this?
Yeah. My dad's code.
I think I can
reverse-engineer it
into a kill code.
- Lockdown.
Lockdown.
-Lockdown.
Don't you guys know it's rude
to talk about someone
behind their back?
Toyman?
Okay, tell me
this is a video, guys.
Oh, no, I am everything
I used to be,
but electronic and immortal.
Now, lower the DEO's firewall
to the World Wide Web
or I will use
all of your toys to kill you.
He's taking control
of our laser defenses.
Did you kill it?
No. I just knocked him
out of the command center.
So he can come back?
Oh, he can, and will.
Okay.
I want us to round up
every item this thing
can use against us,
guns, comm links,
anything with a Bluetooth
that can connect
to our intranet,
and I want it evacuated.
As long as
there's technology here
this AI can access,
we are sitting ducks.
Go.
I'll gather gear too.
Once we've got everything,
I can fly it outside
of Toyman's signal range.
Okay.
Brainy, can you isolate the AI?
I pushed him down
from the command center
to the server level
under a virtual lid.
-But he's still fighting
to get back up here.
Look.
Well, what if he breaks
through the lid?
There is a 92.6% chance
he'll make his way
onto the World Wide Web.
When he's there,
he can attack... everything.
Okay, well, what if Supergirl
goes down to the server level
and fries everything?
The servers are located
on top of the DEO's power core.
If they melt,
so does the core.
It would vaporize all life
within a three-mile radius.
Do you hear that?
Is that
an old-fashioned telephone?
Um...
Okay.
Director Danvers, why is
my DEO on lockdown tonight?
It's Toyman, sir.
Toyman?
I thought he was dead.
Yes, well, apparently,
he has uploaded himself
into our system.
It took us all
completely by surprise.
Clearly.
Can you sequester the AI?
The last thing
this world needs is
a rogue Toyman on the Web.
We're trying.
And in the meantime,
just in case,
I'm gathering
all of our smart tech
to have Supergirl
fly it out immediately.
I know it's a risk,
but if anyone can
do the job, it's her.
But she can't.
In case you've forgotten,
rogue Kryptonians have
attacked our planet before.
The DEO has
Kryptonite safeguards in place,
and, no,
they cannot be disabled.
Well, we have anti-Kryptonite
technology to protect her.
I think you're remembering that
from another time.
Another Earth, perhaps.
I have a split shift crew.
You want the 12 of us
to go around the entire DEO
to dismantle all of our tech
and hope that Toyman
doesn't regain control
while we do it?
National safety is
our primary responsibility,
and that is why you have to do
everything in your power
to neutralize that thing
and not let it get out.
Are we understood?
Yes, sir.
Good. Keep me posted.
Winn.
Agent Dox. I was wondering
when you'd call.
You knew Toyman would
upload himself into the DEO.
I correctly theorized it, yes.
And you didn't tell me.
It was need-to-know.
And now that you do know,
you need to know,
I want you to get me
Toyman's code.
What Toyman used
to put himself
into the computer.
Why?
So we can beat Leviathan
at their own game.
They are the greatest threat
this planet faces.
And you want their immortality.
It's the one advantage
they have over me.
With this code, I can
level the playing field.
As soon as you can make sure
no one is watching,
access Toyman's code
and copy it.
Once you are done,
you'll have gotten us
one step closer
to saving the world.
What was that?
I've never been allergic
to lobster before.
The Bio-Link on the lenses
still isn't working.
Look, eating virtually
still provides the body
with nutrients,
but the interface
is hyper-stimulating
the body's sensory reaction
into a kind of toxic shock.
Last week, we were
this close to perfecting
Obsidian Platinum.
We need to fix this.
- Miss Rojas,
Lena Luthor is waiting
in your office.
Lena.
Twice in one week.
It's getting to be
like old times.
Well, I know
you're gearing up for
the Platinum launch
and I was hoping
I could get a preview.
I loved
your first-generation lenses.
They were helpful to me
in so many ways.
So maybe I could get a peek?
Of course.
Except, we're not
quite ready yet.
Oh.
Is everything all right?
Yes, nothing major. Just, uh...
a small issue
with the Bio-Link algorithm.
Oh, that doesn't sound good.
You know, maybe I can help.
Luthor Corp's been working
with the Pentagon
on a new neural interface.
We've just developed
a special processor
that regulates Bio-Linking
across a wide spectrum.
It's completely eliminated
the feedback loop, gotten
most of the side effects.
Well, that's impressive,
but we're not the Pentagon.
And that's a good thing.
The Pentagon just dropped out,
leaving us with perhaps
the perfect interface for you.
So what do you say?
We help Obsidian North
revolutionize virtual reality?
I appreciate the offer,
but our last attempt
at collaboration
almost ruined everything
between us.
I don't wanna risk that.
You're right.
But let me know
if you change your mind.
The offer still stands.
I will.
There is only one place
I think the AI can be.
In a prime server tower down
in the sub-basement corridor.
Now, the way that we find
which server the Toyman is on,
is to physically go down
into the corridors
and search for it.
Luckily,
we had this in storage.
Van Eck radiation scanner.
It's delinked from our intranet
and able to distinguish
between normal server radiation
and abnormal radiation,
thereby allowing us
to pinpoint Toyman.
Accordingly, I shall head
into the corridors.
No, Brainy,
we need you up here
in case Toyman tries to get
in the command center again.
I'll go.
Uh, not without me.
Are you sure
you're up for this?
This is my enemy.
It's my problem.
Plus, I'm the only one
that knows the code.
Okay, fine.
Winn, Supergirl,
go for the servers,
Brainy, you keep him
at bay digitally,
and I will make sure
that he doesn't get ahold
of any of our tech.
You know, it's so funny
because we have all these
eyes and ears in there
looking and listening
all the time, but...
who is watching who?
Brainy.
I need to know.
Is this another step
in one of Lex's plans?
Lex did help manipulate
Toyman's digital reemergence
but I had nothing
to do with it.
Helping Lex is
what I have to do
for the sake of the future.
You know that.
Still, I promise
I have everything
under control.
Okay.
I am trusting you.
Doppio espresso.
To cheer you up?
What makes you think
I need cheering up?
Well, you're trying to
advance your grand project.
The Q-waves from
the archive cube had helped,
but the next step remains...
elusive.
A Lex who cares about
the emotional state of others.
This really is
a whole new world.
I care because
your goals are my goals.
Ah, it does always come back
to you, doesn't it?
But, yes, with the exception
of field testing,
my Non Nocere
algorithm is almost ready.
Just...
need a distribution device
so I can get it to
as many people as possible
all at once.
I thought I'd come to
an agreement with Andrea
this evening, but--
She said no.
I have to say, Andrea was
always a bit short-sighted.
Perhaps there's something
I can do?
I don't need
anyone murdered, Lex.
I have other skill sets.
Plus, we're partners.
Let me help.
Wait, are you actually
asking my permission?
It's a whole new world.
Fine.
Nice one.
Well, I try.
I just wish
you didn't have to
on account of my dad's
global insanity nightmare--
It's not your fault.
Actually, it kinda is.
When I told you guys that
I remembered my dad's code,
I'm the one
that came up with it.
Look, I thought
it would be cool.
Why just play a video game,
you know, when you can
be inside of one?
I'd stay up past midnight
trying to think
of different ways
to express Premack's theory
of the mind in this
little blue notebook.
My dad finally caught me
with it and asked me
what it was.
I thought he was getting mad,
but he seemed...
He seemed proud.
Of course, now I know
it wasn't pride, it was greed.
The night the police finally
came and took him away,
I went to look
for the notebook.
It was gone.
Turns out that
he had taken it
and left in its place
a little toy monkey.
I'm sorry.
Ah, it... It's fine.
Let's talk about
something else.
Hey. You and William.
-What's with that?
-What?
I totally messed him
asking you out.
-What? No, no. That was not...
-I messed that up.
Well, he wasn't...
-There's... There is
nothing there.
-What?
I'm sorry, but even
in the 30th century,
harmonizing that beautifully
with someone is a definitive
sign of something there.
Maybe I like him.
I don't... I don't know.
The truth is,
given who I am
and the secrets I keep,
I'm not sure I can
even have a relationship.
My double life blew up
my friendship with Lena.
So how am I supposed
to date someone?
Just because Lena reacted
the way that she did
does not mean
that other people will.
Maybe so, but I refuse
to start any relationship
on a lie.
William asked you out
on one date, Kara.
You don't even know
if it's gonna go anywhere,
but you won't find out
unless you try.
And then if it does,
you know, just...
take it one step at a time.
One step at a time, huh?
-That's right.
-Whoa.
So we've got
the command center cleared.
But if Toyman comes back,
we cannot let him
get his digital hands
on any of this.
So, Squad 1, I want you
to pop the chips
out of every smart gun.
Squad 2, do the same
with communication tech.
Squad 3,
delink everything else.
We've really outsmarted
ourselves here, haven't we?
All right, get to work.
Everyone, keep working.
I'll check it out.
Breach!
I think Toyman's
this way.
Toyman?
Winslow.
At last you're here.
Dad.
The song. I...
I knew it was you.
Winn, I had to
get your attention.
Oh, you got my attention.
-No, no. I'm here to help.
-No. Don't.
Explain yourself.
Winn knows.
Digitizing my consciousness
was my dream.
Yeah. A dream you stole.
Fine. But when that
other Winn digitized himself,
he used the underlying code
that I'd written,
plus my hardware.
Now, I managed to translate
80% of myself,
but he must have paired it with some sort of future tech,
because when he came online,
I did too.
And now you wanna help us?
Yes. I'm trapped
in a backup drive,
and the only way
I can do anything is
if you release me.
I'm sorry. Are you insane?
Oh, wait, yes.
Clinically, you are.
If we let him go,
he will do what he always does
and wreak havoc everywhere.
That's not true!
I mean,
it was my original plan,
but this other Winn is planning to do things that are
beyond the pale.
I've seen it in his code.
Yeah, well, that's why
I'm going to delete
both of you.
But I wanna help.
And you can't beat him alone.
Supergirl, Winn,
apparently, three of
Toyman's sentries are headed
for you as we speak.
What kind of sentries?
It seems that before
Toyman's AI got into our net,
it got into
some flying monkeys.
Supergirl, go this way.
-You'll be safe.
No, no, you are not fooling us.
Not now, not ever.
There is a service corridor
behind this wall.
Winslow, no!
Forgive my boldness
at this hour.
It's just I saw you
across the room
and knew I had to pounce.
Lex Luthor.
You should be careful
where you pounce.
You never know
what you might find.
Oh, but I do know
who you are.
Gemma Cooper.
Board chair of Obsidian North,
renowned computer scientist
with excellent taste
in wine, horses,
and business opportunities.
What kind of opportunities?
Mmm. The kind that can satisfy
both Obsidian North
and Luthor Corp.
Funny. I don't think
there is much
we had in common.
Oh. I'd think a woman
of your vision and insight
would be able to see
past the superficial.
You have an interface issue
with the Obsidian Platinum
Bio-Link.
Today, my sister offered
to help fix it.
Your CEO rejected her offer
because she let her feelings
determine her business moves,
and I think you're
smarter than that.
You're suggesting that we get
into bed with Luther Corp?
Since when is that smart?
Whenever it comes to
doing business anywhere
on this planet.
You have amazing technology--
At least you almost do.
We have allies and assets,
government stooges
and supporters
in every corner of the globe.
That's the kind of reach
you can't get with just
a snap of your fingers.
So you have the potential,
but we can help you realize it.
And what do you expect
to get back in exchange
for this "help"?
The tech field can only hold
so many players.
Sooner or later,
there might not be room
for the both of us.
Why be at each other's throats
when we could be
joined at the hip?
Who knows,
we might like it.
I can be an excellent friend
when I want to be.
And I do want
to be your friend...
for a long time.
Are you okay?
I know the last time
you saw your father
was pretty horrible.
Trusting him never leads
to anything good.
I get that,
but "never" is a big word.
J'onn recently found himself
in a blood feud
with his brother
where he said they would
never make amends,
and now they're brothers
that support each other.
Yeah, well, good for J'onn,
but I am not trusting
Toyman No. 1 or 2
until they are both deleted.
Director Danvers,
the rest of the tablets
have been delinked.
Permission to delink yours?
Um, no,
I'll take care of that,
thank you.
You son of a...
Brainy.
What the hell were you
doing in my account?
I trusted you
with that spyware.
And you hacked into my tablet
and you overrode my commands
and you deleted it.
Just tell me I'm wrong!
You're not wrong.
I did it.
I knew it.
You know what?
Ever since those other Brainys
got you to take off
your inhibitors,
you have been acting different,
and it's not some
personality different.
It's like you're
hiding something.
Like you've got
some secret plan.
I did it
to protect you, Alex.
Come on.
Sooner or later,
Lex would have
found your spyware,
he would have traced it
back to your account--
I knew the risk.
It isn't a risk, it's a fact.
Look, if this Toyman fiasco's
taught us anything,
it's that technology,
no matter how sophisticated,
can be used against us.
It's just a matter of when.
I should have told you first.
But I refuse to let
Lex come after you.
Gemma.
Is everything all right?
Apparently not.
According to Lex Luthor,
our interface isn't working,
and it's generating
catastrophic results.
Um, look,
that's an overstatement.
And when you were
given the opportunity
to team up with them
to fix this issue,
you passed.
The Luthors may have
a slight scientific edge,
but...
Lena and I have not had
the best relationship
in the past.
This isn't about
your friendship with Lena.
It's about staying focused
on the business
that your father spent
his life building,
that you yourself have brought
to the precipice
of one of the biggest
tech advancements in history.
I know where we stand.
Then I don't need to remind you
of all the other relationships
you've abandoned
to get this
where it needs to be.
The Luthors can help us.
In college,
when I agreed
to be your mentor,
it was because I believed
you would never back down.
Maybe I was wrong.
Lena?
It's Andrea.
I think I've changed my mind.
This is it.
-Toyman's prime server.
So,
what happens now?
In a few clicks,
this will all be over.
Is everything okay?
Code is not entering.
Brainy.
-Have you found the server?
- Yeah, we did,
but we're having a problem.
What is it?
Every time I try to enter
the kill code, it keeps
getting bounced back.
It seems Toyman's AI is
growing too strong for you
to access it anywhere
outside the server.
But how else do we access it?
I have to go inside it.
I have this
from the Legion ship.
It allows me to enter
the digital space temporarily.
If you go inside it,
can't you run into--
My dad, or Toyman,
or... both.
Yeah.
What was that?
We have Lexosuits?
Toyman's AI
is inside of them.
Get out now.
They're breaking out.
Toyman's tech is trying
to escape.
If it succeeds,
there is a 100% chance
that Toyman will be able to weaponize the entire Internet.
Go. I can do this.
-But your father--
-It's only code, okay?
And this is simple.
I go to it,
I enter the kill code,
and then I get out.
I can do this.
I mean, I have to do this.
Don't forget...
I'm Computer Lad.
Okay, what doesn't belong?
Gotcha.
-Winn!
You... You shouldn't be
in here by yourself.
You won't be able
to hold him back alone.
You need me!
I do not need you!
Tag!
You're it.
Open the doors
with the palm lock, son.
Just reach up
and do it.
Trust me, I've... I've changed!
You can't trust him.
I did all of this for him,
and look how he treats me.
That's because you're a psycho!
I got you. I got you.
Supergirl, you have to
get away from here.
I'm not leaving this fight.
Don't be crazy.
This isn't some time
to stick to some code.
Unless you're them.
Toyman may be controlling
our technology,
but that tech still keys
on sound, motion,
and brightness.
Accordingly, if I become
the brightest and the loudest
in the room,
then I'll be
the tech's only target.
And if it's focused on you,
we can focus on it.
Moths to a flame.
Winn! Just... Just let go!
He's right.
Let go.
The fall will kill you.
Just let go
because in here...
you can!
Leeroy Jenkins!
Winn,
please, just let me out
and we can stop him together!
No way!
Even this dummy knows
you're lying, Dad.
He knows.
If I get deleted, so do you.
All right. When I said
I changed, I lied.
I haven't changed in here,
but I have learned
looking through
the DEO's files here
and all the good things
you've done for your friends
and for the world.
And it made me so proud, son.
I mean, I've always said
that you and I are alike,
but that... that's not true.
No. We're almost nothing alike.
You're simply
the best part of me.
If there was ever a time
to... to take a leap,
it's now.
And like I said,
in here, you can do anything.
Look out!
Go on, son!
Finish entering the code.
Game over.
Supergirl, he's
trying to escape!
Not today.
No! No, stop!
Dad?
Finish it, son!
It's the only way!
Winn?
I'm here.
Are you okay?
My dad saved me.
He was telling the truth.
Sometimes, people
can surprise us.
Nice to
see you back at work.
How did you access my phone?
I have this room shielded.
Just a little bit of tech
I've been working on.
But, really, I just
wanted to see if you'd
sorted things with Andrea.
Clearly you have.
You know the words
you want to hear me say,
"Thank you."
Well, thank you.
You said you'd bring
Andrea around, and you did.
It was my pleasure.
Though, it's still a mystery
why Obsidian's tech
malfunctioned
in the first place.
I suppose
it was just fortuitous
that you were
in the right place
to make the right move.
Is it really?
Oh, Lena.
I am impressed.
Sabotaging your friend
to get what you want.
Not to get what I want.
For the good of humanity.
Ah, of course.
But that is exactly
the kind of thinking
we're going to need
to defeat Leviathan.
Your big brother
is proud of you.
I don't suppose my big brother
wants to tell me what he did
to bring Andrea around.
I just made friends
with an Obsidian board chair,
Gemma Cooper.
If you ask me,
she'll be a friend to us both
for a long time.
Please tell the Anointed One
the Luthors are right
where we want them.
She will be most pleased.
Here is all
the Kryptonite from the DEO.
That's the Lexosuits
and the lockdown shields.
Everything that we could grab.
I can still send
all of it into the sun.
Speaking of space, Alex,
I may have some
Martian eavesdropping tech
that Lex may find
hard to uncover,
if you're interested.
Well, you should
give it to Brainy...
'cause I'm quitting the DEO.
Alex, really?
Lex is everywhere in there,
and I can't keep showing up
and smiling at him,
and... Even if
it's just pretend.
Plus, now you can come
and work with me.
National City may need
the tower,
but the tower needs leaders.
Could be fun.
Fun and logical.
Brainy, you should come too.
I mean, why not
just work here?
Ironically, the logic
that dictates you must leave
also dictates
that I must stay...
to provide you all
with eyes and ears
around Lex.
Your friends are always
gonna have your back, Brainy.
And you, Winn, how are you?
Oh, you know.
Ready to go home.
-Being here with you guys
has, I mean...
It... It's helped me
a lot more than
the future ever could have.
Just... It's just helped me
get over my dad
and, you know, his crimes,
just my past,
all of it. So...
Thank you.
-Come on.
It's been good to see you.
All right.
Come here. Come here.
Ah, we'll see you soon,
Computer Lad.
No!  Okay, okay.
Listen.
It's not Computer Lad
anymore, all right?
From now on...
it's Toyman.
Winn, seriously?
Yeah.
You guys, when I told you
that I was okay
being called Computer Lad,
are you kidding me?
No, I hated that.
"Computer Lad."
-No.
What?
But "Toyman..."
You know, that name has
always haunted me.
But now after having faced
my father...
He told me that
I was better than him.
And he was right.
So I'm gonna reclaim that name.
- Hmm.
-And make it stand for good.
Hey, it's like the Doctor said,
"The future is
whatever you want..."
"So make it a good one."
Nice, "Doc" Brown.
Thank you.
All right, guys.
That's my ride.
Oh, hey. Hey.
I know that
you can't do anything
about Lena right now,
but just give it time.
And with William,
you don't have to start
a relationship with a lie.
Just see where it goes.
One step at a time.
Yeah.
I'll miss you.
Okay. That's enough.
Hello, Kara.
Hello.
So, uh, I was thinking,
-um--
-Just one second.
I'm sorry.
It's for your Gran Gran.
The one who was sick.
Oh, right.
My grandma.
My grandmother swears
a good puzzle is better
than antibiotics.
So.
You were saying?
Yeah. Uh...
I was thinking...
I'm sorry, William,
I just don't feel
that way about you.
Ah...
I understand.
I'm sorry for misreading
the situation.
No, no, it's fine.
I'll see you later.
Yeah.
There.
Toyman's immortality code.
I was able to pull
the relevant sections
while everyone else
was distracted.
You are
a very useful employee,
Agent Dox.
Also, I should add
Director Danvers no longer
poses a threat to you
or our operation.
Perfect.
Especially as I just received
her resignation.
So, it would seem
congratulations are in order.
Congratulations.
To you...
DEO Director Dox.
So, how did it go?
He asked about
my sick grandmother.
-And I had to go with it.
It was the first thing
out of my mouth,
and it was a lie.
And then I just... left.
I can battle
Kryptonite-powered Lexosuits,
but I can't even take
the first step
in a relationship
because it is doomed
with deception.
You don't know that for sure.
Well, it happened
with my friendship with Lena.
And I can't help
thinking that...
if I had done
things differently,
maybe things would have
turned out differently.
There is just...
There's no way of knowing.
Oh, that probably
J'onn with the pizza,
which is great.
Hi!
Some say
there's no way of knowing.
But I say, first,
ask Mr. Mxyzptlk.