Previously onSupergirl...
With Obsidian Platinum,
you will never
have to choose between
your life and your dream.
Ever since Luthor Corp
partnered with us,
the board has a new member.
He could lock in subscribers.
It's built to trap you.
You don't think
our users deserve a warning
that the lenses
might be problematic?
I need a full
diagnostic write-up
on the fail-safe error code.
Yes, Miss Rojas.
We'll always find you, Eve.
Leviathan is everywhere.
The shooter has been identified as Lex Luthor.
Officers responding.
He's been disarmed, but he's still on the premises.
I knew it was him.
That lady
on the ground
was gonna shoot us.
One by one.
And that's when
Mr. Luthor showed up.
He wrestled the gun from her.
It just went off.
You saved them, Mr. Luthor.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
These people will all think
Lex saved them.
Wasn't Lex the one
who put 'em in here?
Apparently not.
Listen to this.
Amy Sapphire was right.
Technology is the greatest evil mankind has ever faced.
I will continue her work
by killing people
until the world wakes up
from its apathy.
She was an acolyte
of Amy Sapphire's.
She'd been kidnapping
Obsidian Platinum users
for weeks.
Took full responsibility.
Thank you so much.
I was sure Lex was behind this.
Yeah. We all were.
I don't understand.
Lex...
a real hero?
How could this be true?
It's so much more fun
making Superman
kill Superman.
You've got to get
Luthor out of your head, Kal.
Who are you?
I...
hate...
Kryptonians.
Are you all right, sir?
That depends.
Am I dead?
Heavens no, sir.
But I dare say
you're a bit hungover.
Coffee?
I saved the world.
It's all in a day's work
for you, isn't it, Mr. Luthor?
Why else would they
be awarding you
the Nobel Peace Prize?
Uh...
I didn't just save the world...
I made a new world.
Any chance you've seen
my darling sister around?
So, the Monitor
kept his word.
The pre-Nobel celebration
went so late...
Ms. Luthor decided
to spend the night.
Don't worry, Lena, this will
just extend your beauty sleep
for a few hours
while I handle
some family business.
Sweet dreams.
Make sure she ends up
in her own home.
Sugar, dear?
You're rather calm for a woman
who just learned
the entire multi-verse
has been obliterated.
You do understand
I'm not the son you raised?
Perfectly.
Would your Lillian
have been frightened
by world destruction?
If so, you've upgraded.
-No sugar.
-That's my boy.
The past is the past.
Best to focus on the future.
In this world,
the Luthors are revered.
How do we maintain our status?
Well, of course,
the first order of business
is finding
the Fortress of Solitude
-and destroying
the Kryptonians--
-Why?
Supergirl is
your greatest ally.
Was, I'm afraid.
Supergirl will remember
the previous world
as vividly as I do.
Soon it will be war.
We need to be prepared.
You, me, and Lena.
The Lena who killed you?
That Lena?
Well, you said she'll remember
your previous world, too.
What's your point?
That you have
an inferiority complex
over a pair of hokey heroes
in blue tights.
If Supergirl sneezes too hard,
it would split
this planet in half.
And yet, it was her friendship
with your sister
that spun you out.
Friendship and loyalty
to Supergirl was what prompted
Lena to kill me.
Your obsession with Kryptonians
led to your demise once.
Let's not create
a repeat performance, hmm?
On this planet,
the Luthors are cool-headed.
We plan,
we implement, and we rise...
together.
Show your sister
you believe in her.
Support her efforts.
She'll gravitate toward you
and away from the Kryptonian.
The question is...
can you give up
your pet vendetta
and stay focused?
Are you really querying
my strength of will, Mother?
I'm a Luthor.
Good.
Now go make Lena your ally.
All right,
so you'll be my friend now?
The world is ours now, Lena.
You don't need a robot.
And you don't need friends.
You need a partner.
Imagine what we could
accomplish together?
Why not give it a go?
You think
this is your world now?
You were a puppet on a string
for Leviathan before.
What makes this time
any different?
What the hell is Leviathan?
You see, that's the thing
about narcissists.
You're so focused on yourself,
you can never see
that you're the mark.
Your little fan-girl
was working for Leviathan
the entire time
she was working you.
Ms. Tessmacher.
And what exactly
does Leviathan want?
No one knows.
They're behind
seismic catastrophes,
earthquakes, floods, plagues.
They're alien, ancient,
and all-powerful.
And if it wasn't
for your hubris,
you would've seen that
they were playing you.
All right, Lena.
You've had your fun letting me
know I let my eye off the ball.
I'll admit this Leviathan
is... irritating.
What are you gonna do?
Exterminate them.
Hello, National City!
Well, by now you might've heard that my splashy show at ToyCon
caused, well...
Hi, boys.
Just stopping by
to examine the ship
for the DEO.
That's your cue to leave
and wait outside.
Search for Leviathan.
Oh...
Of course.
Show me all of her associates.
Stop.
I underestimated you, Eve.
Give me everything you have
on this woman on this Earth.
Please...
It is really loud out there.
Lex Luthor?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help you,
Ms. Tessmacher.
You know my name?
I know a lot more
than your name.
I know that you're brilliant.
I know that Leviathan
recruited you to work for them
as a spy and an assassin.
But you turned them down,
so they murdered your father
to change your mind.
I know that they've forced you
to do their bidding
by vowing to kill
your beloved mother
if you dare defy them.
And I know
that you hate it,
because you're a good person.
Am I?
You are, Eve, believe me.
I wouldn't be rescuing
someone I didn't think was
worthy of my time.
Nobody can fight Leviathan.
You're going to
have to trust me.
Do you think you can do that?
Better decide quick,
Ms. Tessmacher.
Stay with them,
and continue to bloody
those pretty little hands...
or work with me
to destroy the people
who stole your life.
I don't want to kill anymore.
Good choice.
So, what do you want from me?
Be my partner.
Keep working at Leviathan,
and be my eyes and ears.
In return,
I promise I'll protect you.
And that you won't
have to do any of this
awful, dirty work anymore.
I'll do it for you.
Obsidian North is proud
to introduce Platinum,
a virtual reality experience
that will look, feel, and taste
more vivid than real life.
Give yourself
the gift of Platinum.
Ms. Tessmacher...
what is it?
I couldn't get Gamemnae
to take me
onto Leviathan's ship.
-I'm scared.
-Ah. Forgive me, Eve.
I should've eased your mind
days ago. Please.
Now, this is a live feed.
I'm sure you recognize
the sweet little house
you grew up in.
There's your mother
baking in the kitchen.
But I suspect
what you don't recognize
is that sedan,
or those other two.
Those cars belong
to ex-Mossad agents
that I've hired to guard
your mother around the clock.
How can I thank you,
Mr. Luthor?
Lex, please.
And you can thank me
after we've found
the cold-blooded killer
who took your father's life.
We're a team, Eve.
I do have some good news.
I convinced Gamemnae
I would be most useful
at Obsidian...
on the Platinum project.
Well done! You are brilliant.
Well, we do have
one small problem.
The Luthor tech that
your sister convinced
Andrea Rojas
to put into
the Platinum infrastructure,
it helped solve the bio-link
when people were getting
toxic shock
eating virtual food.
I like to refer to that
as the lobster problem.
Or rather, middle America's
desire to be gluttons
without calories.
Well, it caused a glitch.
But...
Your fail-safe failed.
I assure you,
this glitch will be fixed
long before the launch
of Obsidian Platinum.
Don't worry, I found a way
to patch the glitch.
That's not a glitch.
That's my plan.
My colleague is retrieving
a code that digitizes
the human psyche,
enabling us to
make someone immortal
by uploading
their consciousness
into a computer.
I believe we can reverse
the same code
and use it against Leviathan.
Then Leviathan is immortal
no more.
But I need an invitation
to get onto their ship.
Which means I need Gamemnae,
or Gemma, if you prefer,
to trust me.
And trust begins
with that glitch.
But if there's a glitch
and people are getting stuck,
nobody's gonna buy the lenses.
Correct. Leviathan will
need to fix it.
But they won't be able to
because you won't let them.
And when Leviathan
can't fix it,
they'll have to cover it up,
and that's where I come in.
I will help Gemma
with the cover-up.
Once she trusts you,
she'll give you an invitation
to the ship.
An engraved one.
So, you need to go back
to Obsidian
and make sure that glitch
does not get fixed,
or traced back to me or Lena.
Done.
What are you gonna do?
Start exerting pressure.
Give me another one.
Hell, you know what,
just give me the bottle.
My wife is cheating on me.
Tell me about it, man.
Maybe I can help.
Lex.
My new apartment,
it's a dream!
When you said that
you were getting me
a new place,
I thought you meant
a small studio somewhere.
You're very precious
to me, Eve.
No one's ever treated me
this way before.
It's time you realize
how wonderful you are.
But we still have a mission.
How is Obsidian?
I've been monitoring
all of the beta users.
And Richard Bates
still hasn't made a move
on his wife's virtual lover.
Not yet. Because his friend,
the bartender,
who turned out to be
an amazing hacker,
I might add,
won't let him complete
his virtual torture chamber
until the time is right.
And I still need to
create trust with Leviathan.
Amy Sapphire.
She blames Obsidian's VR
for the death of her husband.
She threatened
Andrea Rojas' life.
-You're going to warn Gemma
to gain Leviathan's trust?
-The opposite.
We're gonna help Amy Sapphire
attack Andrea Rojas
and blow up Obsidian.
But if anyone attacks Obsidian,
Leviathan is gonna want me
to terminate them.
Gemma won't ask you
to assassinate anybody
because I will intervene
before she gets the chance.
I will offer up Supergirl
to protect Andrea
and Obsidian.
Just make sure
that Amy Sapphire
gets these gauntlets.
It'll make her
a worthy adversary
for Supergirl.
And after Supergirl succeeds
in saving Andrea,
I will have proven myself
to Gemma.
And then, I will suggest that
I roll out Obsidian Platinum
worldwide.
Lex, you're brilliant.
But beyond that,
you are so kind.
-And I think I'm--
-I know, Eve.
I feel the same.
But we have to stay focused
on our goals,
free you from them
and avenge your father.
There'll be time for us later.
Now, I have to
show you something.
Oh, they're so cute!
Aww!
Q-waves?
Something like that.
Aw, he likes you.
He's happy.
That one isn't.
Oh, gosh!
That didn't work right.
Actually, it worked perfectly.
Amy, no!
This can't be right.
Do you need to get that, dear?
Not important.
Ms. Tessmacher,
why have you brought me
to the world's saddest
urgent care center?
People have begun
getting stuck in the VR,
just like you anticipated.
Uh, Gemma asked me
to look into the glitch.
I told her that
there was nothing we could do
without shutting down
the entire system,
which can't be shut down
thanks to Luthor PowerCore.
She asked Margot
to start cleaning things up.
Who or what is a Margot?
Leviathan middle-management...
and a mean old hag to boot.
It's time
to set Richard loose.
This is a back door
that will allow Richard Bates
to hack into Platinum
to get revenge.
That'll put welcome eyes
on Obsidian's problems
as this place starts
to fill up with bodies.
Make sure he gets it.
Oh, and I have
something else for you.
Perfume?
Uh-uh... Perfume, poison...
Potayto, potahto.
What you're holding
is the deadliest substance
on Earth.
You told me I wouldn't have to
kill for Leviathan ever again.
And I always keep my promises.
Every single one.
That's why I tracked down
the man who murdered
your father...
just like I said I would.
Who is he?
A Leviathan enforcer.
He's in the Peruvian Andes
working undercover with an NGO.
I suspect
because he has a target there.
I should put a bullet
in his head.
It's the least he deserves.
But we can't go to war
with Leviathan.
It has to look like
an accident.
You can handle that, right?
Yes.
Then be quick.
I don't expect that
he will stay in one place
for very long.
And nor will I.
It's time for me to embark
on my world tour,
hawking Obsidian lenses.
The beginning of the end...
of Leviathan.
"Our lives are connected
by 1,000 invisible threads."
Those immortal words
by Herman Melville
are realized today
with Obsidian technology.
This is my house!
-And this is my gun.
But with
Obsidian Platinum,
you hold the thread.
You are the architect
of your world!
-They found Dad.
-Jeremiah?
He's dead.
And not only your world,
but the world.
There is nothing you cannot
manipulate to your own ends.
Nothing you cannot control!
So are you blowing off steam
playing hero,
or working something out?
♪ I never lost control
♪ You're face to face
♪ With the man
Who sold the world... ♪
Obsidian offers
something special,
something unique,
something rare,
and that, my friends,
is control!
-Complete and total control!
One hundred countries,
worldwide saturation.
It took 40 years
for the cell phone to
reach as many users
as our lenses have reached
in one month.
All thanks
to our passionate ambassador,
Lex Luthor.
♪ You're face to face
♪ With the man
Who sold the world ♪
Kara...
I heard about Jeremiah.
I came to offer up sympathies.
"Offer up
my sympathies."
-God, I sound like an android.
-No.
No, you said it like someone
who's afraid
to confront the woman
who called you a villain.
My mother died
when I was very young.
And I'm...
I know that pales
in comparison to the losses
that you've suffered,
but I know
it doesn't get any easier.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for saying that.
That means a lot
coming from you.
Um...
This helped me a lot
with memories of my mother
and other family difficulties.
Well, if it helped with
Luthor family difficulties,
I'm sure it'll help me a lot.
Thank you.
You missed a perfectly fine en passant
capture opportunity.
You're distracted.
What's wrong?
She apologized to her.
Be clear
with your pronouns, dear.
Lena apologized to Kara.
To Supergirl.
For the death of Jeremiah.
-I thought
you put that behind you.
-I did!
The assassination
of Jeremiah Danvers was
the perfect chess move,
but for the fact that
it maddeningly drove Lena
back to Supergirl!
And the worst part is
that I didn't even see it
as a possibility.
So, yes, Mother,
I missed the en passant.
I'm missing a lot of things,
I'm slipping.
The only thing
you're slipping off of
is the wagon.
So Lena showed the alien
a little humanity?
-What's wrong with that?
-It pushes the limit.
First, it's an apology.
Then, it's coffee before work.
Next thing you know,
they're playing Pictionary.
That cannot happen!
I know what to do.
I'll set up Supergirl.
You already
have a plan in place
with Leviathan.
I did, but this is better.
Why use a nuke
to create a catastrophe
to draw Leviathan out,
when I can use a Sun-Eater
to turn Lena against
Kara Danvers in one stroke?
I asked you if you had
the strength of will,
and you said, "Yes, Mother!"
This is a display of weakness.
Not weakness, Mother.
Inspiration.
Checkmate.
Ms. Tessmacher,
it's time to activate
William Dey.
Make sure your contact
gives him the name
on the medical bracelet
he found.
And then,
I need you to move the bodies.
Don't you think
that it's weird
that we're sitting here
eating dumplings
like everything is normal,
and yet, Jeremiah is gone?
No. The only permanent thing
about life is
that things change.
The cycle of life goes on.
And you... still need to eat.
Yeah, you know what,
this book the Lena gave me
actually has
strikingly similar advice.
"Things are constantly in flux,
arising and passing
with each moment."
-We have no control,
so eat the dumplings.
-Yeah.
Well, I still can't believe
the fact that she gave you that
after everything that happened.
Well, maybe she's
coming around.
-Seeing the light about Lex.
No. No light about him.
-That man is--
-The devil incarnate.
-Yes.
-Yeah. Mmm-hmm.
I hope you weren't
talking about me.
No. No, no, no.
Lex Luthor.
-And are these baked goods?
-Yes.
Scones, sticky toffee pudding,
and banoffee pie,
all my mother's
favorite recipes
for comfort food.
-I... I hope it helps.
Oh, my God!
You made all of this?
Well, I didn't want to
show up empty-handed
coming here, asking for help...
with a story on Lex Luthor
and Obsidian.
You got a lead?
Wait, you, you both
have been working on this?
Before your father's funeral,
Kelly and I were onto this idea
that Lex had done something
to Obsidian
to cause people
to get stuck in VR
and disappear.
The missing people were
wearing Obsidian lenses.
And a friend of mine
from the NSA
found a cluster of users
all at the same address,
a warehouse.
But when I checked,
it was empty.
Only weird thing was
a hospital ID bracelet
on the ground.
So, I checked it
for fingerprints.
I found one and sent it
to my buddy at the NSA.
Now, he just called me back
with results when I was baking.
The bracelet belonged
to a Richard Bates.
The same person
who hacked
Obsidian's fail-safe.
And who I beat up in VR.
One and the same.
And get this...
The hospital has no record
of a Richard Bates
ever being admitted.
Wait a minute. Kelly, you said
there was a list of users that
are still stuck in VR, right?
-Can you show me that?
-Yeah.
Here. This is
the current list of users.
Bonnie.
I met this girl in VR.
Why would anyone want
to keep her there?
Human testing.
Organ harvesting.
And if people
are getting hurt in Obsidian,
we need to find out about it
and expose them.
If we find the proof,
I'll run the story.
It'll be around the globe
in minutes.
The world will know
if Obsidian is
endangering them.
They're on your tail.
It doesn't matter.
Our cloaking technology
will cover all our bases
from the human eye.
They won't stop
until they uncover the truth.
And what is that exactly?
That you and your
Leviathan associates
are ancient beings
who manage humanity's
excesses.
Don't get me wrong,
Gemma,
or Gamemnae,
or would you prefer, uh,
Goddess of Technology?
I approve.
Pompei was spectacular,
the Black Plague, intriguing,
and your current move,
creating an addiction
to Obsidian Platinum, genius.
-The only problem is
your plan is now at risk.
-No, it's not.
I'll pull up the timeline
for our VR global event.
It'll be a happening beyond
humanity's wildest dreams.
A virtual gathering of
everyone around the world.
No one will want to miss it.
And once the masses are in VR,
I'll kill them all
with a flick of my wrist.
That would be great,
if you weren't
about to be exposed.
Obsidian will be shut down,
all the lenses returned
before you sell
the first ticket.
You don't have
the luxury of time.
What do you propose?
Create fear.
It's instantaneous,
and I have a specific idea
of how to do it.
I just need
your stealthiest operative.
Director Dox,
long time no see.
I come bearing gifts,
a pysanka.
Gifted to me
by a Ukrainian holy man
on my world tour.
It brings love and wealth,
and of course fertility.
Does it also bring
the end of Leviathan?
You were meant to have gotten
the location of their ship...
so we can implant
the mortality code.
I can't push them.
This delay doesn't have
anything to do
with you using
Obsidian Platinum for
your own ends, does it?
Alex Danvers called me.
She wants me to help her
track Obsidian users
she believes are being
lured into some type of coma.
By you.
While it is utterly predictable
that Alex Danvers
would call you,
it's not me behind
your missing users,
it's Leviathan.
Scout's honor.
I found out from Gemma Cooper.
Then help me find them.
You have the Q-wave cube
from Winn's ship.
I can use it
to track the lenses,
find the missing people.
Ah, well, I gave the cube
to Lena.
And if you involved her,
Leviathan would kill her.
And as much as
I'd like to help you,
I can't.
Leviathan would find out,
and then I'd be their enemy.
And as you know,
the long-term success
of our plan
relies on me
being the opposite.
But, by all means,
you should help them.
I know how important
your friends are to you.
Okay.
Lex, how shall I help them?
There's nothing at the DEO
that could track Q-waves.
Why don't you ask Supergirl?
I'm sure there's something
at that fortress of hers
that could help.
Hey, any luck
with the warehouse?
It was empty.
I was able to pick up
Richard Bates' psychic signal,
along with dozens of
other people in that warehouse.
But when I tried to connect,
there was
some kind of interference.
It's because Obsidian is
adding Platinum users
by the minute.
The lenses interface
with the brain
by using Q-waves...
which operate
on a similar frequency
as Malefic's Martian brain.
Just as I can't connect
with Mal, I can't find
those missing people.
You can connect with them...
by using Myriad.
Lena wanted
to use Myriad to disperse
her Q-wave mind control,
but if you turn it on
in reverse,
it will compress the Q-waves
in the atmosphere...
making it possible
for you to track
the psychic signatures.
And it wouldn't be dangerous?
In your hands, no.
Then I'll go.
But I don't like it.
The brain anatomy
of Patient 054 remains normal
post-Non Nocere.
The trial continues to exhibit
positive results
of Q-wave adoption.
Brava!
You've always been
so meticulous about
your data collection.
-What is that?
I use a Q-wave broadcast
to remotely access
patients' brain activity.
It's being interrupted
by an overlapping signal.
How could someone
suppress Q-waves?
I recognize the signature
of this interruption,
it's Myriad.
Yesterday, I thought
I had an honest conversation
with Supergirl,
and today I find out
that she's using Myriad
to interrupt my experiments?
The very device she told me
was too dangerous
for anyone to use.
You saw Supergirl yesterday?
I could always just
go to the Fortress,
if you told me where it was,
and turn off Myriad
before she interferes again.
No, you'll set off
the El Protocol.
This is a new world.
One where Luthors
and Kryptonians work together.
The fortress security won't be
programmed to attack us.
If she's using Myriad,
I wanna see it for myself.
Besides, you at the fortress
sounds apocalyptic.
Well...
then let this ride be on me.
You are using Myriad.
Lena, what are you doing here?
Question is, what are you
doing here, Supergirl?
I thought it was forbidden
to use Myriad,
but forbidden
for anyone but you.
There are people missing,
dozens of them stuck
in Obsidian's VR.
I have to find them.
There are other ways
to find people than Myriad.
I can think of four
off the top of my head,
but you,
you do what you want.
What I'm doing
is finding people
your brother disappeared.
Do you have any proof
that it was Lex?
No, I didn't think so.
You just return
to your default position
of blaming a Luthor.
You did tell me you'd
treat me like a villain...
If you acted like one,
yeah, I did say that.
And right now,
you're trespassing,
and I don't have time for this.
You need to go.
I'll leave
when you stop using Myriad.
That's not gonna happen.
To think that I was
sincere with you yesterday...
Then I guess
you're used to being two-faced.
No!
Why is this taking so long?
It takes several minutes
for Myriad to suppress
the Q-waves long enough
for J'onn to see clearly.
What is that?
A Sun-Eater.
That's impossible.
The only one in the system...
is the baby
from the Fortress of Solitude.
Supergirl?
Supergirl, are you there?
The Sun-Eater must've absorbed
her power.
Okay, well, we need to
save her. Like now.
We can use a Lexosuit
from the DEO.
If we recalibrate
the suit's internal radiation
to 1,000 watts per meter,
it will act like
a mini-sunlight chamber.
We'll get it
and bring it to the fortress.
-M'gann?
-J'onn...
your brother felt the Q-waves
on Mars and sent me.
My ship is armed
with hydrogen weapons
we can use
to stop the Sun-Eater.
Han Solo never looked so good.
-That was
a Star Warsreference.
-I know it. I know. Yeah.
Let's go save the sun.
Oh, heaven to Betsy.
The hydrogen explosive
should reduce it to a size
that we can contain.
If I can detonate one
inside it
and saturate it
like water with a fire.
I have faith in you,
J'onn J'onzz.
J'onn?
Anyone see a Sun-Eater
around here?
Supergirl!
We think we can shrink it
by detonating this explosive
in its core.
Lucky this suit has
its own explosives.
Missiles hot!
Right on schedule.
Ms. Tessmacher!
That thing is
much cuter when it's smaller.
Yeah, and not destroying
the solar system.
Have you figured out
what the Morae wanted
or who she works for?
She says she works
for someone called Leviathan.
-J'onn, what is it?
Myriad... the psychic trail.
I know where
those missing people are.
Lex, a real hero?
How can this be true?
If you weren't so obsessed
with trying to persecute me,
you might see that
on this Earth,
I've always been the hero.
All these people say so.
But I guess
we're all heroes today,
since I'm assuming
you and your friends
dealt with the big blackout.
You're not gonna
try and pin that on me,
are you?
No, that was... Leviathan.
The same Leviathan that
I told you would be a problem
months ago?
Perhaps if you listened to me
and tried to work with me,
we could stop
these dangerous organizations
before they try
to blot out the sun.
So, do you know what they want,
or where their base is?
Not yet.
-But we will.
-We're going to stop them.
You murdered Margot!
One of my own,
one of Leviathan's
most trusted agents.
Margot's death was unfortunate.
But she had to die,
given the breadth of our--
You don't tell me anything.
I am a god.
You are a nothing.
Do you understand?
Explain yourself.
As I said earlier...
the Supers were close
to finding your comatose souls.
So, I had to find them first.
I moved them,
and then pinned their existence
on someone else.
So, I connected Margot
to Amy Sapphire
and divorced her
from you and Leviathan.
Because of what I did,
no one is suspecting
Obsidian anymore.
Maybe you were right
to kill Margot,
but you made a mistake
with the disaster.
And now the Kryptonian
has one of my assassins
in her custody!
I underestimated Supergirl
and her team.
The chaos of the disaster
was working
until she intervened.
But now I know
you were right about
the global VR celebration.
We should
implement it immediately.
Gather everyone into VR
at once...
with this
sparkling distraction.
But first...
we must kill Supergirl.
She will always foil the plan.
And a warning...
no mere mortal can kill her.
Many have tried and failed.
I will not fail.
Do I smell Beef Wellington?
Victory and role-playing
makes me hungry.
"Amy Sapphire was right.
Technology is the greatest evil
mankind has ever faced."
Okay, stop there.
Please don't ever image-induce
into her ever again.
-I might lose my appetite.
I'm so glad
we finally have a night
to spend some time alone
as a couple.
A couple?
I've been trying to tell you
how I feel...
and it's not just
because you helped me
escape Leviathan,
it's because of who you are.
How could I not love you?
Oh...
Ms. Tessmacher...
you sad, silly woman...
of course you love me.
What's funny is, you thought
I could love you back.
I don't understand.
We're a team.
-We're meant to be together.
We're destined--
-Oh, we're destined.
On another world,
in another life, we knew
each other very well.
And in that life,
you said you loved me, too.
You distracted me,
you made me weaker.
But that's not happening
this time, honey.
I feel nothing for you.
I saved you
because you were useful.
I needed a spy
inside Leviathan.
Oh, and as for your mother...
she's still in danger,
but from me.
Those cars I showed you,
the men in them
are just waiting
to pull the trigger
if you ever betray me.
But I'd think twice
about that.
That man you killed
in the Andes
didn't murder your father.
I never bothered to find out
who knocked off
your old man.
No, the man you murdered
is Supergirl's father.
Oh, that's good.
I have video of you
killing him, by the way.
Defy me, and I'll pass it on.
Believe me, you do not
want to be on the wrong side
of those laser eyes.
You are worse than Leviathan.
Not worse.
Better.
- Mother.
Hate to say I told you so,
but it all went
according to plan.
Lena's back on my side,
Leviathan is set to
kill our enemies,
and I'm set
to wipe out Leviathan.
And...
I did it my way.
Ah, screw it.