Previously
onSupergirl...
The shrinking and collection
of worlds
is a common practice
among our ancestors.
William and I discovered
thatEve Tessmacher
has been working
for Obsidian.
If you're going to be
a vigilante,
maybe you should get
better at hiding.
What do you mean, like,
wear a mask?
I don't know who
this Brainy is.
But I know I don't trust him.
Andrea knows nothing.
Seems on this Earth,
post-Crisis, Leviathan
hasn't activated her yet.
Gemma Cooper
is warming to me.
And when she sees
my newest present,
she'll roll out the red carpet.
And if that means helping them
get a weapon or two, so be it.
You know what
this weapon is,
so you know what it needs.
Get it for me.
And this time, do not fail.
Regarding your request
to meet my colleagues,
I'll send you a car
tomorrow morning.
See you tomorrow.
I have made
a terrible mistake.
Lex is working with Leviathan,
and they are going
to use Obsidian to do
something terrible.
I want to help
stop them.
An elevator?
Seems a little pedestrian
for a goddess of technology.
Welcome to Leviathan.
You know...
I pride myself
on seeing things.
Connections where others
see only coincidence.
Pathways where others
see only walls.
I anticipate everything.
But I must admit,
I didn't not except you
to live in a casino.
After you.
One small step from that--
Lex Luthor.
The fabled man of tomorrow.
At least you have the decency
to bow before the gods.
I told you to disable
the shields.
As long as he knows
where we live it stays on.
At all times.
-On whose orders?
-Whose do you think?
-The ship's defense mechanism.
A proto-focused
radiation shield.
This pin will protect you.
Wow, you really know how to
make your guests feel welcome.
Well now the, uh...
...pleasantries are
out of the way,
don't you think we
should discuss our plan
to take out Supergirl
and her friends?
These rings
bought you a ticket to
board our ship.
So enjoy your photo op.
But leave the slaughter
of Supergirl to us.
Thank you for
letting me in, Kara.
It's been a year
and I still haven't come to
terms with what I did.
Shot my brother and...
I mean, I thought I was
protecting everyone
but it really started
all that--
I don't want to talk
about the past.
All that matters now is
the threat ahead of us and how
we are going to stop it.
Understood.
Get down on the ground, now.
No, Alex, no.
You texted 911.
Not about her.
She's here to help
us stop Lex.
And Leviathan.
Oh.
So Lex and Leviathan
are planning something
using Obsidian virtual
reality platform.
And my tech likely made
that possible.
That must be why
Rama Khan went after the
DEO's Kryptonite.
To keep Supergirl from
interfering.
Well, the joke's on Rama Khan
and his big dumb
gladiator outfit.
Because I have already
defeated him once.
Don't be rash, Kara.
He's tied to the Earth.
Which means he can track
your slightest movements.
If you use your powers
even once,
he will sense them,
and attack.
With all that
Kryptonite at his fingertips,
he could kill you.
You guys will protect me.
Just like we protected the DEO?
It's not checkmate.
Not yet.
I haven't made Kara
an anti-Kryptonite suit
in this world.
But I could.
Just need to get you
safely to my lab.
Your lab is across
the city.
And Kara can't use her powers.
We could get her there.
If we had the right
distraction.
Or the right decoys.
No, no, no way.
Absolutely not.
I can tell those pants
will chafe.
Ugh!
I was right.
I quite like it.
This is just like
the beginning
of Deathly Hallows.
Moody and Hedwig died.
You lost
comrades in battle?
My condolences.
No, it's...
Dreamer and
I will draw Rama Khan out in
Courtney Park.
M'gann, Alex,
you move across the rooftops
to cover us.
While they're distracting
Leviathan,
you and I will make our way
to LuthorCorp.
Come here.
I have to show you something.
Okay. Stay right there.
Oh, my God.
J'onn made it for me.
She looks great.
Oh, it was
a scream of delight.
Thank H'ronmeer.
Well, we should probably
get going.
Stay safe out there.
I know that may not
have been the most
pleasant experience.
But Rama Khan was just
trying to protect the base.
Not only Ram Khan, it seems.
And here I was thinking you
were the top of the food chain.
I answer to another.
Took me a long time
to gain her trust.
Which is why the Unity
Festival must succeed.
I'm yours.
Whatever you need.
Keep it.
You've earned it.
That's why I brought
you to the ship.
You're one of us now.
Today is the last day
of the old era.
Tomorrow the future begins.
Did you get
the ship's location?
Indeed.
But it has a nasty
defense mechanism.
They gave me something
to protect from it.
Give it to me.
Not yet.
We've come all this way...
We have done all
those terrible things,
so that I can sneak up
aboard the Leviathan ship
and upload the mortality
code, so that I can kill
the immortals.
And we shall.
But first, Rama Khan and his
element-bending goons
need to eliminate Supergirl's
friends one by one.
And when she
has nothing left...
they'll slay her, too.
After that you kill the gods.
You think I'm just
gonna sit back
while Leviathan murders
my friends?
Former friends.
And yes, I think you will.
Because if you get on
that ship any sooner,
you'll die with them.
Leviathan
is the enemy, Lex.
Not Supergirl,
not J'onn J'onzz.
-Not Dreamer.
-You're right.
They're heroes.
They would happily sacrifice
themselves to save the world.
Maybe they'll even thank us.
There's no place
I can't find you.
That's where you're wrong.
M'gann you're off the hook.
We've got Rama Khan.
Copy that.
We're on our way.
Wait.
There's someone else.
Another element bender.
Gotcha!
There's more than
one of us, too.
Kara, we got her.
Kara, come on, we've gotta go.
Dreamer.
Dreamer, what happened?
J'onn, no.
Go. Go, go, go.
The suit won't be ready for
at least another few hours.
But I'm doing everything in my
power to speed it along.
Hey.
What happened?
It's just not Rama Khan
out there.
There's three of them.
Each with different
element-bending power.
Where are the others?
J'onn was injured.
M'gann and Dreamer
are taken back to the tower.
I should have been there,
fighting alongside
you, I'm sorry.
Kara, it's okay.
We all still have our ears.
Kelly, hey.
Oh, thank God
I got you.
William texted me last night,
that he was going after
Eve Tessmacher.
I haven't been able to
reach him since.
William went after Eve alone?
No super-hearings.
-Sorry.
-Eve Tessmacher?
She's back?
Look, I'll get to you as
soon as I can.
Hey, if this Eve is
working with Lex,
William has no idea
the danger he is in.
I...
Alex, I have to do something.
I can't just sit here.
I have to help him,
-somehow.
-Okay, listen to me. Stop.
I know how hard it is for you
to sit on the sidelines.
Okay, but Kelly and I,
we will handle this.
We will access Eve's files
at Obsidian North
and we'll see what she's up to.
And if she has gotten
to William, hey.
We will find him.
You just need to stay safe
until Lena finishes your suit.
Okay, all right, fine.
But please, be careful.
You know me.
Yeah, exactly,
that's what I'm worried about.
Come on
Satellite uplink
is nearly ready.
We should launch.
Gemma?
I was communicating with her.
-The news isn't good.
-What is it?
Tezumak managed to
injure one of the Martians.
But Supergirl never even joined
the fight and the others
got away.
I've gambled everything on
this Unity Festival.
Then we have to make sure
it goes off without a hitch.
Lex, Gemma...
It's time.
So?
Shall we begin ending
the world?
Al's dive bar?
This is where you summoned
me at a time like this?
It's the place where you first
gave me this mission.
Work with Lex Luthor.
Defeat Leviathan.
No matter the cost.
Today I will feel the full
extent of that cost.
Querl.
I know things
spun out of control
last time you disobeyed Lex.
But you don't have to do this.
You don't have to let
your friends die.
I don't plan to.
I don't plan on using Lex's
mortality code on the gods,
either.
But how will you defeat them?
By using this.
Rather than kill the gods.
And I shall reclaim
the actions of our ancestors.
For good.
Instead of evil.
I'll shrink them.
I'll bottle them
here in stasis,
where they can harm neither
this planet nor my friends.
But if you enter the ship
without Lex's
anti-radiation pin, you'll...
You'll... You'll die.
I pushed away everyone I loved
because you told me I must.
You were right.
This planet...
my friends...
It's worth it.
I called you here
simply because...
I don't wanna die alone.
Citizens of the world.
Today we stand on the
precipice of history.
Ours is a world of pain,
suffering.
Of conflict, of chaos.
But when you enter
Obsidian's world...
The problems of the real
one melt away.
In virtual reality, there is
nothing to want.
No reason to harm one another.
It's a place where we can be
our best and truest selves.
This world can be
our real world.
And it all starts today.
With the Obsidian
Worldwide Unity Festival.
Oh, nice.
Did someone call for
tech support?
I just said a mask, but...
Wow.
Bummer we have to get to
straight to business.
Yeah, I guess you inspired me.
I could have never
gotten past security.
My girlfriend's a badass.
Breaking into a tech
corps, that's easy.
What I battled earlier today...
These are gods.
I mean, I finally got
this baby working.
But compared to what those
guys are packing...
I might as well have brought
a slingshot.
I've never felt so human.
Oh, wait, wait,
we got something.
Eve's IP address.
-Okay.
-Wait.
It's encrypted.
Better call Lena.
These programs should
be able to crack Eve's cipher
in minutes.
Talk about history
repeating itself.
Tracking Lex down
through Eve...
It's just like Kaznia.
Please, Kara, I'm sorry.
Okay, I truly believed what I
was doing was helping people.
I told you I don't want
to talk about the past.
Oh, come on, you can scream
at me if you'd like.
I know I deserve it.
I know now that working
with Non Nocere was a mistake,
that working with Lex--
This isn't about Lex.
This is about J'onn and Alex
and all the other people that
could have been killed today
because they are on my team.
Don't you understand that?
No, I do, of course I do.
No you don't.
You have never understood
what it means share a secret
identity with someone.
How much danger
that puts them in.
You... You never
even understood
that I kept my identity
from you because I wanted
to protect you.
I know, I know
that I hurt you
by waiting so long
to tell my truth.
But what about all
the ways you hurt me?
You pretended to be my
friend for weeks.
Just so you could
manipulate me.
You stole from me.
You convinced me to
steal for you.
And then, then, you even...
You used Kryptonite on me.
I made one mistake.
One mistake
that was only ever meant
to protect you.
And in return,
all you did was hurt me
in every way imaginable.
I'm sorry.
I know you are.
But if you came to me looking
for absolution,
I can't give it to you.
It's Eve's location.
I'm going.
No, Kara, your suit
isn't ready yet.
I don't care.
Protecting people is what I do.
You should know that by now.
Then I'm going with you.
Now that you're up,
you better start talking.
Why were you following me?
I'm pursuing a story
on Lex Luthor.
I know he is up to something
criminal.
I don't know your
involvement.
But I believe you've been
working for him.
You have no idea what
you have gotten yourself into.
You should have
stayed out of it.
Now I have no choice.
I'm a journalist.
Okay, I can read people.
You're a good person who
looks trapped.
It's clear you're not
a killer.
What does he have with you?
Did he threaten someone
you care about?
My mother.
I am so sorry.
But you don't have
to fight this alone.
I can help you
and your mother.
We can bring
the truth to light.
If the truth comes to light,
my mother is dead.
Eve, please.
I really am so sorry.
It's okay. I've got you.
Okay. The bullet went
through and through
through but we still need to
get you to a hospital.
No, no, no,
he's losing to much blood.
There's no time.
Okay.
I can cauterize it but it's
gonna hurt.
-Do it, do it.
-All right.
Don't do it.
Too late, too late. It's done.
-You okay?
Yes, it just hurt.
All right,
what happened here?
I was following a lead.
Got jumped.
Ah, Reporting 101.
If you get kidnapped,
you must be on the right track.
-Something Kara Danvers
likes to say.
She was working the case
with me.
I need to make sure
she is all right.
Kara is fine.
I spoke to her,
she's in a safe place.
Get William and Eve
out of here.
I'll deal with this.
Are you mad?
They've got Kryptonite.
Well, then you'd better get
that suit here fast.
It's already on its way.
And I'll call for back-up.
Kill her.
Did someone call
for backup?
Now it's a fair fight.
Couldn't let you have
all the fun.
Can't believe you
left to play earth, wind and
fire without us.
They're...
They're gone.
The explosion killed them.
We have to get out of here.
Now.
Let's replenish ourselves and
finish this once and for all.
That's when their bodies
started to reform like
out of a horror movie.
Yeah, but that means...
They're indestructible.
Immortal.
This isn't about defeating
them anymore.
They want us to fight
until we drop.
So they can distract us from
whatever Lex is planning.
Do we even know what that is?
I'm gonna go find out.
Eve.
Eve, can you hear me?
-Is the reporter okay?
-Yes.
He told us everything.
Please understand...
I was just trying to protect
my mom.
Now Lex is gonna kill her.
I know you must feel
like there is no way out.
But it is when things feel
their most hopeless
that we have to dig down deep
to do what is right.
Otherwise the bad guys win.
Help us, Eve.
Help us fight.
And I promise I will do
everything in my power to keep
you and your mom safe.
Gemma Cooper is not
who she says she is.
Her real name is Gamemnae.
She is a member of Leviathan,
just like Rama Khan.
Tonight they are planning
to attack the Unity Festival.
Once all four million
subscribers are inside...
Gemma will kill them all.
I recommend the chocos.
How's J'onn?
Recovering.
You can't fool a sidekick.
I saw you hesitate
during the fight.
You dreamed something.
And it terrified you.
What did you see?
Brainy.
You two were couple, right?
You know J'onn.
For a deeply serious man,
he's got a big mouth.
I know.
It was more than
a relationship.
We were partners.
We...
protected each other.
Turns out that one thing I
couldn't protect him from
was himself.
I told him to take
off those inhibitors.
Maybe these dreams
are because of my guilt.
There may be more to what he's
going through than you know.
When J'onn discovered
that I was a White Martian.
He thought the worst of me.
Until he finally saw my soul.
I'm not a telepath.
No, you're a dreamer.
And like it or not,
you're dreaming now.
You have to engage with it.
It could have meaning
far deeper
than you realize.
I'm sorry M'gann, I need to be
keeping Brainy out of my mind,
not letting him in.
There is nearly
a billion people logged into
the Unity Fest already.
Can we shut down
the system?
Or destroy it somehow?
No.
The Luthor power core
has an indestructible
fail safe.
So, you're saying
we need to convince potentially
billions of people
to log out of virtual
reality paradise of their
own free will.
Hope you've got one of those
classic hope speeches handy.
I mean, I've done it before
but never on this level.
Oh, if anyone can do it,
it's you.
Jinx.
All right, so what do we
do about Leviathan?
We'll fight till
our last breath.
J'onn, are you sure?
With you by my side, 100%.
Well, we'll need
to do something to drive
Leviathan out.
I'll send them a message.
-What are you going to say?
-Something to get
their attention.
That arrogant Martian thinks
he can speak to me like that?
I'm a god!
Once we're done with
this world, I'll turn to
Mars next.
Now's your chance.
Place your hand on
the central terminal.
You'll be able to upload
the shrink code.
Now you can't
move your hand or else you
have to start over.
The upload will take
ten minutes.
I don't know if I can
last that long.
You can.
I'll be with you
the whole way.
Kelly opened
the back door
into the festival.
It should help protect you
from the kill switch.
Hopefully we get everyone out
before Lex and Gemma hit it.
You will.
Let's do this.
Wow.
This is amazing.
I've never seen
anything like this.
No wonder so many people
signed up.
There's still no
sign of them.
Guess they didn't
take the bait.
Maybe you should have
been meaner.
Ah...
-No.
I was just mean enough.
What? No Supergirl?
Let's see if we can't
convince her to join us.
- What's wrong?
-Supergirl.
She's inside
the Unity Festival.
We need to hit
the kill switch.
Wipe out as many people
as possible.
before she has a chance
to interfere.
There aren't any enough
people logged in yet.
We need to get 50% saturation.
What good is wiping out
one quarter of the world
if the other three quarters
rise up against us.
We'll worry about that
problem tomorrow.
This is about tomorrow.
You told me you answer
to a higher power.
How will she feel
when you give in on
the mission before
it's complete?
And if Supergirl is in
the Unity festival,
then her physical body
is vulnerable.
Rama Khan, Tezumak and Sela
might be able to
make it back in time.
They need to take out
Supergirl's friends.
Then what do you propose?
Send another assassin.
Someone who won't fail you.
Hi.
We are nearing
two billion simultaneous users.
Our dreams are finally
a reality.
Not just our dreams, Andrea.
Your father's.
Hm.
And Leviathan's.
Leviathan?
How do you know that name?
Because I am Leviathan.
What does that mean?
All I know is that Leviathan
rescued me that day
in the cave.
It was I who rescued you.
And I have been looking
out for you every day since.
But now I need your help.
Yes.
Yes, of course, anything.
There is great power in you.
I know you feel it.
The power of shadows.
I need you to use that power...
to kill Supergirl.
What?
No. I don't...
I can't.
Yes, you can.
And when you do,
you'll have power beyond
your wildest dreams.
And your company
will be untouchable.
If you don't,
your company will collapse.
You will lose everything.
Your father will be crushed.
We both know he won't be
able to survive the blow.
Everyone listen to me.
There is something wrong
with the program.
You need to end
the simulation now.
What are you
talking about?
There is no one in here but
my late husband.
It's so good to hear his voice.
Hey. Hey, kid.
Kid, can you hear me?
You need to disengage
from the program.
Leave me alone.
My mom is back.
I missed her.
It's...
It's not working.
There are too many people,
they feel connected to their
loved ones.
It's spiritual.
I have no idea how to
break through to them.
I think I can give you a way
to talk to everyone at once.
-Try now.
I need
you all to listen to me.
You're in danger.
If you and I fan out to the
side we can draw their fire.
While you two attack
through the middle.
-Sound good?
-Why not?
-You ready?
-Nope.
Me neither.
Let's go.
Five more minutes.
Stay focused.
Andrea.
The medallion.
You've been activated.
If I don't kill Supergirl,
they'll kill my father.
I know it can be addictive,
to live in a perfect place
where nothing hurts.
But that's not reality.
Killing for them...
Going down this path,
it won't keep him safe.
How do you know?
Because I've been down
it before.
We all get hurt.
But it's only by going
through that pain
that we're able to appreciate
the good.
Pain is what helps us grow.
Without it, we'd never
be able to...
To evolve, to overcome.
To forgive.
I have done terrible things
to protect myself and
the people I love.
But it has never kept
me safe from pain.
It's just brought me
a new kind of misery.
And I moved further
and further
away from the person
I was, until one day
I woke up
and I was utterly alone.
Each of us came here
because we are afraid.
I'm afraid of getting hurt,
just like you.
And I do everything I can
to escape pain, just like you.
But the cost of escape
is too great.
Years ago...
we made a promise
to each other.
You jump, I jump.
If you choose to go down
this path...
I will be there.
If you want to get
to Supergirl,
you're gonna have to
go through me.
We have to wake up now.
We need to end the simulation
once and for all.
I believe in you.
Hey, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
End simulation.
Go...
on...
I had hoped
you'd die screaming.
But I'll take what I can get.
What have you done?
I...
beat...
you.
What's happening?
The Coluan.
I never thought
I'd see the day.
Obsidian Platinum,
the most popular
VR platform ever created.
And not a single person
is using it.
Alex called...
Leviathan has disappeared.
You did what you
said you would.
Almost.
I still have one promise
left to keep.
You did it, Querl.
You did it.
You saved this world.
You saved your friends.
Will you...
...stay with me?
Till the very end.
Nia.
Who do you think you are?
We had a plan.
Leviathan kills Supergirl
and you kill Leviathan.
And together we
save this planet
from the invulnerable aliens,
who think they know
what's best for mankind.
Why couldn't you just wait
for Supergirl to die?
Underestimated me.
My friends.
I'd never let you kill them.
No, Braniac 5.
Uh, I underestimate nothing.
I knew you would decide to
shrink the gods
instead of kill them
due to your precious
moral code.
I planned for that.
I just didn't think that
you would kill yourself.
Well...
Supergirl lives.
But, I have the ball.
No...
You gave me exactly...
what I needed.
I'm just gonna kill
Supergirl myself.
It'll be fun.
And you...
can die alone.
Just like you intended.
No, no, no, Brainy.
I should have listened to you.
It's Brainy.
He stopped Leviathan.
He saved us.
He needs my help.
Oh...
Oh, my God.
It's actually you.
In the last world,
she betrayed us.
We may never know what
was driving her, but...
I do know what was
driving you.
You didn't want to tell me
who you really were
because you didn't want
me to get hurt.
But I did get hurt.
And I did what I always do
when people hurt me.
I...
built a wall and I suffocated
behind it.
Makes it very difficult to
see things from other people's
point of view.
But I see yours now.
And I am very sorry it
took me so long.
You know, when you showed
up at my door this morning I...
I didn't wanna let you in.
And I kept waiting for
you to let me down.
But at every turn you
came through.
Building that suit.
Protecting my identity,
supporting me.
I wasn't ready to accept
your apology.
But maybe,
maybe I am now.
Okay.
What now?
Well, there is one bad guy
left to catch.
Let's go take
my brother down.
Let's get to work, Doc.
Right away, dear.