In the beginning,
there was only one.
A single black infinitude.
Then the infinitude
found release,
and, finally,
the darkness broke,
filling it with life...
With the multi-verse.
Every existence multiplied
by possibility.
And spread out before
space and time
in infinite measure.
Civilizations rose and fell.
And rose again across
reality's grasping expanse.
Life. A precious gift
persevering in the face
of every obstacle,
until, finally, the age
of heroes was born.
Chaos. The constant
enemy of life
kept at bay by champions from across the multi-verse...
...joining forces to fight
on behalf of all creation.
They found each other
just in time,
because now,
the entire multi-verse is about to come under attack.
There is a malevolent force
at work,
one driven by a singular goal.
I hope you're watching,
big guy.
The destruction
of all there is.
I have planned,
there are those who say
I have schemed,
but the time for preparation
has passed.
The Crisis is now upon us all.
Holy crimson skies of death!
The end of the world
is licking at our heels!
Soon, thou shall be not
but dust,
twisting and writhing
in the dead of space!
-Not even Supergirl
will save you from...
Guess Supergirl was able
to save you.
Now, go! Run!
Hey, Spike! Remember me?
Ilana's worried about you.
She knows you're afraid
of something,
-but she just wants you
to come home.
Come here.
What's got
you so spooked, buddy?
Every pet in National City
is having a nervous breakdown.
This feels bigger
than Leviathan.
The USGS didn't register
an early warning,
-so it took everyone
completely by surprise.
She does mean everyone
because this earthquake
is quite, literally, worldwide.
But the seismic activity wasn't
coming from within the planet,
it's coming from without.
-That's--
-Extra-normal.
I was gonna say "impossible,"
but okay.
Yes, yes, a fair descriptor.
As would be, uh...
"unfeasible, unthinkable,
absurd, outlandish."
But however you choose
to describe this event,
one thing
is absolutely certain.
-We have--
-A major crisis on our hands.
The Monitor freed Mal?
I didn't know he was
of this universe.
Yes, I thought the Monitor
was a Flash and Green Arrow's
problem.
He's of every universe
and everyone's problem.
Last year, he tested Kara
and Earth-1's heroes
with Dr. Deegan
and the Book of Destiny.
This year, he's testing me
to make sure
I'm ready for this.
And what exactly is this?
-Another reality wave?
-Not exactly.
Whatever is it, it is
hurtling through space
at an impossible speed.
I calculate it will reach
the edge of the universe
in exactly 5.3 hours,
at which point,
it will boomerang back.
Once it intersects again
with our solar system,
the results will be,
in a word, cataclysmic.
Exactly when will it reach us?
There are too many variables
to calculate precisely,
but I will say this.
If this wave isn't stopped
by tomorrow night...
there will be no more us...
no more future...
no more anything.
Are there any
inhabited planets
in its trajectory?
-Just one.
Argo City.
-Oh, my God. Superman's there
with Lois and...
-My mom.
Can we warn them?
Argo Harun-El sure makes
communication difficult,
but I will try.
-How much time
do they have, Brainy?
-Not enough.
Superman,
champion of Earth,
who faced off with Doomsday,
apprehended General Zod,
and went toe-to-toe
with dozens of Lex Luthor's
death traps,
has finally met his match.
-A dirty diaper.
What do you think?
Front page news?
Uh... I mean, I think
it's a little lowbrow
-for Lois Lane.
-Lowbrow?
If only the citizens of Earth
could see Kal-El
struggling with spit up.
Need I remind you, Miss Lane,
uh, I have no powers here.
Oh, don't you be blaming this
on the red sun, honey.
Hey, buddy.
-Yay, Daddy did it.
-Yeah, kinda.
Jonathan really
has your eyes, huh?
I'll take it...
so long he has
your everything else.
You know, when I used
to picture us together,
we were always
living on Earth,
and we had two kids.
Well, I hate to break it
to you, Kansas,
but prognostication
is not one of your superpowers.
Oh...
Kal, Lois...
Kara? In pants?
How did she manage
to break through
Argo's shield interference?
Not well, apparently.
Kal, Lois... Argo is in danger.
You need to get out now!
Alura!
Kal, Lois, thank God.
What's happening?
A massive energy
is moving through space.
It's killing everything
in its path.
-How long do we have?
-Minutes!
Quickly! With me!
We must set a course for Earth.
Hopefully, they'll have
enough time
to stop this wave
before it hits.
- Where are the rest?
There are no others.
Only this one.
We'll always
be with you, Jonathan.
We will never leave you.
Even in the face of our deaths.
We love you.
They're gone.
And we're next.
For a very long time,
I have hated this place.
I think about all the people
that it took from me.
It would just...
It would just make me
so angry.
But you're not now.
I'm still a little bit angry.
This island taught me
to survive.
It turned me into someone else.
Somebody better than
the person I was before.
So, despite my feelings...
there are no stories
about the Green Arrow to tell
if I don't make my way
to Lian Yu.
And I'm also not standing,
at this moment...
looking at my daughter.
Thank you for letting me
be a part of your story.
Even if it was only
for a little while.
Yeah, something tells me
you're gonna create
your own stories.
Lyla.
The Crisis has begun.
Cisco,
what have you got?
Is this an isolated event?
Is it everywhere?
-Cisco?
Iris!
-Lyla?
-I'm Harbinger now.
I'm working with the Monitor.
He sent you to get me?
-Because the Crisis is here?
-That is correct.
I'm ready.
Turning our
attention to local news,
a series of robberies
by the Wonderland Gang
continues
with seemingly no end
in sight...
Where is Alice?
-I said, "Where is Alice?"
Okay... okay, I'll tell you.
-There's an old sugar factory.
-Where is it?
Batwoman, the multi-verse
is in great danger.
You are needed.
I'll deal with,
whatever your crazy is,
in a minute.
There is no more time.
Okay, folks, time for
our tie-breaker question
of the night. Here we go.
What is the name
of the last song
Janis Joplin ever recorded?
Ready for some free drinks?
And the answer to our final
bonus question is...
"Little Robot Man."
The strange visitors
are the winners tonight.
Better luck next time, legends.
Uh, no, that's wrong.
But "Mercedes Benz"
was Janis Joplin's last song.
I'm gonna tell
that trivia host.
Sara.
So, you remember
last year at Woodstock
when I was supposed to steal
a lock of Janis Joplin's hair
without her noticing?
-Yeah?
-Uh, she noticed.
-Then she called me--
-"Little Robot Man."
Well, congratulations,
you change history
and lost us trivia night.
Oh, and we're done here.
Lyla? What's with the suit?
Panic is rising out there.
I want every available agent
in the field
until we get a handle
on whatever this thing is.
Hey! Face down
on the floor. Now!
Did you do this?
Did you destroy Argo?
Oh, my God, you're okay.
Thanks to her. She appeared
at the last second
and brought us here.
We sent Jonathan off
in an escape pod.
And my mother?
I'm so sorry, Kara.
Kara?
Where are we?
And what just happened?
-Um--
-You're on Earth-38.
-There was--
That rabbit was about to talk.
This one speaks to rabbits.
It's okay. 'Cause we're all
on the same side.
Are we?
'Cause I don't know them.
But you know me.
And if you were brought here
with all these other heroes,
it's probably because
we need you.
I trust everyone
in this room
with my life.
Including you.
Well, I guess you should all
just call me Kate.
Yeah, yeah, that makes
a lot of sense.
Uh, I'm Mia.
I'm Oliver's daughter.
I never knew he had a daughter.
He gets that a lot.
Hmm...
Okay, you. Start talking.
There's a wave
of anti-matter sweeping
across this universe,
destroying everything
in its path.
I've seen the anti-matter wave
in action.
It wiped all of Earth-2
right out of existence.
I brought you all
to Earth-38 because
this is where
the Monitor wants you
to make your stand.
This universe
is the tipping point.
If we don't stop
the anti-matter wave here,
it will continue
to the next universe,
and the next, and the next.
Until it has obliterated,
not only every Earth,
but every thing...
across all reality.
Right. So, we are going to
need a bigger team.
Where's Barry?
Where are the legends?
Doing reconnaissance.
I'm headed
to check on them now.
I still don't like her.
Well, Brainy's algorithm
will help forecast
exactly how much time we have
until the anti-matter wave
hits.
Thank you all for being here.
I know we can
beat this together.
About Jonathan...
we set a course for Earth
in his pod, but we don't know
where it landed.
Or even if it landed.
Brainy, can you track
his trajectory?
Absolutely.
We'll find that bouncing bundle
of Kryptonian joy
-faster than
a flying Flackurian--
This is a new problem.
I can handle it.
Wait, the tower
isn't a threat.
How do you know?
It's a quantum tower,
apparently.
And it's the only thing
that can save the people
of this world.
At the dawn of time,
the Monitor placed
quantum towers
on key Earths
as a last line of defense.
The red skies are dissipating,
which means it's working.
From this design,
it looks like
the tower is capable
of generating
a quantum flux field,
-which can, theoretically--
-Reverse the exogenic state
of the anti-matter wave,
thereby dissipating
the anti-matter energy.
Yes. Finally, someone
who speaks my language.
Love your suit.
If you want, I can probably
give it an upgrade.
Depends on how attached you are
to your hand.
Pretty attached.
So the tower can stop
this Earth from
being destroyed?
If you can protect it.
-Protect it from what?
-The Anti-Monitor.
He commands forces
greater than any army.
When the tower stops the wave,
they will come to thwart
any effort to save this planet
and its people.
Sprock!
Jonathan's pod
has disappeared
from our radar.
It appears to have been
sucked into a wormhole.
-What are the co-ordinates?
-Star City. Earth-16.
Interesting.
It must've been
a temporal wormhole because...
well, the pod
is in the year 2046.
We've been there before.
Apparently, we didn't
just travel to the future.
Yeah, we traveled
to a parallel Earth
in the future. That's great.
-I'm going after him.
-Clark, you can't.
Those are two words
I'm not used to hearing
and my son needs me.
I'm a parent and I get it.
The entire universe needs you.
When that tower gets attacked,
you have to be here
to protect it.
I'll go.
Lois...
I'll back you up.
-I know the terrain.
- As will I.
I happen to be excellent
with children.
Don't worry, I'll get him.
I love you.
You know, Oliver...
I've seen playboy Oliver,
vigilante Oliver,
but I never thought
I would see parent Oliver.
-It's weird, right?
-So weird.
But... it looks good on you.
Uh, J'onn, I thought
Director Danvers was with you.
She was.
But she went to call
the president to co-ordinate
the evacuation,
in case
the quantum tower fails.
She is smart, that is exactly
what I was about to suggest,
but has she contemplated
the number of ships
one would require
for such an exodus?
Brainy, every alien refugee
on this planet came here
on a ship.
I intend to ask them
for their help.
Do you really think they will?
After how the government
treated them last year.
I have faith that...
everybody will do
the right thing.
Humans and aliens alike.
Well, in any event...
this should help.
Oh, Sprock.
I just managed
to zero in on Jonathan's
location in Star City.
The president is in.
He's speaking
with other world leaders.
We'll co-ordinate
the effort from National City.
But J'onn...
even if we did manage
to get enough ships
for everyone,
we can't just fly off Earth.
I mean, space itself
is being erased.
Earth-1 is the last stop
on the anti-matter trajectory.
We can try
and get everybody there.
Well, one little extrapolator
is not gonna do the job.
The transmatter portal?
Who could build one big enough?
I mean, not even Brainy has.
Lena.
She built an enormous one
for the daxamites.
-I'm sure she could
build one twice as big.
-No, that's too big of a risk.
I mean, after Myriad,
after everything...
she can't be trusted.
What other choice do we have?
I'm sorry about your mom.
I couldn't save her.
You had no powers on Argo.
There was nothing you could do.
I feel like a fool.
I thought I could
give up the cape and just...
have everything
I ever wanted.
And now, Argo is gone,
this Earth is in danger,
Lois and Jonathan
are out in the universe,
where I can't protect them.
And part of me can't help
thinking that...
that I deserve this...
for thinking that
I could have so much.
That anyone could.
I get it.
I've been thinking that
a lot, too, lately.
How I can never do enough.
How my mistakes outweigh
all the good I've ever done.
But it's not true.
It can't be.
And we're going to save them.
Lois, Jonathan,
this whole planet.
We've done it a dozen times
and we're going to do it again.
How are you so...
hopeful right now?
You've lost
just as much as I have today.
Argo, your mom...
Before our parents
sent us to Earth...
nobody here knew
about Krypton.
Now, there are stories,
celebrations,
museum exhibits.
Just like you shared
our home with your family,
we shared our home
with this whole world.
Krypton's not just a place,
it's a spirit.
It's hope. It's sacrifice.
It's what our parents
did for us.
What you did for Jonathan.
We have made our parents proud
by fighting for what's right.
So, we have to keep fighting.
And as long as
that spirit is alive,
Krypton will never die.
-You wanted to see me?
-I did.
I have something for you.
What is it?
Only one way to find out.
Okay, please tell me
you're planning on
wearing this.
I don't think that
that one would fit me.
There should always be
at least one Green Arrow.
Dad, I can't.
You know, Mia, the Monitor
has taken a lot from me.
But I will always
be grateful for the time
he has given me with you.
If you're not gonna wear this,
no one should.
You earned it.
Just try it on, okay?
I gotta find Barry.
The fastest man alive
shows up late to the Crisis
we've been expecting for years.
-Ugh...
-It's not the...
it's not the best look, Barry.
Lyla had us doing some recon
of the quantum towers.
But listen, do you remember
the newspaper article
I showed you on the time vault?
Red skies and a "crisis"?
Okay, well, the Monitor
confirmed the papers
had lied and...
in this Crisis,
I'm supposed to die.
-No.
-No?
We need to talk. Now!
Who're you talking to?
Hey, right now!
We are past the time
for discussion, Oliver.
You and I had an agreement.
I die.
Barry and Kara live!
Yes... to keep
the cosmic balance.
So, why are you telling Barry
that he's gonna die?
I spared your friends' lives
so they could save
their world last year.
This... is a very
different threat.
You need to
stop playing games with me.
You tell me
why the Anti-Monitor
is doing this.
And then tell me
how I'm going to prevent it.
Not knowing
what you're fighting means
you will prepare
for every possibility.
Because this threat
brings with it
the annihilation of all life
in all realities.
Do you now comprehend
the scope...
of the danger we all now face?
Are you here to arrest me
during the apocalypse,
or to try and kill me
because you weren't successful
the other day?
I wasn't trying
to hurt you, Lena.
I was trying to stop you
from using Myriad.
Right. Is that why you had
a Claymore satellite
aimed at me?
And I didn't use Myriad,
that was Eve Tessmacher.
You and I both know
that that isn't true.
The reason the sky is red,
and the planet feels like
it's falling apart
is because it is.
There is an anti-matter wave
that is tearing through
the universe right now,
and it will destroy Earth
if Kara and the other heroes
don't stop it.
Now, I am working with J'onn
to hedge our bets
and mount an evacuation,
but in order to do that...
we need your help.
Look, I am sorry
that I lied to you.
And not just me,
and not just Kara...
it was all of us.
J'onn and Brainy and Nia.
You know, you actually
had me believe
that you hated Supergirl.
I wasn't pretending about that.
And that is a... long story.
Listen, I-- I know
that you feel burned by us.
And that there is nothing
that I can say
in this moment
that is going to change that.
But if you could please
just put your feelings aside,
J'onn and I really, really,
need your help.
I don't want
your apology, Alex.
'Cause you will never again
have my friendship or my trust.
I have learned my lesson
from all of you.
But if the world is at stake,
then of course, I'll help.
It is hubris of you
to think that I wouldn't,
but then, you've made it
perfectly clear
how little you've thought of me
these last few years, so...
what do you need me to do?
Whatever
is inside there,
it's working.
The anti-matter wave
has stopped
and it's slowly dissipating.
How do we protect that thing
from an enemy we know
nothing about,
but we know is coming?
We head inside...
stake out strategic positions.
If we're fortified,
we control the battle.
Earthquake that magnitude
could overwhelm
the entire coast.
Go. Help contain the damage.
Go! We got this.
Let's go inside and dig in.
You've gotta be
kidding me.
What are the odds
that my son's pod landed here?
Three billion, eight hundred
and twenty seven million
to one.
Uh... but the pod
didn't land here.
But you said that
this is where Jonathan is.
Yes. This is where
I tracked him.
But I can't speculate
as to why Oliver Queen
would kidnap a baby.
Well, he probably thought
he was rescuing him.
I mean, Star City is no place
for a child.
Well, I'll thank him
when I have Jonathan back.
-In the meantime,
we should split up--
This is unnecessary.
Oliver?
Oliver.
Jonathan!
Yes. Yes, you go get Jonathan.
I'll...
I'll stay here,
What? No.
No, it's not possible.
You're dead.
You...
you went down with the Gambit.
But I came back. Remember?
I found you in Lian Yu.
I must be losing my mind.
-No, Ollie, you're not--
-Hey.
You're not. You're...
It's just a long story.
The longest.
Thank you, Oliver.
Thank you for helping my baby.
So, what is this?
The proverbial calm
before the storm?
Something like that.
Remember, Mia,
whatever happens...
find your mother.
Tell her how much I love her.
Okay.
When Lyla said an army,
I thought
she meant an... army.
She did. It's just that...
we've never faced
one like this before.
"One army." She said,
"One army." It's more like ten!
-Very nice.
-Learned from the best.
-Take cover!
They're trying
to breach the tower.
Well, we can't let that happen!
I'll take that upgrade now.
Oh, uh, if I can have
one of those without
losing an appendage.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Oh, so cool!
Incredibly balanced.
Carbon fiber?
-Your friend talks a lot.
-Yeah, you get used to it.
Hey, Ray, focus!
Focusing.
Now, if we can just charge
your Batarang with
my compressed light energy.
Incoming!
Not bad.
Dad!
There's too many of them.
You want some help?
There's no need for panic.
Supergirl and Superman
are working hard
to save this planet.
Soon, alien ships will begin
circling the globe,
picking people up
and taking you to safety.
-Hey.
Did Alex get Lena on board?
Yeah, they're working on
the portal now.
I just hope
J'onn can get enough ships.
There are literally
billions of people
to get off the planet.
That's why Brainy left J'onn
his keys.
Keys to what?
The Legion left it here.
Right on time, J'onn.
Are you ready
to get this evacuation
underway?
Start getting people
into groups and I'll start
beaming them up.
Let's just hope Alex and Lena
get that portal on in time
so we have somewhere to go.
-Go ahead. This way.
-All right, people,
let's get in to the ship.
The quantum tower
is keeping the wave at bay.
Supergirl is...
fighting really hard
to protect it,
but we've got to get
this portal up and running.
I'm trying!
But the transmatter portal
works by synthesizing
polyelectronic anions.
And if I don't get
the energy levels right
when I interface
with the breach device,
then the ships
will disintegrate
when they fly right through it.
-Right. That is not
a good option.
-No.
Have you thought about
using an inverse variable
to help calculate
the differential?
Galleon's theory.
That's smart.
An inverse beta-decay
to figure constituent quark,
that could work.
Thanks.
Yeah, um... just...
keep working.
I've got your back.
I never thought
I'd see you again.
One of the benefits
of parallel Earths.
Parallel Earths?
It would appear that
your reality is a little...
stranger than mine.
You really have no idea.
All my life...
I just wanted to...
to apologize
for bringing you
on that boat.
But you aren't even you.
Ollie.
If your me was anything
like I was,
then getting on the Gambit
with you was her choice.
And in my world, that trip...
it set off
a whole series of events
that neither you or I
could've ever dreamed of.
You became a hero,
a husband, a father.
And I'm flying through time
happier than I've ever been.
And none of that
would've ever happened
if I didn't get on
that boat with you.
It was destiny.
I'm... sorry to break up
what I'm sure must be
the strangest reunion
in the history of the world,
but, um,
if we don't leave now,
I'm afraid our extrapolator
might not have enough power
for us to return home.
Wait, what's an extrapolator?
It's another long story.
You're a good man...
on every Earth.
-Is that it?
-Like that was easy?
They're on the roof.
What's happening out there?
The skies are red again, the anti-matter wave's moving,
and the portal isn't open yet.
-There's more
shadow demons incoming.
Kara, Clark, get to the roof.
Get the tower operational
again. We'll stay behind
and hold them off.
Are those solar panels?
Looks close enough.
We won't be able
to power it definitely.
We just need to buy more time.
We might lose
the planet, but we can
still save the people.
You almost got it?
Almost done, I think.
Yes! Systems are a go.
Calculating destination...
destination set.
Smart call
with Galleon's theory.
Oh, lucky guess. But you're
the real genius here, so...
Don't mistake us
working together
for friendship.
I told you before,
Kara and you showed me
who you were and I accept that.
Now, let's go help people
get on these ships.
-That was too close
for comfort.
Always gotta one-up me, huh?
-Did it work?
-You did it.
The tower is working again
and the portal is open.
Uh, but the ships
better be fast.
The Supers' charge didn't
actually stop the wave,
it just slowed it down.
According to
Brainy's algorithm,
we have 14 minutes
before it makes contact
with Earth.
Well, then
we better make
every minute count.
We've got your back.
We need to keep those
shadow demons at bay until
every last ship gets through--
All right, get to the ships!
Keep your eyes open
for debris, people!
Keep it orderly, people.
Come on.
James left it for me.
The battle is lost!
We must retreat
and save our resources
for battles yet to come.
Oliver! Oli--
Oliver! It is time!
Has the planet been
evacuated yet?
Not entirely.
Then it's not time.
Oliver.
He fought to his last breath.
Knowing every moment
was another life saved.
-Saved?
-Your universe is no more.
Of 7.53 billion...
three billion souls
made it to Earth-1
on the armada of ships.
I calculate one billion souls
survived due to
his noble sacrifice.
Nash?
Once upon a time.
Not anymore.
Now, I'm simply a man
serving his penance.
Penance for what?
I freed the Anti-Monitor
from his confinement only...
to become a... Pariah.
Sentenced to bear witness
to his actions.
Oliver!
It's okay, Sara.
This is my destiny.
-Oliver.
-Barry?
You, my friend...
are the very best of us.
I gave it all up...
for you and Kara.
What-- What do you mean?
I need the two of you to...
be the one to...
to save us now.
Mia...
Dad.
Don't forget
to find your mother.
Okay.
Find William.
Tell him how much I love him.
I love you, Mia.
You keep me
in your heart, okay?
-Dad...
-Okay?
It was
not supposed to be like this.
This is not his ending
I foresaw.
Things are turning out
differently than I expected.
But one thing is certain.
Everything we know...
everything there is...
and everything
there ever was...
is doomed.