Foul beast.
Plague of my family.
Today your life ends.
End simulation.
These new Obsidian Platinum
lenses are amazing!
Well, Kelly said the upgrade
is so realistic that people
can actually touch and taste
and smell things in the VR.
I mean, look at that guy.
He's actually feeling like
he's going that fast.
He must be fearless.
That would make
even me dizzy.
Oh, hardly.
But fearless
is definitely something
I wish I was feeling,
'cause right now,
being out in this crowd,
I don't like it
without my sidearm.
I can't believe Lex
made you give up your gun
when you left the DEO.
This is the first time
in eight years I've been
out without it.
You know what? I love it.
You and J'onn, The Tower,
without bureaucracy.
Without an evil overlord
holding you back.
I think it's great.
-Hi.
-Hi. Oh, my gosh!
-Look at this place.
It's amazing!
-It's all Andrea.
Well, okay, sure. Maybe
the pizzazz part, but I mean,
not the upgraded 150
petaflop bio-link interface.
She has never said
words like that.
Oh, you are paying attention
to my late night ramblings.
-I do listen. Yes.
-More importantly,
what's in the box?
This is a first day gift
for my awesome girlfriend.
Hot pockets,
macaroni and cheese
and your favorite
dumplings from Wang Foo's.
-Dumplings?
-Oh, no. Hey. Uh-uh.
This is comfort food for me.
-I might share with J'onn.
Maybe. If he asks.
-What?
-I've been listen...
-Um, don't look now
but the co-worker you rejected
is coming this way.
-Don't look now.
-Oh.
-Oh. You should do your thing.
-I gotta go to The Tower.
-We have a thing
that we have to do.
-Traitors. Traitors!
-Hi!
-Morning!
Hello.
-I come bearing lattes.
-Oh.
-Sugar-free vanilla latte.
-Thank you.
And for you, double caff,
double foam
with caramel and mocha.
How did you know that?
I'm an
investigative journalist.
But don't we all know
our friends' orders by heart?
This was very thoughtful
of you, thank you.
-It was nothing.
See you guys there.
-Bye.
-Wow.
Rejection never looked so good
or was so cool about it.
Why am I so bad at this?
At 9:00 p.m. tonight,
Obsidian will change
the way you think
and feel and experience life.
The countdown to your
dreams starts now.
Eleven hours and counting.
Exclamation point,
exclamation point.
Help! Help!
Are you okay?
I am now.
Thank you for saving me.
What the hell happened?
Someone tried
to kill you.
-How did you know?
-Because of this.
It was delivered
five minutes ago.
It's an Anti-Obsidian
manifesto.
"Obsidian North
is technological genocide.
With Andrea Rojas now dead,
consider this
your final warning.
Cancel the Obsidian Platinum
launch or more will die."
He can threaten
whatever he wants.
I will not postpone.
Well, isn't that cute?
I wasn't aware
a Maladorian Dendroasp
could show any restraint.
-And you two share
a lot in common.
-Hmm.
Non Nocere does
what God couldn't.
Turns the most ferocious animal
instincts into "do no harm."
So far, all of your
animal trials have
produced perfect results.
Yeah, but the human brain
is far more complex
and I've yet to test it
to see that it's working
just as perfectly.
Can't have any critics
pouncing on any mistakes.
Hmm. That has a bit
of a personal ring to it.
Let me guess. Your biggest
critic is a Kryptonian?
Before Crisis, when I tried to
use Myriad, she assumed that
I was trying
to mind control people.
Her and her friends think
I'm going down a dark path.
They think
you've turned into me.
Or at least, Mother.
But you haven't... tragically.
Can you imagine what it would
be like if humanity didn't
succumb to terror,
rage and worry?
We would be the best
versions of ourselves.
-Be creative. Be free--
-Utopia.
Exactly. But Supergirl and her
friends just can't accept that
I don't want to
puppet master humanity.
Since I anticipated
you being ready for
the next phase of testing,
I took the liberty of setting
up a trial at that cute little
prison we own.
Willing subjects waiting for
a chance to be better people.
There's a car waiting
for you downstairs.
Gotta go. Duty calls.
Got your text.
Good news on inverting
Toyman's Immortality Code
for use against Leviathan?
Yes. I'm nearly done
re-purposing the code
to render Leviathan vulnerable,
but seeing as how they are
a techno-organic species
from the same
solar system as Krypton,
I've calculated that it would
be next to impossible
to inject
the code into their skin
without first, somehow,
weakening them.
So, are you saying
we would need to find
their version of Kryptonite?
In so many words, yes.
Then no.
I've been down that road
and let's just say,
I didn't win.
There is one
intriguing possibility.
but that would require
access to Leviathan's
base of operations.
Which we don't even know
the location of.
Sir.
There's been an attack
on Andrea Rojas.
Despite a vicious attack,
Andrea Rojas promised that
the launch will proceed
as planned
at 9:00 p.m. tonight...
This is terrible.
Or fortuitous.
We need to get closer
to Leviathan
so that we can
find their home base
to administer
the Mortality Code.
Gemma Cooper is heavily
invested in both Andrea
and the launch,
which will need protection.
What better way
to get in with Leviathan
than to protect
their favorite child?
Call Supergirl.
I am not a bodyguard, Lex.
With you guarding her,
there is a 99.7% chance
that Andrea survives
and her assailant is captured.
Well, instead, why doesn't
the DEO track the terrorists
before they attack again?
When I rescued her
this morning,
there was pink energy
surrounding the elevator.
Pink energy would suggest
a Chlorophyllian.
And their energy
is impossible to track.
Finding them before
the launch tonight
seems unlikely.
And if you refuse, you know
the leverage I have.
Not to mention you'll have
the blood of a poor,
innocent billionaire
on your hands.
Platinum lets you be
whomever you want,
whenever you want.
We have more cases
than I care to count.
Runaway aliens,
missing persons,
and... the odd wayward spouse.
And still no leads
on what Lex is up to.
We will get to the bottom
of that, I promise you.
Are you okay?
I've had a clear mission
and a boss to answer to
every day of my life
since medical school.
And now,
with all this freedom,
-I'm just starting
to feel a little--
-Discombobulated.
Yes.
-Hey.
Lex just personally
assigned me
to bodyguard Andrea Rojas
until Platinum's launch
tonight.
Bodyguard?
Why does Lex care so much
about the launch?
Exactly. He must have
an ulterior motive
against Obsidian.
Or it's a trap.
Well, either way,
I'll investigate
when I'm with Andrea,
but I came here first
to see if you guys could help.
Do you have any idea
who attacked Andrea?
I saw pink energy
in the elevator
while it was falling.
And Brainy says
it could be Chlorophyllian,
but he also said their energy
is impossible to track, so...
Chlorophyllians are
a peaceful race.
They absorb sunlight
through their dermis
in order to super-grow crops.
They shouldn't be able
to siphon off
electrical energy.
Still, it's a lead.
We'll get on it.
Well, if you need me
I'll be glued
to Andrea's side.
You're a difficult woman
to track down.
You being here
blocking my way
would suggest otherwise.
I heard the terrible news.
How perplexing
that terrorists were able
to breach your security.
And you want to "help" me.
How thoughtful.
On such a momentous day
for your company
I feel it's my civic duty.
What could you
possibly give us
that we can't give ourselves?
Supergirl...
For Andrea Rojas's protection.
I don't need your Supergirl,
nor do I want her.
Oh, I think you do.
I know you prefer yourpeople
to not be in the public eye,
and, well, this launch... Wow.
Talk about the headlines.
And if you know my people,
you know what I can do
to a yappy little dog
that nips at my heel.
That's why I adore you.
I can give you something
you value above all else...
anonymity.
The entire world will be
watching and recording
Andrea Rojas' every move
until the launch at 9:00 p.m.
Given the high-profile nature
of the situation,
I'm the easy choice.
I do admire your confidence,
Mr. Luthor.
Always the over-achiever.
I'll call off my friends.
But be forewarned,
we don't give second chances.
So don't make promises
you can't keep.
All of these men volunteered?
They did.
It's a cross section
of inmates
from the most violent
to those who are afraid
of their own shadow.
What are you looking at?
Nothing, nothing.
I'm sorry, Toby.
Guards!
Are you all right?
It's nothing.
That was practically
a high five,
considering what he does
to me most days.
How do you cope?
It's prison.
Guys like me
don't stand a chance.
Five years in here
taught me that.
But maybe after your trials,
I won't have to worry.
I've heard you're trying
to turn them
peaceful as Quakers.
If you succeed,
that'd be a real godsend
for guys like me, Lena Luthor.
Let's get started.
Thank you for seeing
how important this is
and having my back.
With you by my side,
people will be
even more amped
for the launch.
Selfie?
Uh...
Hashtag SuperGuard.
When is everyone
getting here?
I cancelled the live audience.
I won't risk innocent lives.
And I won't give in to terror.
Andrea!
Natalia.
Oh, my God, how are you?
You must still be shaking.
Oh, better now that I'm here.
Pleasure to meet you,
Supergirl.
William Dey.
-We crossed paths this morning.
-Uh, yeah, yes.
It's very nice to meet you...
formally.
What are you doing here?
I'm covering the Obsidian
North Platinum launch,
and this is the first stop
on the press tour.
You're following Andrea
around all day?
Well, if someone attacks,
you could get hurt, or killed.
I'm a journalist.
We put ourselves
in harm's way
to show our readers
the truth.
How can I shy away
from danger
when the people I cover can't?
That's very heroic.
Ah, I don't know about that,
but thank you.
It's also a huge story.
For better or worse,
this launch
is the biggest thing
since the invention
of the computer.
Harry!
-J'onn J'onzz!
-Hey, man.
-It's been a while.
-Yeah.
What are you up to?
We're looking for
a Chlorophyllian.
You know any?
Can't say that I do.
But Dmitry over there,
he knows everybody.
Might be worth a shot.
-Thanks, man.
-Thanks.
Hey, man.
You!
Get away from me.
You two know each other?
I might've roughed him up
once or twice
while tracking a lead.
It's not the arm-twisting
I'm worried about,
it's the jail time
I did afterward
that I'd like to avoid.
Look, we're not here
to arrest you. Okay?
I don't work for
the government anymore.
We're gonna need your help.
Look, we're looking for
a Chlorophyllian.
Somebody with tech issues
or possibly
an anger management
problem.
I have a buddy
who engages in certain...
less than legal
weapons transactions.
He mentioned a Chlorophyllian
asking about
some military-grade tech.
The Chlorophyllian...
any ideas where
we can find him?
My buddy was complaining
about making the trek out
to a farmhouse on Route 89.
Thank you.
And I... I'm sorry
about last time.
-She's sorry. Thanks.
-Yeah.
This sounds
really bad, J'onn.
I'm gonna call Brainy
and see what he can find.
You sure that's wise?
If Lex finds out
Brainy's using
DEO resources for you,
it could put him
in Lex's crosshairs.
-He's family. He'll let us
know if he can't.
Brainy, hey.
We got a lead.
That's excellent news.
Can you see if there's
a Chlorophyllian living off
of Route 89?
It's some kind of farm.
I just need a name, address...
anything you can get.
Unfortunately,
I see no record
of any Chlorophyllians
living in that vicinity.
In fact, the only farm
off Route 89
has been liquidated
with no proof
of asset dispersion.
Okay, thanks, Brainy.
No dice.
Ah, look, I still want
to track down that farm.
Yeah, agreed.
I apologize for
the intrusion.
I'm here to help.
Lex must ingratiate
himself with Gemma Cooper
in order to defeat Leviathan.
For that to happen,
Supergirl must save
Andrea Rojas.
Therefore, Alex Danvers
and J'onn J'onzz need to be
left in the dark.
I've done the calculations.
There is
a 93.2% probability that
none will invite me
to Thanksgiving...
after I do what must be done.
Yes, well, that is a quite
the conundrum, Querl.
Alas, in a moment like this,
there is only one thing
you can do.
Trust the math.
Your ultimate allegiance
must remain with Lex.
Only then, will the future
unfold the way we need it to.
Trust that your friends
are strong.
I mean, they areheroes,
after all.
And that is quantifiable.
I desperately hope
you're right.
Man, that is a nice haircut.
Shut up.
Non Nocere program
uploading.
Let's see if this works.
Gentlemen, stand
and remove your lenses.
Yo, Steve, come here.
Do you wanna grab
some grub?
Uh, sure, Toby...
That would be lovely.
Yeah.
You're a genius.
...as a testament to the people
who are standing up
to these threats.
What do you make of all this?
How do you mean?
The culprit, the manifesto,
the whole situation?
Off the record, of course.
I think it's horrible.
People should never
resort to violence.
-But...
-I hate to say it,
but I think the manifesto
makes some slightly
decent points.
I mean, not that
"Obsidian Lenses will take
our sentient minds hostage."
But that people
disconnecting from
the real world
could backfire
in unforeseen ways,
creating irreparable damage.
What do you think?
The way I look at it,
Obsidian North's
biggest appeal is that
it taps into people's desire
to feel connected.
And when you
only live in that VR world,
you end up getting
further and further away
from the real world.
You've thought a lot
about this.
When the first generation
lenses dropped, I was buzzing.
I thought about being able
to hang with my buddy
who I lost a few years ago.
But it wasn't until
I hung out with my friend,
or, co-worker, Kara,
that I remembered what
being really connected
feels like.
All it took was some karaoke
and a game night.
But I realized
I didn't want to live in
some perfect VR world,
I just wanted to be with
the people I care about.
Andrea Rojas!
Ms. Rojas, we need to
get you to a secure location.
I am not running away.
You were just attacked
by someone who can
travel through light.
Then it's good
that saving people
is what you do best.
And Obsidian...
It's what I do best.
It's my life.
It's my father's, too.
This company
is his life's work.
Mi papábuilt it
from the ground up.
He sacrificed everything,
and...
...and so did I.
I've done things to help him
restore Obsidian to glory.
Things I'm not proud of,
and things I can never undo.
I pushed away friends
for my own gain...
But I would do it all again
in a heartbeat.
I will not stop
just because someone
is threatening me.
Your next appearance
is downtown
at the Obsidian store pop-up.
I will have to do a sweep
of the area, twice,
and I'm not letting you
out of my sight.
Thank you, Supergirl.
Hi, Steve.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
for whatever I did.
Everything okay?
No, it's not.
I'm not okay!
Steve! Steve!
Get a medic!
Steve?
Can you hear me?
You had a reaction.
It caused
a grand mal seizure.
Do you remember what happened?
It was Toby.
I thought
he was going to hit me.
When he asked me
if I was okay...
I felt something
I'd never felt before.
For...
For the first time... ever,
I wanted to be the bully.
Fear is the only emotion
I've known for most of my life,
but then you came along
and I... finally felt hope.
But now, all I feel is
a hunger for revenge,
for violence...
It's trapped inside me,
it's trying to
claw its way out,
I can't get rid of it.
It's so much worse
than anything that Toby
ever did to me.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You fixed those monsters,
but what about me?
Why didn't you fix me?
I will fix it, okay?
I promise. I promise!
You know, I could have
phased us both through.
Yeah, but I really missed
kicking doors in.
Whoever this belongs to
has himself a green thumb.
Just like a Chlorophyllian.
Walden Pond... an idealized
return to nature.
Certainly jives
with the manifesto.
"Our inventions are wont
to be pretty toys,
which distract our attention
from serious things."
Look at these schematics.
Looks like he has
a pretty toy all of his own.
These are weapons-grade
components.
This is what
he must've been trying
to buy on the black market.
Some kind of gauntlet.
I want you by my side
at all times. Got it?
You're the boss.
Hello, everyone!
Which of you is ready
to change your life?
You shouldn't be here.
Watch out!
Hey...
Supergirl.
We need to go, now.
What? Wait,
you can't leave me here!
Are you okay?
I think so.
-What happened?
Whoever it was,
they were able to take
my powers
and use them against me.
Is that something
Chlorophyllians can even do?
Not at all.
Must be those gauntlets.
They're enhancing
their abilities,
allowing them to harness
any form of energy,
including the powers
of other aliens.
Well, Andrea is safe
at the DEO.
Let's see if we can
salvage something.
Right.
I'd say
go easy on that thing,
but if it takes
the pressure off,
you may as well.
Do you remember when
you turned the sun red,
what you told me?
You told me
that you were doing it
for the good
of the human race.
You deluded yourself
into thinking
you were saving us,
when you were really
killing us.
And maybe I'm just
as deluded as you are.
I haven't been deluded
a day in my life.
You want to know
what I remember?
You showed up at my office
with the Man of Tomorrow award.
It was the last time
you were ever proud of me.
We had just made
first contact with
an alien race
and you didn't care.
You didn't see the threat.
You just wanted to focus
on the more philanthropic
efforts of Luthor Corp.
And I fired you for it.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you're going down
the same path I did,
and you are better than that.
Superman was my downfall.
I let my obsession
with destroying him
drive me off-course,
but now I have
a second chance
to do things the right way,
with you.
Non Nocere was supposed
to liberate people,
not take away their free will.
But all I've managed to do
is to trap people
in their own bodies
with their ugliest
inclinations.
Maybe I have gone down
a dark path.
Don't let your obsession
with what Supergirl thinks
get in your way.
You can't change
what's in her heart any more
than you can change mine.
But unlike her,
I believe in
what you're doing.
We'll figure this out
together,
and I'm not leaving
until we do.
Pull up the algorithm.
You wanna talk?
We almost died today
because I couldn't save us.
I don't have freeze breath
and I can't
phase through things.
But it didn't even
matter before then
because I had this
entire team that was behind me.
I turned in my gun
and my badge
so that I could stop Lex
from the outside.
I thought the DEO
was holding me back,
but what if it was
holding me up?
Alex, when I left the DEO,
I was lost, too.
But you came to me
at a real low point
and you reminded me that
sometimes it takes a while
to grow into
the new version of yourself.
It's a process, Alex.
And today is the first day.
Give yourself time
to recalibrate.
And in the meantime,
just know that we all
have your back.
I found something.
What'd you get?
"Todd Sapphire."
He worked for Obsidian?
Looks like Sapphire had
someone he cared deeply about.
What happened
to him?
According to Obsidian HR,
he became addicted
to the virtual reality lenses
and was terminated
because he stole a pair
for an all-night binge.
Could the attack
on Andrea be retaliation
for getting fired?
This is a suicide note.
Addressed to "My darling Amy.
I'm sorry I could not be
stronger for you, my love,
but ever since we left
our home world
I have felt lost
and the only relief
I've found is in VR.
I'm so homesick
I can't think of anything else.
I can't go on."
Wait a minute.
He died a year ago.
So if he's dead,
then he couldn't have
attacked Andrea...
Then was it his wife?
She blames
Obsidian for his death.
And the manifesto warned
against making VR
a new paradise...
Amy is trying
to stop the launch
to save people
from her husband's fate.
The launch
is in 27 minutes.
I have to get
to CatCo.
Get out if you wanna live!
You!
Where is Andrea Rojas?
She's not here.
Leave these people alone.
I'm stopping the launch.
Not if I have anything
to say about it.
This ends now.
I'm sorry.
I can't let you stop me.
It's time to put
your toys to bed.
-Are you okay?
- I will be.
Get everyone out of here.
I'll go after Amy.
Director Dox,
we're receiving reports
of a terrorist event
at Obsidian.
And a massive power outage
that seems to be
spreading across the city.
The launch,
the whole Platinum cloud,
has a failsafe.
If power is drained
from our generators,
the failsafe pulls power
from the city's grid
to ensure the launch.
The Luthor PowerCore?
That system reacquires energy
as rapidly as it is lost.
If power continues
to deplete at this rate--
It could not only cause
a massive blackout
to National City,
but could also cause
the majority of
its transformers to explode.
Fire, chaos...
I have to get to CatCo
and take the failsafe offline.
No. It's too dangerous.
I'll go.
Please,
take me with you.
Supergirl promised
Mr. Luthor that you would
stay out of danger.
Put her in a holding cell.
Come on. Come on.
Go! Go!
Please stop!
If you destroy
the processor
it will explode.
I don't intend to destroy it.
I just need it to stop.
Hi.
Follow me,
I'll get you all to safety.
Now, quickly.
Let's go! Let's go!
Amy, no!
No, no, no, no.
This can't be right!
Let me go!
Please. I need
to get to CatCo.
Amy, please, you can't
go through with this.
You don't have
any power to stop me.
You're right. I'm powerless.
So blast me again
if you want to.
But I know about Todd.
I know how much
you loved each other.
And I know
what dark spiral
he went down
after he got addicted
to Obsidian's VR.
But Amy, just as Todd
became obsessed
with a virtual world,
you have become obsessed
with finding justice for him.
No one else should suffer
the way I did.
Oh, my God.
You shouldn't be here.
Who released you
from custody?
It's not working.
Someone built a failsafe
into the failsafe
to secure the launch.
I read your manifesto...
Your point that people
would rather live in
a virtual world
than actually help
the real world,
I hear that.
I hear you.
It's built to trap you.
An addiction.
That's what it did to Todd.
I know.
But if you go through
with what you're doing,
it won't just shut down
the launch.
Innocent people will die.
I know you don't want that.
What you want
is for people to engage.
For people to know
what it's like to be
in the outside world.
To be a partner, to love,
to have friends.
Nothing can change the past.
Believe me, I've tried.
But you are in control
of your own future.
Todd may not be here anymore,
but you are.
Just look deep
inside yourself and think,
is thiswhat Todd
would have really wanted?
I miss him every day.
How did you get back here
so fast from the DEO?
I convinced some agents
to bring me.
Todd Sapphire became
addicted to a proto version
of Obsidian VR.
Maybe you should
slow down the rollout.
Todd's story was tragic,
but he's not
the only story out there.
After the attack tonight,
do you know what happened?
Our employees used our VR
to cope with the trauma
they'd just experienced.
Bottom line, Supergirl,
I'm here to help people.
Remember that.
Acrata...
power through shadows.
Well, Alex, you made it
through your first day.
Still no leads
on Lex though.
This is gonna be
a long road, Alex.
-And I think...
...you are gonna need...
some backup.
My gun.
Not quite.
Back on Mars we called this...
...or "hand of the soldier."
It can transform
into any weapon.
-What?
-You just have to picture it
in your mind's eye.
Look, I know
you don't have a badge,
but today you proved
you didn't need one.
J'onn, this is amazing.
-I don't know what to say.
Thank you.
With a little practice
you'll learn to control it.
Yeah.
It's gone.
All that pain...
The hunger.
Those feelings, it's as if...
I never had them.
How did you do that?
My brother, of all people,
helped me focus on
what really mattered.
I had accounted
for violent tendencies,
but not the feelings
of injustice
which activate
a different part of the brain.
So it was just a matter
of tweaking the algorithm
to account for that.
Well, whatever you did,
it worked.
For the first time in maybe...
ever...
I feel safe.
You really are the hero
people say you are.
If this works, the world
won't need heroes.
-That's so cool.
So, it's Martian?
-Yeah.
Well, I mean,
it's really a gun though.
Or I mean, whatever weapon
I want it to be.
J'onn just has to train me
how to use it.
Well, even without it today
you were pretty badass.
Who says you need
a badge and the DEO?
-That's right.
Oh! William.
"I couldn't find you
after the attack.
Are you okay?"
That is none of your business.
I really need to text him back.
I mean, it sounds like
he still really likes you.
Are you regretting
saying no?
I don't know.
I've been so preoccupied
with people using VR
to escape the real world,
when that's exactly
what I'm doing with William.
I'm avoiding my own reality.
Well, it sounds like
you know what
you need to do.
It's just one dinner, right?
Yeah.
I'm alive.
Kara! Oh, thank God.
I heard you got out
but it's much better to...
-...see for myself.
Yeah. By the time I had
gotten your messages,
I figured
it was easier to just
show you proof of life.
Yeah, sure.
So how did you know
I was here?
Well, it's common knowledge
you're a night owl
and a workaholic,
and one of the most
dedicated reporters I know.
I think you give me
a run for my money there.
Oh, God, this is too much,
isn't it?
The coffee, the texts,
the compliments.
I'm sorry, you asked
to be friends
and I should be
respecting that,
but instead I've been
overstepping all day.
No, no, no. Not at all.
It's fine.
That's actually why
I'm here.
I made a mistake last week
because I was scared.
You're a great guy.
More than a great guy.
And... And I would
love to go out.
I would love that.
There's my favorite Coluan.
The progress you've made
inverting the code,
-looks like a real killer.
Don't you just love it
when a plan comes together?
What? You don't love it?
I encountered
your Luthor PowerCore
this evening
and was unable
to take it offline.
I texted you for assistance
and I got no reply.
That failsafe
endangered 67%
of National City's population.
So a few houses
could've burned down.
Small price for progress.
People could have died.
If Supergirl hadn't--
But she did.
Have you forgotten,
Director Dox?
Supergirl always
saves the day.
Saving Obsidian Platinum
solidified our worth
to our new friends.
Gotta go. Time to close.
Forgive me for
keeping you waiting.
You should be more considerate.
When you make promises,
those around you
expect you to keep them.
I know that
to the untrained eye,
-today did not seem ideal.
-Oh.
Fires, police, superheroes.
Which part of this
do you consider not ideal?
I believe that a woman with
your wisdom and foresight
would see that we delivered
the results you desired,
we just did it with panache.
And without you having
to stick out your pretty neck.
But I believe fate
has thrown us together.
Me, the most trusted
and beloved man on Earth...
Who better to represent
Obsidian Platinum
in its worldwide rollout
than Lex Luthor?
I'm the chocolate
to your peanut butter.
With me as
your global ambassador,
there won't be an eyeball
from Tokyo to Tajikistan
without Obsidian lenses
on it.
You make
a persuasive case, Lex.
Hmm, as I told you,
I can be an excellent
friend when I want to be.
And I want to be
very good friends.
So tell me this...
As a friend,
do you expect something
in return?
It would be lovely
to meet your friends.
Make good on your word,
and we can discuss.