Previously on
Supergirl...
My brother was a traitor.
He poisoned us.
Perhaps if I can access
more of my memories,
I might be able to uncover
what his next move will be.
Kelly, do you think
we can go deeper
with Obsidian's tech?
That kind of power
could re-set your brain
for good.
The power to incept
was stolen from me
in the Phantom Zone.
That woman gave you the answer.
Eve, meet Hope.
You two are going to be working
closely together.
I see you.
You're a saboteur.
That's a rotten way
of making it to the top.
Hey, Jarrod.
Blowing me off
was not a smart move.
Was I unclear
the first 12 times?
I'm not interested.
If you don't work with us,
this will end very badly.
You're going with threats?
You should see
what my board
threatens me with
every other Tuesday.
You're making a mistake.
Thanks, Jenny.
The next time your sister
asks you to babysit,
just say no.
Remember, boundaries.
Speaking of boundaries,
do you even know that woman?
I just met her, why?
She just told you
her whole life story?
It's kind of my job
to listen, guys.
Kelly, you were attacked
by a shapeshifter.
And he's still out there.
And you have every DEO agent
working to find him.
I don't think it could hurt
to reel it in
just until they catch him.
And as Alex's sister,
I can tell you
that she's almost always
annoyingly right.
And as Kelly's brother,
I can tell you
that she can handle herself.
Listen, I hate to break up
this Danvers-Olsen scrimmage,
but we have to get
to our meeting.
- All right.
-Try not to worry so much.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Any sign of Malefic?
No. He doesn't seem to have
any psychic signature either.
But we'll find him.
We have to.
Oh! You... You all right?
Maybe I'm a little nervous
about having lunch with Lena.
It's the first time
we're hanging out
since I told her
I was Supergirl.
I was just
lying to her for so long.
Kara, Lena forgave you.
Okay? So you're going to have
to just let go of the past.
I just want things
to be great between us.
I... And I want
this lunch to be--
Perfect.
Yes.
And it will.
Look, Lena wants
your relationship
back on track, too.
Look, I have to get back
to the DEO.
You go be perfect
somewhere else.
I'll try.
Okay.
Damn it!
The transmitter you duplicated
from the Obsidian contacts
uses an ocular interface.
Since you modeled it
directly into the brain,
may I suggest
you lower the frequency
another 7.32%?
It's not that, Hope.
In theory,
Q-waves should allow me
to rewrite portions
of the human brain.
To rid the world of lying,
manipulation and violence.
Yes, but no matter
how I manipulate the frequency,
the transmitter
will only allow me
to read information
from the brain.
If I try to augment it,
I get a zombie effect.
And you don't want
a world of robots.
You just want better people.
Right.
I am sorry, Ms. Luthor.
It must be uncomfortable,
with me in this form,
for you to trust me.
I don't trust people, Hope.
I believed I could once.
I had friends
that made me believe I could.
But they betrayed me
like everyone else.
Your brother, Lex,
was the worst of them.
But I believe
he could help you now.
I have access to
Eve Tessmacher's memories.
Lex was working with Q-waves.
It was part of his plan
to get past
Superman's invulnerable skin.
He left detailed records
in his private journals.
His journals?
There are three of them.
They are currently
in a level five secure facility
at Fort Summit.
However, upon further analysis,
retrieving them
would be impossible.
For me, maybe, but...
not for everyone.
Graceful arcs across her brow
I'm left forever to wonder how
A being as perfect
as my Nia Nal
Could ever love
-Someone as small...
-Put up with this all.
What was that?
Um, just thank you
for poem one hundred and--
One hundred and twenty-seven.
Yes, I've almost
mastered the sonnet.
Oh, I think you've got it.
But you don't wanna
overdo it.
You're right.
Brevity is the soul of wit,
as Polonius said to Hamlet.
Now I shall move on
to the villanelle.
A more complicated form,
but capable of much deeper
emotional resonance,
as exemplified by Dylan Thomas'
"Don't go gentle--"
Nia.
All right,
what's next on the docket?
Any celebrity divorces?
Disgraced influencers?
Show me the clicks.
I've got this week's
medical examiner's report,
and I thought we could
run a story on recent deaths.
People love
to read about death.
It reminds them
that they're alive,
and it gives them
the pleasure of schadenfreude.
I like it.
Twenty-year-old Uber driver,
hit by a car.
If the person is boring,
then the cause of death
is boring.
Wow me.
Show me some sparkly death.
No, no, no...
Um... Oh!
Dr. Niles Jarrod,
a health tech billionaire,
recently discovered deceased
in a night club bathroom.
My God!
Dr. Jarrod died?
I... I interviewed him
last year--
For your piece
on the moral implications
of gene manipulation.
Knowing the dead person
does not make
their death interesting.
-Next.
-Wait, wait.
A 33-year-old genius
doing significant work
in the field of extending life
dies young, unexpectedly?
It's tragic.
And certainly worth a story.
There's hard news,
legitimate feature,
or brain candy.
Sentimental tripe
you just pitched us
is a category of its own...
Trash.
How dare you--
William's right.
A dead scientist
is not sparkly.
And there's
no substantive story.
So stop wasting our time.
How do you know
there's no substantive story
when we haven't even
looked into it yet?
I've looked into it.
Thoroughly.
Nothing there.
Franklin,
next corpse, please.
Perfect.
I think you know more about
the Jarrod story,
and for some reason
you don't want me on it.
You're paranoid.
You lied up there. Why?
Stop humiliating yourself,
Danvers.
It's painful to watch.
I know that braid.
-You okay?
Yeah. I thought I had
William Dey pegged
as an ambitious ass,
but I think
he might be much worse.
-You remember that piece I did
on genetic engineering?
-Yeah.
Well, my main subject,
Dr. Jarrod,
was found dead in a club.
-Overdose?
-Unclear.
And William Dey
spiked the story.
He said
he'd already looked into it
and there was nothing more
to find.
-So?
-He was lying.
His heart rate
was through the roof.
He knows something more
about Dr. Jarrod's death,
and he doesn't want me
to find out about it.
Sounds like we should
be calling my contact
at the M.E.'s office.
I'm sorry. We?
Yeah. I mean,
I want to get out of my head
about the job offers, and...
We may have a murder to solve.
Unless you don't want
a super friend.
No, of course I do.
Okay then.
I'll keep you updated.
Okay.
Nia, come on in.
J'onn, what is it? Is it Mal?
-No, no, no. Nothing like that.
Another poem.
Every hour of every day
Brainy sends a new ode
to a new body part.
Sorry, um, not appropriate.
Or important, right now.
How can I help?
I wanna restore
my missing memories.
I was hoping that you
and your dream power
might go deeper
than Kelly's technology could.
Isn't messing with memories
dangerous?
No, I believe
that restoring lost memories
through dreams should be safe,
because I will be finding them
myself in an organic way.
With your help, of course.
J'onn, are you sure
you want to remember?
Malefic said
I was still in the dark.
And I believe he's right.
And one of those
missing memories
has the key to unlock
why he betrayed our people.
Why he's coming after
everybody I care about.
If I can truly understand
what happened,
I might be able to stop him.
Pete Andrews?
-What are you doing here?
I haven't seen you in, what?
Like two years?
Well, one of the guys
posted something online
about you working here.
So...
That's funny, I just started.
Well, I was in town,
I thought I might drop by
and see your new digs.
Kind of fancy, Olsen.
Thanks.
God, it's so cool of you
to stop by.
Dr. Olsen.
Your 1:30 appointment is here.
Yeah. Ugh, I'm sorry.
I would so love to catch up,
I just, I can't right now.
Kelly, I came to
National City to see you.
I think...
I think I need help.
Of course.
My last appointment
wraps up around 6:30.
Come back then, we'll talk.
Thank you.
You always had
the biggest heart in the world.
Merci.
Au revoir.
You brought me
coffee eclairs
from Cafe Rue Serret
on the Champs-Elysees?
I know they're your favorite.
And the cappuccinos,
did you really go to
Pave in Milan?
It didn't take me that long.
You know, I have really
been missing out
on the perks
of having Supergirl
as a best friend.
Well, we have a lot
of lost time to make up for.
Yeah, but you know
you don't have to go to Paris
to pick up lunch, Kara.
That's not
what's important to me.
But, these scones from Dublin,
oh, my God,
you can fly these in everyday.
Mmm. So, tell me,
how is CatCo?
Is everything okay?
Is Andrea behaving civilized?
Oh, that's not exactly the word
I would use to describe her.
Her mandate has been
making CatCo
the most viewed news website
in the world
using tactics like pop quizzes
and clickbait.
Kara, I'm so sorry
to hear that.
Yeah, and then she hired
this snake named William Dey.
Wait, William Dey? Really?
He's supposed to be
a really talented journalist.
I know, but sadly, talent
doesn't always mean integrity.
And I have no idea
what his MO is,
but James is helping me
figure it out.
Enough about me. How are you?
Um...
To tell you the truth,
I haven't had the easiest time
of it since Lex.
I've been having nightmares.
I try not to sleep.
Oh, Lena.
Nights are filled
with apocalyptic visions
of torture and anguish
at the hands of my brother.
Kelly is working
with PTSD patients
at Obsidian North.
Maybe she could help you.
Thank you. But you know
how private a person I am.
Yeah.
You know,
the really frustrating part is
I figured out a way
to heal myself.
I mean, do you remember
the journals we found
at Stryker's?
Of course.
Well, reading them is
the only thing that calms me.
Somehow, hearing Lex's voice
takes the mystery away.
And the terror.
I just know if I could
read them all then
I would be able to cure myself
of the trauma.
Well, then that's what
you have to do.
Unfortunately
that is not an option.
The government has confiscated
all of Lex's possessions.
His technologies, his weapons,
even his childhood journals.
Well, that's ridiculous.
You're the only person that
could have an interest in that.
Can't you just ask
for them back?
Believe me, I have tried,
but it is all tied up
in bureaucracy and red tape.
My lawyer said I would never
get them out of Fort Summit.
Well, I could get them for you.
Kara, don't be ridiculous.
The journals
will help you heal,
and they're only locked up
due to a technicality.
I could go and get them
and no one would ever know.
No, I couldn't ask you
to do that.
You're not asking.
I'm...
I'm offering.
-Oh.
Oh, it's James.
He's at the M.E.'s office.
That's okay, we can talk later.
Thank you.
Hey, we have five minutes.
Okay.
You okay? You look like
you robbed a bank.
Robbed a bank?
No, never.
I would never rob anything.
It's, uh...
Just an expression, Kara.
Right.
Okay, healthy
33-year-old male.
Cause of death, heart attack.
EMTs found him unresponsive
on the bathroom floor
in a nightclub downtown.
There's something there.
Is that a...
tattoo?
Inside his heart?
How do you get a tattoo
inside your heart?
This is t'fek'lya.
It may taste a little weird.
It's a Martian herb
which aids
in the connection of minds.
Ugh.
No, it's great.
You ready?
Let's do this.
Get him! Get him!
I don't understand.
What is this?
Why are they in human form?
Your memories
are being filtered
through my subconscious
in a way
that makes sense to me.
J'onn, wait up.
J'onn, I think that's you.
Let's play hide and seek.
J'onn, you're it.
I remember playing this game.
There.
-Nice job.
Malefic, you go now.
He cannot connect
to the hive mind.
He can't do it.
-What's wrong with you?
-He can't do anything.
Stop it, Malefic!
Sleep.
I thought
the White Martians
used some kind of technology
to turn Malefic
into a terrible weapon,
but he was born that way.
Born able to project
his thoughts
and his will on others, but...
cut off from my people
in the cruelest way.
Where are we going, Papa?
Where no one
can hurt you, my son.
My beautiful son,
know that you are loved
and that we will
pray for you everyday
as you must pray yourself.
Look to H'ronmeer's teachings
for guidance and healing.
Let his counsel
lighten your pain,
so that he might
deliver us to a better place.
Father! J'onn!
Don't leave me here!
I'll be good. I promise.
Our god will
never forsake you.
Malefic, I love you.
Please...
Don't leave me here.
I'll do anything.
Malefic, it's J'onn.
Father prays
for your healing everyday.
He has faith that...
one day you will return
home to us.
H'ronmeer is not
my salvation, brother.
They are.
H'ronmeer...
I failed you
as I failed my own son.
Allowed Malefic
to be conscripted
by the White Martians,
allowed the council
to send him to that purgatory.
The agony in my heart...
It's...
Unbearable.
In my father's anguish,
he must have wiped
both our memories.
Wiped my brother
from existence.
J'onn...
Of course Malefic turned
against his own people.
The isolation,
the betrayal he must have felt.
He wasn't evil,
he was a child.
He needed our help.
And then my father goes
and compounds the tragedy by...
wiping his memory
from the collective.
For Martians,
death isn't final,
but erasing a memory is.
It's as if my father...
murdered his own son.
And the hypocrisy.
His whole life
was about being a holy man.
And then he goes and...
commits our culture's
greatest sin.
Where are the dumplings?
Oh, shoot!
I totally forgot
to put the order in.
I'm sorry.
I just got caught up
investigating
the weird death of this guy
with a tattoo on his heart.
Oh.
Okay.
I can see why you
forgot the dumplings.
All's forgiven.
Yeah, but there's more.
William Dey, he knows
something about it,
and he actively tried
blocking me
from getting involved.
Well, it sounds like
a really good story, right?
And this guy's always been
very competitive with you.
Do you think he's trying to
just steal the scoop
for himself?
Maybe. But something
just doesn't feel right.
As fascinated as I am
by a dead guy
with a tattooed heart,
I am far more interested
in hearing about
your lunch with Lena.
How did it go?
Uh... It was great.
-Uh-oh.
-Great.
Oh, no.
What happened?
Nothing.
I flew to Paris,
Milan, Dublin,
I got all
of her favorite things.
It was...
Great.
So why does it look like
you ran over a puppy?
It was nothing.
Really. I...
I just... I kind of
spontaneously agreed to...
do a favor for Lena.
Okay. So, what's wrong
with that?
Nothing. It just entails...
Breaking into
a secure Army facility
and stealing
Lex Luthor's journals.
What?
Kara, are you
out of your mind?
I just blurted it out.
I wasn't thinking.
But, you should have seen
how much pain she was in,
and she's so traumatized
by Lex's death,
and the journals
are the only way
-she can find closure.
-No.
You're going to call her
right now,
and you're going to tell her
that you made a mistake.
-You're not doing it.
-No. I can't.
No. What you can't do
is break the law
and steal federal property.
Technically,
I break the law all the time.
I just broke into
a supermax prison
two months ago.
Okay.
That is totally different.
That's to serve justice. Right?
Okay. What you're
talking about here
is crossing that line
for a friend.
How is it different?
She deserves to heal,
and who would it be hurting?
You know what?
Brainy just illegally hacked
into security cameras
at a nightclub to help me solve
this Dr. Jarrod's murder.
I don't see you scolding him.
Totally different.
But... Yes,
Brainy should
not be using DEO tech
to help you write articles.
I will crack down on that.
Just want to point out.
Who do you think we learned
all this rule-breaking from?
That cuts deep.
That's Dr. Jarrod,
with William Dey.
And what would he
be doing there?
- Hang on.
Let me zoom in.
That's... the spider.
That's the tattoo on his heart.
What do you see?
Do you know that woman?
No. But...
I know those tattoos.
So, tell me
what you're going through.
Migraines.
Panic attacks.
Well, getting pinned
by snipers in Kandahar
is hard on the psyche.
I'm not the same person
I was before.
Afghanistan
took something from me.
Something in my brain
is broken.
And I want it back.
Can you help me?
I have an opening
this Friday,
and we'll start
the intake process.
It can take
a few months to qualify--
No!
Oh, I'm so...
Kelly, I can't wait.
I'm in crisis now.
If I don't
get a handle on this...
I'm scared
I'm gonna hurt myself.
I am not going to let you
hurt yourself, Pete.
You have to understand...
it's not that simple.
My job is new,
and then there's protocol...
Kelly, please help me.
The office will
thin out in an hour,
and I'll sneak you in later.
We'll start
with the diagnostic,
and get you some answers.
But Pete...
we have to keep this
on the down-low.
-Is that okay?
-Oh, of course.
You're a life saver.
Something is bothering you.
No, it's nothing.
Your pupil dilation
says otherwise.
You can tell me anything.
Brainy, if you had something
really important
to tell someone, but...
if you did tell them,
it would hurt them very much,
would you still do it?
In my experience...
if you care about someone,
you should tell them the truth.
However painful,
both of you
will be better for it.
If you are still feeling blue,
I could cheer you up
with a poem.
"An Ode to Nia Nal's
Left Earlobe.
-A Villanelle--"
-No!
Please, no.
Is there something
you wanted to tell me?
No. Um...
But there is something
that I have to tell J'onn.
They aren't tattoos.
This is an Aurafacian.
This is an alien organism
that attaches to a host body.
This is the original host.
This Aurafacian
was one of the aliens
that Lex had transferred
out of our desert facility,
and obviously
is still at large.
It can transform back and forth
between a tattoo
and a three-dimensional
creature, making her
uniquely dangerous
and very hard to stop.
Now...
Meet our new host.
-Can we get an ID?
-Yeah.
And...
Bingo.
Caroline O'Connor.
She's former
special ops command,
she's highly rated
in hand-to-hand combat,
explosives,
and she's a sniper.
She went off the radar
two years ago,
and somehow hooked up
with our alien.
So somebody
hired her to kill Jarrod.
Yeah. But who? And why?
Well, someone went a long way
to cover her tracks.
- Not far enough.
We just got an address.
I'm not gonna let her
hurt anyone else.
A flash drive
hidden behind a dresser?
Huh.
I don't think
I invited you here.
I invited myself.
Yeah.
I came prepared.
James!
Kara!
This device uses
magnetic resonance
to attract the heavy metals
in their ink.
You ready?
Yeah.
We're examining the evidence
from O'Connor's apartment,
including the external drive
you located, Supergirl.
I am simultaneously attempting
to break the encryption on it,
but...
it is far more complicated
than anything I've seen
in the next 1,000 years.
All right.
Let's get these down
into holding.
Ew. Ew.
You okay?
Yeah.
I've been hit harder than that.
You didn't have to do that.
With everything you have
on your plate,
your potential
run for Senate...
What if she really hurt you?
When your friend's in trouble,
you jump in, period.
Doesn't matter
the consequences.
You keep resting.
Tell Alex and Brainy
that I'll be right back.
I'll be on comms
if they get a lead on O'Connor.
Okay.
Where you going?
To help a friend.
It's late, you all right?
I need to show you something.
It's the rest of your dream
about what happened on Mars.
The part you didn't see.
Do you want to see it?
Because it's going
to be painful.
Absolutely.
H'ronmeer...
I failed you
as I failed my own son.
The agony in my heart...
It's...
Unbearable.
Father, you did the best
you could for Mal.
It's not your fault.
He was my boy.
My child.
He could not control
his illness.
The test was mine
and I failed!
I do not deserve to live.
And how can I continue
to counsel our people...
when I myself am nothing.
Father, our people need you.
I need you.
Then I have failed everyone.
H'ronmeer, forgive me.
It was me.
I'm sorry.
I erased him from our minds.
I as good as murdered
my own brother.
To save your father.
To save us both.
I had, uh...
I had gone to my father
to seek counsel.
To ease my own pain.
And seeing him like that...
Rather than finding
the strength to lift him up,
I, uh...
I crossed a line
that's unforgivable
in my culture.
I spent
the last 300 years...
trying to repent
for having fled Mars...
only to find out
that is the least of my sins.
Oh, I am so ashamed.
You did it out of compassion.
Out of goodness.
Your father was heartbroken.
You saved him.
My father
would rather die than have
his holy mind wiped.
What I did, I did for myself.
You must swear to me...
you will never speak of
what you saw...
to anyone.
I swear.
These will scan your brain
and read your memories.
And your memories
will appear on this screen.
You... You can
see my memories?
Just so I can help you
process them.
Everything's confidential.
Okay, but...
So, they're just gonna...
appear there in real time?
Uh, no, there's a bit of a lag.
It takes a few minutes
for the mapping to finish
and the image generators
to do their thing.
Don't worry.
You'll do great.
Let's do it.
Supergirl?
Brainy cracked the encryption
on O'Connor's drive.
Her next target is
Dr. Andrew Stern
at National City Hospital.
We're en route.
I'm on my way.
Supergirl, I got him.
We're in the atrium.
Dr. Stern,
we have reason to believe
that you are the target of
an assassination attempt--
Ah!
-Dr. Stern?
Nice shot.
You're really
starting to bug me.
You're him.
My inception power.
It worked.
It's Kelly.
Who do you work for?
-Alex!
She's dead.
What just killed her?
Thank you, human.
You have returned my power.
What?
What are you doing to me?
This is the power that
the Phantom Zone took from me.
The power
to control your mind.
You can thank
your weakness for this.
In gratitude,
I'll grant you a quick death.
No...
Please.
Malefic! No!
No! H'ronmeer's curse.
Freeze.
Help.
They're trying to kill me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
There he is. The coffee guy.
No, no, no, wait.
There he is, the janitor.
You can see me?
Kelly, look out.
He's gone.
What happened?
Malefic came after her.
My psychic scan shows
no serious signs of trauma.
But it would seem
the release of Q-waves
somehow interacted
with Obsidian's tech
and forged a link between
Kelly's mind and Malefic's.
She could see him,
even when he shapeshifted.
Well, if she can see him...
Then she's a threat to him.
I'm afraid
it's even worse than that.
My brother now has
the Martian power to incept.
Make you do the things
he wants you to do
against your will.
He'll come after her again.
He'll come after all of you.
Have you been able
to figure out
why he's doing this?
I put him
in the Phantom Zone
for betraying my people.
I guess he just wants revenge.
Look, I'm sorry
that your association with me
has put you all in danger.
Malefic is my responsibility.
Right now...
we need to get Kelly to safety.
Taking her off the board
is gonna be our best bet.
That way I can focus
all of my attention
and our DEO resources
on finding him.
You want me to go away?
Yes. But just until
we catch him.
I think Alex is right.
But don't worry,
I will stay with you. Okay?
No, you've got
decisions to make.
I don't want you missing out.
But you are my priority.
You should leave tonight.
How did it go with J'onn?
Good.
Turned out not to be
that big of a deal.
I can sense that something
is weighing on you.
Well, nothing lifts the spirit
like a villanelle--
Stop.
You said I had to be honest
even if it hurts your feelings,
so here's the truth.
It's just... too much. Okay?
From now on, no more food,
no more poems,
no more anything.
I know...
that you mean well.
I know where
you're coming from,
and it's... sweet.
It's all so sweet.
I... I just...
It's too much.
You... You asked me
to be myself.
To be completely
myself with you.
But now you tell me
you don't want that.
I can only operate at 100%.
That's just how I'm built.
Which is entirely my problem...
and not yours.
Brainy.
I heard about Jarrod.
Yeah.
I don't know how much longer
I can keep this all going.
Keep at it.
And good luck.
You were right.
I was too open
and too trusting.
It's all my fault.
I hope they help.
They already have.
I hope we haven't crossed
any boundaries?
No, for a friend like you
there are no boundaries.
Don't tell me
where you're going, all right?
It's going to be better
that way.
-Okay.
-Thank you, James.
Hey.
Here.
Take this.
It's one of Lex's
transmatter portal watches.
Don't ask me how I got it.
Just... If there's trouble,
just use it.
Thank you.
Everything
is going to be okay.
I'm going to find Malefic
and I'm going
to bring you home.
-Bye.
-Drive safe.
You know, you say
everything's going to be fine,
but... I know that face.
You don't believe it.
Look, I love the fact
that she's so open.
It just scares
the life out of me.
Well, maybe...
Maybe it's not so bad,
and it will all work out.
It worked out
with me and Lena.
I hope so.
For the both of us.
Did you find what you need?
Take a look.
Tell me what you see.
Lex's childhood journals.
Hmm. Not seeing schematics
or anything technical.
It's Lex's version
of a Vigenere cipher.
It's a deceptively complex
polyalphabetic substitution.
Ah...
I see it now.
Deciphering now.
Now I know what I have to do.