Inhale, tadassana...
Exhale. Padmasana.
Again. Inhale, tadassana...
And as we close
our practice,
let us thank
Lena Luthor
for freeing us from rage
and for bringing us peace.
-Namaste.
- Namaste.
What's going on?
Wh... Why won't
the doors open?
The solar event must've
knocked the power out.
I can't breathe.
I think
he's claustrophobic.
I got
to get out of here!
Is that our invitation
to the Leviathan ship?
I really have to put
a bell on you.
No, but I'm close.
I think Gemma Cooper
is warming to me.
And when she sees
my newest present,
she'll roll out
the red carpet.
Another present
like the Sun-Eater?
I'm a twelfth level
intellect.
Did you really think
I wouldn't connect the dots?
-What's your point?
-Okay. I... I know
that you've been
cozying up to Gemma Cooper
for strategic reasons,
but there's a distinction
between manipulating
Leviathan and helping them
destroy the world!
What kind of operation
do you think this is?
Mr. Smith
Goes to Leviathan?
Sometimes, to get
what you want,
you have to play
a little dirty.
I cannot get
that invitation
unless they think
I'm on their side
and if that means
helping them get
a weapon or two,
so be it.
People could've died.
My friends could've died.
Three months ago,
you said that Leviathan
was our biggest threat,
that if we didn't
defeat them,
the global repercussions
would be catastrophic.
Millions dead,
us and the Supers included.
And your very words were,
"The only way
that you could
successfully defeat them
was by working with me,
by trusting me."
So, trust me now...
because I know
what you're thinking.
You're thinking that
if you can get
the location
of the Leviathan ship
before I get that invitation,
you can maybe end this
before anyone gets hurt.
But that's your anxiety
thinking, not logic.
I don't want
your friends to die either,
but sometimes,
for the greater good,
you have to break
a few super-eggs.
And you expect me
to just stand back
while Leviathan tries
to kill my friends?
I expect you
to trust the process.
War is brewing between
Leviathan and the Supers
and you are not
to intervene.
So, we tried
to find Leviathan's
last known location.
There's no trace,
no hidden signs,
no radiation.
Even the elevator was gone.
J'onn is out scanning
for any other signs
of Leviathan right now.
We don't even know
if their headquarters
are in National City
on this Earth.
Well, one thing
that we do know
is that Leviathan strikes
quickly after a failure.
I wish Brainy would give us
another crack at that Morae.
What I'd really like
to know is
why Lena was at the Fortress
at the exact same time.
Myriad is a trigger
for Lena.
So, maybe her arrival
is a coincidence.
Like it was a coincidence
that Lex just heroed in
and saved all those
coma patients
the exact same day Leviathan
tried to destroy the sun?
No. Where there is smoke,
there is a Luthor.
Right now, we have
no reason to believe
that Lena is involved
with Leviathan.
We have no reason
to believe she isn't.
Okay. So, let's start
with something that we do know.
Rama Khan.
Except he hasn't been
seen on this Earth
for hundreds of years.
I can monitor for
unusual seismic activity
until J'onn gets back.
Rama Khan isn't
the only member of Leviathan.
So, we should search
for record
of any others
throughout history.
How can we do that
without the DEO's database?
Kelly's mentioned
an old military friend
who's an expert in
semiotics and iconography
and he's currently
an archivist
at the United States
Congressional Library.
So, I will ask her
to reach out to him
and maybe he can help.
I'll stay here,
see if I can't dream
of Leviathan's
new headquarters.
Good. Look,
we've stopped him before,
we can do it again.
And this time, we'll take down
both the Luthors and Leviathan.
So, the blackout provoked
the subject to have
some sort of episode?
No, I think something's
interfering with
his Non Nocere directive.
Do you think your BFF
messing with Myriad Q-waves
yesterday had anything
to do with it?
That was the very
first thing I thought of,
but I checked and it didn't.
Well, even still,
I could have a bag
of Kryptonite dumplings
delivered to her door.
Mr. Luthor,
I didn't know you were
gonna be here, too.
What an honor.
And I had no idea you...
existed.
This is Steve Lomelli.
I asked him to come.
He was with Klaus
when he changed,
but Steve's Non Nocere
directive is still intact.
So, it was
an isolated incident.
Great. Just need to re-adjust
the Q-wave frequencies
and that should re-establish
Non Nocere.
Don't worry.
I turned the sun red.
I think we can fix
one broken inmate.
Imagine a place where
there's only peace,
connection, unity,
where we can connect
with everyone,
past, present and future,
where a lost loved one
can stand by your side
once more.
I give you Obsidian North's
greatest VR achievement,
the Obsidian Worldwide
Unity Festival.
An Obsidian employee
kidnaps hundreds of users
and the next day,
we're planning
a Live Aid 2020.
If Margot Morrison had
anything to do
with the glitch
that trapped Alex,
who knows what else
she may have planted.
Great. Everyone, thank you.
That'll be it.
-Andrea.
-Kelly. Isn't this exciting?
We're obviously
working late tonight.
I was thinking Thai.
There's so much to do.
Andrea, we are not
in a position to launch
such a massive event.
After what we just
went through,
-we have a responsibility--
-I told you.
I took care of that
glitch personally.
We're clean.
And right now, we have
what every company needs,
-momentum.
-To launch this event
without proper vetting,
is reckless.
We owe it to our users
to make sure it's safe.
It is safe.
So, unless you have
specific proof that it's not,
please do not waste
my time with this, again.
So, wait, this is
the army buddy
Malefic impersonated?
Yes, but this is
the real Pete
and Kelly adores him.
-You must be Alex.
-Hi.
Kelly couldn't stop
talking about you
when she called.
Oh, hey, thanks so much
for meeting with us.
Uh, Pete Andrews,
this is Kara Danvers,
my sister.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Of CatCo Worldwide Media.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
Your use of syntax
and imagery is sublime,
suggesting a much deeper
understanding of language
than just modern English.
Uh, thank you.
Did you spend a lot
of time growing up
in foreign countries?
Uh, no.
We're Midvale born
and raised.
Yup. Yup.
Although right now, I feel
a little like Eliza Doolittle.
"The rain in Spain...
...stays, um,
mainly in the plain."
-Sorry.
-I'm sorry.
Occupational hazard
for a linguist.
I can't turn it off.
Kelly said that you need help
finding a unique symbol?
Yes. It belongs
to a very dangerous
organization that
we're tracking.
We're trying to find
any evidence of it on Earth.
Buildings, temples,
whatever can pinpoint us
to their current location,
Though we think they were
behind the solar event
yesterday.
-They're called Leviathan.
-Leviathan?
I've heard whispers about them,
but only as myth.
Well, we can assure you
they are very real,
and they are very dangerous.
I think I know
where to start.
Neat party trick.
Do you use that at your
corporate cocktail soirees?
Don't be bitter.
You had your chance
at the throne.
Oh, you think
you can fare better?
With those idiotic ringlets
and obnoxious
porcelain cheek bones.
You are a bolt
of power and fear,
and yet you insist
on wearing this
stupid human shell.
You're an insult.
You are just jealous
because I have evolved.
Fitting in with the humans
has allowed me to lull them
into a false sense
of security.
You should really
consider it.
What's in there?
Poison lipstick?
This was stolen from us
years ago.
Lex Luthor found it
just wasting away
in a chilly place that
you know quite well.
So, you came here
to gloat.
I came here to give you
a second chance
to destroy the Supers.
You know what this
weapon is,
so you know what it needs.
Get it for me.
And this time,
do not fail.
In 1752, a series
of crop circles
appeared in Greece,
only weeks before
a plague of locusts
took out the entire region.
But this symbol is similar,
but it's slightly off.
Well, symbols like languages
evolve over time.
But all of these
have the same DNA.
Look at this.
567 A.D, Macedonia,
1134 A.D, Bavaria.
Each time this symbol
has appeared,
catastrophe has followed.
There's gotta be a way
to use this pattern
to predict where
Leviathan is now.
Well, there's a special
collections room
in the library,
might have more information.
I'll go try to get access.
-Great.
-Be right back.
You know what?
I'm starting to get it.
The desire to be
in a new reality,
to live in a world that's
a little less complicated.
Hmm. Is this about
your run-in with Lena?
She was so kind
after Jeremiah died,
and then... and then she
breaks into the fortress
and accuses me,
me, of hypocrisy.
And you know what?
The more I think about it,
the more the pattern
makes sense.
Her and Lex are working
on something with Leviathan,
and it makes me
so angry,
I... I just...
I wanna--
Hide?
William, what's going on?
I've been dissecting
Margot Morrison's
manifesto video.
I think I found something
you're gonna want to see.
I'll be right there.
William thinks he found
something connected
to Margot.
Go. Check it out.
-I'll stay with Pete.
-Thank you.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm so sorry.
Kara had a work emergency.
She had to go.
Oh, that's all right. I think
we may have hit a wall anyway.
All of my requests
were completely denied,
which is strange,
because I've been
in that room
many times.
I think it stopped when
I mentioned
the word Leviathan.
Which means that
we must've struck a nerve.
And in my experience,
that means that we're on
the right path.
Maybe. I mean,
they shut me down cold.
So we find a new way.
Pete, if we are right
about this,
this is a matter
of global security.
We cannot be concerned
about breaking the rules.
-Now, are you with me?
-Yeah.
Lead the way.
Why are his eyes
like that?
The Q-waves have
a direct effect on his irises.
The inkiness indicates
an irregular break.
Did Klaus hurt
the other prisoner
before his eyes turned?
Or after?
Before. Definitely before.
What if the act of violence
isn't a result
of Non Nocere failing?
What if the act itself
caused the failure?
His need to survive
clashed with his directive
to do no harm.
Klaus felt like his life
was in danger.
His brain adapted,
it evolved
to protect himself.
But now,
his survival instincts,
they're in overdrive.
You can fix it, right?
I mean, after all
you've done for us here,
now that I'm free
from fear and anger,
I'm finally enjoying life
and the community.
I forgot what it was like
to have friends.
Are you feeling okay after
what happened in the elevator?
Technology is
the greatest evil
mankind has ever faced.
See? Right there.
Oh, my God.
You're right.
Whoever that is, they're
wearing an Image Inducer.
But why would someone
imitate her?
You said she worked
at Obsidian North?
Let's get our hands on
Obsidian's personnel files,
see everyone she was
in contact with.
I expanded my search,
but no sign of Leviathan
anywhere within
a 300-mile radius.
Hmm. Perhaps, we can
try again later.
Oh, yeah. It's a little
unconventional, I know.
To go out wearing this face,
but I like it like this.
I'm just as much
J'onn J'onzz
the human as I am
the Martian Manhunter.
The last time I saw you,
you were wrestling with
your own sense of self,
burdened by the ghost
of your father.
But now...
You're finally in command
of who you are.
And you,
the last time I saw you,
you were engaged in
endless Martian civil wars--
Until your brother's
heroic return to Mars,
which was nothing
short of a miracle.
We're finally on the path
to peace because of him.
Because of you.
Well, I guess we were both
in different places back then.
But I gotta say,
I'm really glad
you're here now.
-Should we wake her, or--
-No, no, no. That's, uh...
That's just how
she works.
-I don't understand it.
Every time we try
to re-establish
Non Nocere in the subject,
his vitals spike
and his body's
overriding it.
It's like he's treating
my directive
like some kind of flu virus.
Try again.
We've already
given what we can.
Any more would kill him.
Uh, guys.
It's spreading.
Wait. I created
a safe environment,
free from outside predators
so that the prisoners
would be safe.
But when Klaus turned,
he became the predator,
triggering the survival
instincts in
the other inmate.
So, when he attacked
the other inmate
in the elevator--
A domino effect was born.
Evolution is a bitch.
Hello?
Get out of my dreams, Brainy.
Get out of my dreams!
Gotcha.
Mmm. Mmm.
Seriously, what do
you put in these things?
I can't stop eating them.
They're so good.
Crack.
Just kidding. But seriously,
um, I can't tell you.
Chef Emile would drag me
to patisserie prison
for even hinting at it.
So, I didn't find any
communication between
Margot and the Luthors.
But she did spend
a lot of time
talking to
this employee, 873.
No name.
Just a badge number.
Well, then let's find
this mysterious number 873.
Supergirl,
Dreamer just woke up
from a vision.
We believe Rama Khan
is at the Oregon Geological Monitoring Station.
We think he's gonna
trigger a massive earthquake.
Uh... Oh, shoot.
-Shoot. It's my sister's cat.
-Oh.
He got out again.
I gotta go.
I'll come with you.
Cats love me,
for some reason.
Of course they do.
Uh, but this one, he gets
real skittish around...
around tall guys with...
accents and...
and he bites.
Well, a shy biter. He...
You call Kelly
about number 873.
I'll be right back.
It's over, Rama Khan.
Oh, no.
It's just begun.
We're in a massive
subduction zone.
If it ruptures, the results
will be devastating.
Then we should
stop that from happening.
Director Dox,
we have reports that
Rama Khan has triggered
a massive seismic event
in Portland.
Supergirl and her allies
are already there, sir.
Should we provide backup?
Yes.
I think I can fix this.
I can reset everything
with a burst of Q-waves.
We just need to reconfigure
the Q-wave generator
in my office.
It's on the other side
of the prison.
All right.
Safety in numbers.
I'm coming with you.
Excuse me.
Lena, help!
Stop, please!
Oh, are you all right?
We need to get the staff.
It's enhancing his powers.
Supergirl,
we've stopped the quake.
We're gonna go put
the town back together.
Thank you for the assistance,
we'll take it from here.
Assistance?
We found him.
We get to question him first.
Absolutely not.
Leviathan is the DEO's
top priority.
No, Brainy, the DEO
might be compromised.
I have reason to believe
that Lex
has been working
with Leviathan.
You turn Rama Khan
into the DEO,
who knows
what Lex will do.
I'm sorry.
My decision is final.
Rama Khan comes with me.
So are we.
The Special Collections Room
is right here.
Okay.
Well, just keep watch.
I need a minute.
We only have one.
It's the 5:00 p.m.
shift change.
The new guard's gonna be
coming on duty any second.
- Run.
What's wrong?
It's just...
Something about that staff
is giving me bad vibes.
Hey, Brainy.
We need to find out
if Leviathan
has anything else planned.
I will.
You and Dreamer can watch
from the observation room.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
You said
I could go in there
with you.
I said you could come
to the DEO.
Look, this is a very
sensitive prisoner.
By my calculations,
any interrogation will be
85% more successful
without you in the room.
Brainy...
Are you really going
to shut us out like that?
Did you call me when you found
Rama Khan's location?
Did you?
Are you sure
this is a good idea,
leaving Brainy alone
in there with him?
No, I don't love it,
but it is Brainy's DEO.
Brainy was in
my dream of Rama Khan.
What was he doing?
He was playing games
with Rama Khan.
More like, Brainy was
using Rama Khan.
So, it's just you
and me now, Coluan.
You will tell me
what I want to know.
Your fellow Leviathan,
your headquarters,
your endgame.
And why would I do that?
How is my wife?
She's sure somebody's
watching the house.
Oh, God. I'm so sorry for
dragging you into all this.
No, I jumped willingly.
But I think I better keep
my head down for a bit.
I got a friend who's gonna get
my family and me off the grid.
You should think
about it, too.
Not until we bring
all of Leviathan down.
Alex...
For what it's worth,
you still sound like someone
who's a part of the military.
I get it.
Shifting to civilian life
can be hard.
It took me months, years.
Hell, if you ask my wife,
I still think I'm leading
a platoon of 20.
You get used to the
power of the uniform.
There comes a day
when you realize...
you gotta let it go.
Thanks again
for helping me out.
I know it goes against
Andrea's orders,
and I don't want to get you
in any more trouble.
All right, let's see
who you are,
Employee 873.
Eve Tessmacher.
Did you know her?
Oh, in another life.
And if she's still
who I think she is...
this is bad news.
Wait, what did he say?
That's not
a language I know,
or ever heard Brainy use.
Did he just say "Luthor"?
What is it?
Something's wrong.
Rama Khan's staff.
It's scanning the DEO
for something.
It's a trap!
Not so fast.
The prisoner has escaped.
Initiate Protocol Five.
Evacuate the DEO.
Enough!
And now to get
what I came for.
I can't find
the right frequency,
I need more time.
Back in a minute.
Gentlemen!
Shall we dance?
You're gonna have to do
better than that.
Steve!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Except...
What?
I feel like I used to feel.
The peace.
It's all gone.
Rama Khan! Over here.
M'gann! No!
Is everyone safe?
Everyone's fine.
But Rama Khan's gone.
We need to find him.
J'onn and M'gann are
out looking for him.
He could be
anywhere by now.
Well, then we'll
look everywhere.
We'll start at the Tower.
See if we can trace
his seismic signature.
-I'm needed here,
but I--
-Don't.
-Nia.
-No!
When you took off
your inhibitors,
I swore to be there for you
no matter what.
But, maybe I was wrong.
Because I don't know
who this Brainy is.
But, I know
I don't like him.
And I definitely don't
trust him.
Look...
I can't explain.
No more riddles.
What the hell were you doing
in there with Rama Khan?
What was that language?
And what did Lex Luthor
have to do with it?
Tell me.
Right here, right now.
I can't.
You can't play the game
from both sides, Brainy.
You can't pretend to be
on our side one minute
and then push us away
the next.
If you can't pick a side,
I'll choose one for you.
And this is who?
She apparently
has a list of names
and identities...
Her real name
is Eve Tessmacher
and she's a very
dangerous individual.
Well, it says here,
we hired her
on direct, personal
recommendation of
Gemma Cooper,
our board chair
and my friend.
No criminal record,
no black marks
on her file,
practically
a model citizen.
I don't know
what kind of game
you two are playing,
coming to me with these
concerns based on nothing.
But I've worked too hard
to get this company
to where it is
to lose momentum now.
If you can't find it in you
to get fully behind
Obsidian Worldwide's
Unity Festival,
then perhaps,
you should consider
finding the door.
Peace at last.
It took a bit of persuading,
but the prisoners have been
pacified and neutralized.
They're ready for
the next round.
Non Nocere is dead.
It doesn't work.
It can't.
It never could.
Pain is a necessary part
of being human, of life.
And I was delusional
to think
that I could save people,
or fix it.
Humanity will always try
to protect itself, to evolve.
You can't stop that.
You saw Steve,
how helpless he was,
all because of me.
I was rooting for you, Lena.
But,
I have to agree.
Humanity can't be fixed.
They need to be controlled.
Leviathan may be
our biggest threat,
but they were right
about one thing.
Humanity needs a firm hand
to guide it.
To lead it.
And not some
arrogant alien.
It needs to be human.
You mean, a Luthor.
Think of all that we could
accomplish together,
if we just take our rightful
place as humanity's saviors.
Saviors?
Of course.
You never change.
This was always
all about you,
your megalomania.
You... knew my plan
wouldn't work,
that it was doomed.
You were counting on it.
How dare you?
I gave you the world.
Everything.
I supported you.
I sabotaged nothing,
touched nothing.
I set aside my own goals
for you.
Because you needed to see
your little project fail
with your own eyes.
To know the true depravity
of humanity.
To know that my way
was the only way.
You're a monster.
But that doesn't mean
I have to be one, too.
We've lost the DEO,
we've lost Brainy.
Leviathan has Kryptonite.
Without Lena to build
me a Kryptonite suit,
I have nothing.
We still have each other.
And we will stop them.
Go home.
We'll deal with this
in the morning.
M'gann.
I can't find Rama Khan's
energy signal.
I've lost his trail.
Listen, listen, listen.
I nearly lost you
out there today.
-I'm just not sure I can--
J'onn.
It's okay.
- Hey.
-Hi.
How did it go with Pete?
Oh.
Not so good.
Um, we were ambushed
by Leviathan.
Wait, what?
Pete's okay.
It's fine. I just...
Look, I made a mistake.
I just...
I pressed and I put him
in danger.
I just...
I'm not used to
being so exposed.
And now with the DEO,
it's gone...
I'm so sorry.
Oh, and speaking
of exposed,
William and I discovered
that Eve Tessmacher
has been working
for Obsidian.
Have you talked
to Andrea?
She didn't care.
In this world
there is no record
of Eve being anything
but perfect.
She threatened to fire me
if I came to her again.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
So, what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna leave Obsidian?
No.
No. That'll make it
much harder
to get to the bottom of this.
I just...
I've got to get better
at hiding.
Maybe you should, too.
What do you mean,
like, wear a mask?
It worked for my brother.
If you're going to be
a vigilante,
you might as well
go all the way.
Mr. Luthor?
We got the prisoners
back in their cells.
What do you want us
to do with them?
Burn it.
Just the person I was
hoping to hear from.
Did you get my gift?
Oh, yes.
I am very grateful.
How grateful?
Regarding your request
to meet my colleagues,
I'll send you a car
tomorrow morning.
Well, now I'm grateful.
See you tomorrow.
Eventful day, Director Dox?
I know. I disobeyed
your direct order.
I interfered with Leviathan
and the Supers.
I am responsible.
For everything.
Oh, Dox.
Of course, I knew that
you'd rush in
to help your little friends.
You're all gooey hero
on the inside.
I don't have to be a genius
to know that.
But don't worry.
Everything is right on track.
Even the loss of the DEO
is a tax write-off.
You wanted Rama Khan
to be brought here.
To get the Kryptonite.
I gave Leviathan
a little trinket
from the Fortress that,
with Kryptonite,
will make Supergirl's life
miserable.
And they were
very appreciative.
You got an invite
to the ship.
I told you,
trust the process,
save the world.
Get some sleep.
Big day tomorrow.
I have made
a terrible mistake.
I was hurt.
I was so hurt. And...
I thought I could
get rid of the hurt.
I thought that
I knew better,
that I could make
the world
a better place.
But I was wrong.
That hurt, um,
took me down
a dark, dark path,
where I was
blind to what I was
really doing,
to what I'd become.
You were right.
This whole time
I became a villain,
and then...
I'm not looking
for forgiveness.
I know what I said
and I know what I did,
but I am...
I am really hoping that you
will believe me right now.
Okay?
Lex is working
with Leviathan,
and they are going
to use Obsidian
to do something terrible...
using the system,
that I made
with my project.
I didn't know I was
helping them, but I did.
And...
now I want to help
stop them, so...
Please, okay?
I want to help stop
Lex and Leviathan.
Sit down.