Previously on
Supergirl...
I'm sorry, who are you?
Andrea Rojas.
I sold CatCo
to Andrea.
Tomorrow,
we'll be joined by
the renowned
William Day.
From
The Times of London?
I quit.
But I have a calling, Hope,
and it's to fix mankind.
I never thought Supergirl
would tell me who she was,
but now that she has,
I have an opportunity,
and I can use Supergirl
to achieve my ends.
Who are you?
You don't recognize me.
Brother.
♪ Stop me on the corner
-♪ I swear you hit me
Like a vision ♪
♪ I, I, I wasn't expecting
♪ But who am I to tell fate
♪ Where it's
Supposed to go with it? ♪
♪ Don't you blink
You might miss it ♪
♪ See we got a right...
Thank you, Supergirl.
Yeah.
That woman shouldn't
have been texting and walking.
...as citizens
of National City
prepare to head
to the ballot box
for the upcoming midterms.
Obsidian North contact lenses,
they let you do you,
whenever, wherever,
and whatever you want.
Seriously?
As if you weren't
amazing enough,
you're also a gourmet chef?
Hardly.
But I am famous
-for this breakfast
in particular.
-Oh.
So, we have poached eggs,
crispy bacon,
fresh whipped cream,
and...
Danvers'
blueberry pancakes.
-Um...
-I know, right?
One bite of these
and you will die for them.
I really will.
What's wrong?
I'm not the biggest fan
of blueberries.
-Oh!
-In fact, I'm deadly allergic.
You are?
When I was four,
I ate a handful of them,
and my throat closed up,
and my face probably turned
the color of those blueberries.
Oh, my God.
I... I am so sorry.
It's okay. I was four.
No, but I nearly
just killed you.
Okay, you didn't
just kill me,
and I always carry
an emergency EpiPen with me.
Really?
I didn't know that.
Hey, it's all good.
Also, bacon and whipped cream
happen to be two of
my most favorite foods
on the planet.
So, you don't really like
poached eggs either, do you?
Not so much.
But do you know
what I like more than anything?
Mmm-mmm.
You.
Okay.
Thank you.
I need breakfast.
And coffee.
Yes, this is your pattern,
which is why
I've prepared accordingly.
Breakfast burritos!
With chorizo and crema,
as you like.
Plus your nitro-coffee with
an extra shot of cold brew.
This is
the best morning ever.
"Best morning ever"?
But that would include eons,
both before and after
this moment.
I really think
you're misusing the ter--
Message received.
I can't believe
I didn't see it before.
Andrea bought CatCo
to get free global advertising
for Obsidian North.
And then this morning
on the jumbotron
an important story about
the election
was swallowed up
by a gigantic
Obsidian commercial.
-It's...
Well, speaking of
the upcoming election,
I got some interesting news
last night.
I got a call
from a group of people
who want to back me
for senator.
Senator?
-Yeah.
-That's incredible.
I never imagined
going into politics.
Are you kidding me?
We would all be lucky
to have you in Washington.
I also have an offer to be
the media director
at the Smithsonian.
Uh, so how long has it been
since you left CatCo,
what, 12 hours? That's...
That's the universe telling me
I'm on the right path.
Uh, well, I think
the universe is just telling me
that I have to keep
my spirits up
and fight the good fight.
Your spirits
do seem remarkably high
for someone who strongly
dislikes her new boss.
Well, that's thanks to Lena.
I don't think I realized
how burdened I was
by lying to her.
And now that she knows
I'm Supergirl,
and she's forgiven me,
I feel 1,000 pounds lighter.
Like I can do anything.
Bring it!
J'onn, we got you a latte.
Oh, my God.
J'onn?
-J'onn!
Well, this should help
take away the pain temporarily.
I don't understand.
You think that
whoever did this to you
was also the person
that released Midnight?
Yes.
He said
he was my brother.
At first, I didn't believe him,
but now I know it must be true.
How do you know?
This is specifically
a Martian form of agony.
In the early days of Mars,
there were two brothers:
Phobos and Deimos.
Their rivalry and bloodshed
was the reason for
the split of the Green
and White Martians.
To prevent this
ever happening again,
a curse was placed on
the Green Martians.
We called it Fa'ra'too'rik.
It is the punishment for
brother attacking brother.
But you've never even mentioned
having a brother.
I never knew of one.
Seems unthinkable.
But perhaps his existence
was hidden from me
by my parents.
And hidden by
the entire Martian community
by their hive mind?
We're going to find him,
but first we need
to deal with your pain.
There is no cure for this
on this planet.
There is in the future.
We treat afflicted Euphorians,
an alien race with similar
brain structure to Martians,
with Q-waves.
They are narrow waveforms
that exist between
X and gamma rays.
You haven't heard of them
because Q-waves
don't get discovered
until sometime
in the late dark ages.
Actually, Kelly's been
using Q-waves
as part of her
brain computer interface
at Obsidian.
Well, no time like the present
to create the future.
Oh...
Nia?
Kara,
you need
to get here immediately.
Ms. Rojas is on a rampage,
and she won't start
the editorial meeting
until everyone's present.
I'm on my way.
-You guys get J'onn to Kelly.
-Okay.
And I'll have the DEO
start a broadband scan
for Green Martians ASAP.
J'onn,
we're going to
find your brother.
Who hurt you?
I went to see my brother.
He struck at me
and inflicted us both with
the sting of Fa'ra'too'rik.
I cannot cure your affliction,
but I will do what I can
to ease your suffering,
old friend.
Once I am able,
I will tear this new family
of J'onn J'onzz's apart,
for both of us.
Hope?
Good morning,
Ms. Luthor.
Is it morning?
I lost track of time.
I had an epiphany last night.
There's something
in these lenses
of the Obsidian technology
that's going to allow me
to change the course
of humanity.
That is
an exciting agenda.
What is
your scientific hypothesis?
Hope, could you hurt someone?
I am incapable
of causing pain.
It is against
my prime directive.
Exactly.
Because you were built
in the very image
of perfection.
You have
no selfish inclinations.
Your base code is morality,
empathy, and logic.
Humans and aliens,
however, are flawed.
They are driven
by their emotions.
They lie, cheat,
and hurt each other
to protect themselves.
But it's not their fault,
it's just
how they're programed.
I am going to make them better
with Project Non Nocere.
Do no harm.
I'm going to rid humanity
of its instincts
to hurt each other.
But you cannot reprogram
organic creatures.
The VR lenses create a link
between what we want
and what we see,
constructing a blank slate
in the brain
on which
a new world can be projected.
If I can find the source
of that link,
I can redirect the blank slate
to have one single rule.
Non Nocere.Do no harm.
Is there anything I can do
to assist you in this endeavor?
You will eventually,
but right now,
I need more resources.
The subject
is gaining consciousness.
Good.
I'm ready for her.
How did you sleep?
Kara!
Nia. There you are.
We can finally get started.
What's this?
A gift! From Obsidian North.
From now on
all work will be filed
through a portal
only accessible
through these tablets.
Thanks, boss.
At The Timeswe were lucky
if we got a legal pad.
Didn't you say
your wife was a lawyer?
Shouldn't you have a house
filled with legal pads?
Yeah. Right.
Which just makes this
all the more special.
Now,
for writing assignments,
I need interesting takes.
Kara,
you're on the fashion beat.
Um... That's not
really my style.
Style? Cute.
You're witty.
I thought it would be
meta for you to cover
the "Who wore what?"
to your Pulitzer party.
I think I'd actually
prefer to do something
a little more...
Elitist? Yes, we all know that
you can do
highbrow journalism.
I want to see
how low you can go.
It'll be good for you
to stretch that muscle.
Well, I'm always looking
to stretch my craft.
In fact, I, uh...
I may have a beat on
a new senate candidate.
Maybe I can get us
an exclusive,
have them announce
their race on our website.
That is a good story.
So, you know what I think?
I think you should do both.
But mine first.
And I want it on my desk
by lunch.
Thank you.
Um... I actually don't know
if I have time, but...
Here you go.
Okay, we're gonna go slow.
And I'm going to be here
monitoring your brain activity
and your vitals
the whole time.
And James is right outside,
if we need anything.
All right.
-Initiating energy cycle.
Q-wave protocol initiated.
Please... Please let me go.
I know that you're mad at me,
but just know that
I would be the most loyal
to you, if you let me live.
Okay, I'm not mad at you.
-Then why am I here?
-Why did you betray me?
I swear I didn't want to,
and that's true. It's just...
-They made me do it.
-Who is they? Lex's cronies?
I can't.
-They're everywhere.
-All right.
Blame the bogeyman.
Please, if they even think that
I told you, they will kill me,
and they will kill you too.
Why should I believe
anything you say?
Because it's true.
They recruited me
when I was 16.
Same year my parents died.
I was already in college.
I had so much debt.
They said
they could fix everything.
All I had to do
was work for them.
-And betray me.
-No!
I hated doing it.
It hurt me every time.
Eve, I asked you
a question.
My mother always said
actions speak
louder than words.
And I was there, Eve.
I was on the other side
of that gun you pulled,
and I looked down the barrel,
and I knew,
that you would've shot me.
So don't tell me
that you didn't have a choice.
There is always a choice,
and you always chose
the same thing.
You betrayed me
because you wanted to.
You liked the power
that it gave you.
So, if you want me
to trust you,
try telling the truth for once.
Hey, Alex, I'm so sorry.
I think I'm stuck here
until I'm done
with these assignments.
Andrea's been
all over me today.
But the second you get a hit,
I'll blow out of here. Okay.
Nia?
Hey!
Whoa.
You have a bento box fort.
Yup, yeah, I do.
-Can I have some?
-Yes!
-I'm starving
-Yes, please, take them all.
I'm still stuffed
from breakfast.
Let me guess. Is this Brainy?
This morning, he brought me
my favorite breakfast,
and it was perfect.
I don't know,
isn't this a little excessive?
Maybe giving food
is Brainy's language
of love. I don't know.
Well, I think
I just need to tell him
in plain English
that this is 35 boxes of sushi
too much love.
Yeah, that sounds
like a very healthy
and mature thing to do.
But I'm going to enjoy this
while it lasts.
All right. Well...
Great.
More reason
to get this done quickly.
I just reconfigured
all possible energy signatures
based on J'onn's DNA.
Mmm. You really are
on top of it all, Brainy.
I really am, aren't I?
I began this morning
by executing
a perfect breakfast
for Nia Nal.
She called it
"the best morning ever."
And as of 10 minutes ago,
she's having
an even better afternoon.
She is welcome.
You see, the key
to a good relationship
is knowing each other fully.
Hmm, I don't know
if that's really true.
Your voice just went up
two octaves.
Is everything all right?
Everything is great.
Except I almost kind of
poisoned Kelly this morning,
but it was
just a silly mistake.
Sounds like a deadly mistake.
I didn't know
she was allergic
to blueberries.
Okay?
How could I?
She never told me that.
And then I started thinking,
"Okay, well, what else
hasn't she told me?
What else might I
accidently kill her with?"
Because
I really like her, Brainy,
like, like a lot.
And I don't want to kill her.
You and Kelly are still in the
"getting to know you" stage.
Okay, but that's what
I'm talking about.
When did this happen?
When did my feelings for Kelly
get so strong,
and how could I possibly
feel this way
about somebody
that I barely know?
From what I've learned,
the heart
is not logical.
Okay, we're going to
40 biohertz now.
Q-wave protocol initiated.
Turn it off.
What's going on?
Pain has just got worse.
Oh, there's something off
on your scan.
Okay, part of what
this tech does
is it maps and catalogs
your memories.
Okay, these rings represent
every year of your life.
Think of them like tree rings.
You see these? They're broken.
Have you ever had illness
or brain trauma before?
I've had many battles.
Didn't you also inherit
Myr'nn's memories?
Maybe that's causing
a rift in your own?
Okay. We should
rule out everything.
And if you want,
we can further
explore the breaks.
It might help us figure out
a better way
to stop your pain.
Whatever you think will help.
Okay.
I'm gonna go in with him,
make sure nobody
interrupts us.
-Got it.
-Okay.
Ready?
Initiating...
Pushing to 60 biohertz now.
First, we build.
I find it's easiest
for patients to create a method
for organizing their memories.
Imagine somewhere familiar.
You see how some of
these spines are blank?
This must have been the breaks
that I saw on the scan.
Battle of L'Zoril M'nt.
Battle of C'arel.
These are battles
of the Martian Civil War.
There's something about...
this one.
I've never seen this before.
It's Martian.
What do you think
that void means?
Someone wiped my mind.
I just located J'onn's brother,
five miles from here.
Great.
Get everyone out there,
I'll call Supergirl.
Hey...
Alex. Hey.
Sure. I just...
It's him?
Don't make contact with him
until I'm there.
Yeah. I'll sneak out of here
and meet you.
Where you going?
Everything okay?
It's a family emergency.
Hey.
I know the NSA
doesn't do this anymore,
but you owe me a favor.
I need you to track
someone in National City.
Last name Danvers,
first name Kara.
Glad to see you've escaped
your tower, Rapunzel.
Yeah, and into a sewer.
Where's J'onn's brother?
Who would mind-wipe you?
Only another Martian
would be strong enough.
But wiping a Martian's mind
is the greatest sin
in Martian culture.
Well, we could
rebuild your memory
based on what you already know.
Repairing the break
could also help ease your pain.
I'm not sure I can face
what's inside that void.
J'onn...
I... I know
that looking into your past
can be terrifying.
When I did it,
I thought I might
lose myself for good.
But Kelly was right by my side,
and I came back stronger.
Give me those contacts.
Brainy,
are we close
to J'onn's brother?
There seems to be interference
with the signal.
What kind of interference?
It's unclear.
There's something else
in here too.
Are you sure
this is where Kara Danvers is?
Yep. That's where she is.
What are you doing here?
Get out! Now!
Remember, this world
is a construct.
Nothing in here is by accident.
The book
that led you to the void,
you said it was about
the Martian Civil War?
It was the darkest moment
in Martian history.
In fact, it ended our history.
The White Martians attacked us,
sabotaging us on every front.
Including our minds.
How did they sabotage you?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
That's him.
Don't hurt them.
My brother was a traitor.
He poisoned us
with H'ronmeer's Curse.
We went before
the High Council.
Malefic betrayed us,
worked with the White Martians to poison our people.
He is not one of us.
Send him to the Phantom Zone.
You are still in the dark,
Brother.
Q-wave protocol completed.
The pain...
It's gone.
Thank you, Brother.
Alex, watch out.
It's J'onn's brother.
No!
He's gone.
That was Kelly on the phone.
J'onn's okay. His pain is gone.
Well, that's a relief.
Are you finding anything?
Negative.
I lost his signal
when he and the White Martian
phased out of the sewer.
I will reconfigure
his signature
to include both Green
and White Martian energy.
Great, then we'll
get back to the DEO.
-Wow! I'm sorry.
-What?
-You smell.
But you smell of sewer.
Maybe a change of clothes
could help.
Wow.
He's not wrong about the smell.
Okay. Well, y'all smell, too.
How about that?
Worry not, the work is handled.
-Oh, hey, Nia. What is it?
Kara, Ms. Rojas is furious.
Where are you?
On my way.
I'll stay with J'onn tonight,
in case his brother comes back.
But I have to do
some damage control
-at CatCo first.
-Okay.
Kara. It's after lunch,
and I haven't even received
your first article yet.
I was just about to file that.
William already did.
He wrote my article?
And it's excellent,
I may add.
Perhaps the transition is
harder on you than I thought.
Our copy editing staff
is a little shorthanded.
Maybe you can help them out.
I'm... I'm not a copy editor.
A beginner's mind
is a Zen mind.
Really?
Broken?
Intentionally?
And you're certain
it's that user?
I'll handle it.
The pile on the right
is for you.
Don't ever steal
one of my stories again.
Hey, I did you a favor.
Yeah? What kind of
twisted logic is it
that makes you think that
by stealing one of my bylines
you're doing me a favor?
And tattling on me?
What are you, five?
Maybe if you focused
on the work actually
assigned to you,
you wouldn't have this problem.
Well, maybe if you supported
your fellow journalists
instead of competing with them
you wouldn't be such a jerk.
Do I look like a guy
who does charity?
You want someone
to look out for you?
Look somewhere else.
Well, since you enjoy
doing my work so much,
have at it.
I've been thinking about
what you said.
You're right.
I wasn't motivated by fear
or blackmail.
Every decision that I made,
every crummy thing
that I did to you,
to everyone, I wanted to do it.
I liked doing it.
Lena.
Andrea? How did
you get down here?
Oh, your assistant
is my best friend's girlfriend.
Cute couple.
Surprised you didn't know.
You shouldn't
underestimate me, Lena.
Do you really think
that I don't know when someone
is trying to steal my IP?
You put trackers in the lenses.
And you shattered it,
along with
the Lumus pixellator.
But you already knew that.
That's what you were trying
to anatomize, wasn't it?
You know, I really thought
more of you, Lena.
Caught trying to steal
my technology?
How embarrassing for you.
What would
your shareholders think?
Or the world?
Oh, and I ran diagnostics
before you...
shattered these.
I know how valuable
they are to you.
How many hours
you've spent in them.
You're cut off.
You won't get
another pair from me.
Keep screwing with me,
and you won't
just owe me a story.
You'll be the story.
Lena.
I could have called for help,
and all of this would have been
over in one minute.
But I didn't.
Because I meant what I said.
You can trust me.
Yes,
it appears that I can.
No matter how I reconfigure
the Green Martian
energy signature,
I cannot get a hit
besides J'onn J'onzz himself.
Thank you.
Nia!
You are welcome.
I assume you received
the pizza delivery.
Thank you
for the pizzas
but my dress is bursting
at the seams,
and I'm pretty sure
I have heartburn.
Hmm, yes. My heart also burns.
You're not listening to me.
But this morning you said,
"I love this."
Remember "Best morning ever"?
I... I did, I do.
I just...
I appreciate all the stuff
you're doing to make me happy.
But I love lots of things.
I love...
stupid buddy comedies
and Taylor Swift,
and quiet nights,
and poetry,
and just spending time
with you.
I love that, too.
So you'll chill on the food?
Indeed.
But just to be clear,
chill doesn't mean
you want gelato
or a nice chilled
shrimp cocktail, correct?
No more food. Hot or cold.
I'm sorry about
your brother.
Here.
Thank you.
Knowing now
that I am tied to someone
who betrayed my people
so violently
is, uh, unsettling.
And it makes me worry.
If this memory
was taken from me,
what else might I not know
about myself,
good or bad?
Well, you have us,
and we know you.
Thank you.
And I appreciate you
letting me be here.
But shouldn't you be working?
Oh, please.
You are a welcome distraction.
Andrea is gunning for me,
and that William guy...
I mean,
who does he think he is?
I caught him following me.
Following you?
Did you confront him?
No. I couldn't.
I was Supergirl.
But he is sneaky.
And I think
he's trying to sabotage me.
He just rattles
around the office
with his smug
British accent. And...
You know who I feel bad for?
His wife,
'cause she's stuck with him.
J'onn, I don't know
how much longer
I can last at CatCo.
The Kara Danvers I know
is not a quitter.
If someone's trying to
sabotage you,
you just ignore them.
They're spending
all their energy on you,
you spend yours
on being the best you.
Kelly? Hey!
Did I leave the door unlocked?
Yep.
Oh, geez.
Uh, I'm gonna put on
a sweater real quick.
You open the wine.
To a successful day.
Ugh.
To an exhausting day.
And, um...
Thank you so much
for helping J'onn.
You really are
a miracle worker.
It was nothing.
You're the real hero.
Almost catching
J'onn's brother.
I feel like I barely understand
what you guys do.
How did you
manage to track him?
You know what...
Let's not order in.
I still have some of that
blueberry pancakes batter
in the fridge,
so how about I whip
some of those up?
Sounds good.
You're not my girlfriend.
You killed my comrade.
-It's Alex.
She's in trouble.
We gotta go.
Alex?
Hey, I got your signal.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, I must have just bumped it.
What did you do with Alex?
Oh...
Humans are so fragile,
aren't they?
That wasn't very nice.
I got this.
You go get my brother.
I'm going to help those people.
Why are Alex
and Supergirl fighting?
That's not Alex,
that's my brother.
Alex may still be inside.
I'm gonna go find her.
- Move,
move, move, move!
Let's go! Let's go!
Alex?
Alex, wake up.
-Wake up, Alex.
-Don't touch me.
-Hey, it's me. It's me.
It's you. Okay.
It's you.
Okay.
We have to get out of here.
We gotta go.
Okay.
Wait. There's a fire
in the stairwell.
I barely made it up here.
Okay. We can get out
through the roof.
Okay, go.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Alex, it's me.
Alex, listen to me.
Just hold us both here
until help comes.
No. He's just trying to escape.
Shoot him.
No!
No.
Well, the building's all right.
Everything's sound.
But I can't speak
for your reputation
with your neighbors
or Mr. Nelson's
melted pint of Rocky Road.
So, that was your brother,
the traitor?
Yes.
I'm afraid
this is far from over.
When our minds were joined,
Malefic said
I was still in the dark.
Perhaps if I could access
more of my memories,
I might be able to uncover
what his next move will be.
Kelly, do you think
we could go deeper
with Obsidian's tech?
Perhaps turn the energy
up to 80 biohertz?
That kind of power
could reset your brain
for good.
We can't take that chance.
All right.
William?
You're here late.
Working on a new
extracurricular story?
No. Actually, I'm just here
to do my job.
That's a nice change.
You know what?
I see you.
You're a saboteur.
You bring other people down
to make you look better.
And maybe that's how
you've made it this far,
but that's a rotten way
of making it to the top.
So you can try
to get me in trouble
and steal my stories,
but while you're busy plotting
and undermining me,
I'm going to be doing my job,
with heart and integrity,
and I'm gonna be doing it well.
Nothing says sorry
for the terror like cookies.
Oh, hey,
I got you a little gift.
Oh!
So this
is the list of my allergies.
Blueberries, hazelnuts,
bees, and cats.
This is very helpful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You know, I...
I realized that my spiral
this morning
about the blueberries
wasn't really about
the blueberries.
What do you mean?
We haven't been together
for very long,
so, you know,
it just made me realize
how much we still don't know
about each other.
And, you know, I really
frickin' like you like a lot.
And so...
That scared me.
Alex, you're safe with me.
I know that now.
Earlier when I...
When I touched her hand,
I knew that wasn't you.
Because you can't fake
how that feels.
Just like you can't fake
being who you are.
So, on that rooftop,
when you made
that very selfless choice,
I knew exactly in that moment
which one of you was my Kelly.
And I might not know
every little detail
about you yet,
but I know you.
Aw!
-So sweet.
-Isn't it?
- Dearest, Nia...
"Shall I compare thee
to a summer's day?"
Brainy, wha...
Why are you doing all this?
Nia, I heard you
loud and clear.
From now on I will shower you
with poetry.
Oh!
Have no fear.
Even without spicy tuna,
I will venture to make each day
the best day ever.
Which is theoretically
impossible.
But...
you make me want to do
the impossible.
Brainy you are
adorable.
But sometimes
you are the dumbest
smartest person I know.
Thank you.
Eve, I've decided
that it's time
to fill you in on
what I've been doing.
You will not
regret this, Ms. Luthor.
You can count on me.
For real this time.
I must admit, I had my doubts.
But now I know that
there are aspects
of your brain that I need.
And now that I know
that I can trust you,
I believe you and I
are going to do
great things together.
Eve,
meet Hope.
You two are going to be
working closely together.
How so?
Well, first, Eve,
we need to evolve you,
and you yourself said that
you wanted to be better.
I promise you,
you will not feel a thing.
You've been mapping my mind?
I needed to locate
and highlight
the centers of your brain
that trigger
honesty and loyalty.
Why?
So Hope knows where to go.
"I didn't develop
a sense of smell
until the tender age of 14."
Kara, have you finished
editing, yet?
I have.
I also sent you 11 pitches
ahead of tomorrow's meeting,
all with eye-grabbing headlines
and image options.
Well,
I look forward
to discussing them tomorrow.
Don't be late.
Without the powers
that were stolen from me
in the Phantom Zone,
the power to incept,
there's no way I can defeat
my brother and his friends.
You listen,
but you do not hear.
That woman gave you the answer.
That kind of power
could reset your brain
for good.
Reset your brain.
Hope?
Good morning, Ms. Luthor.
Since Andrea Rojas
took my lenses,
we need a new plan.
Luckily she confirmed
my hypothesis
about the interworking
of her technology.
This pleases you.
We don't need Andrea's tech.
With your help,
I can build my own.
And together
we can rebuild humanity.