Previously on
Supergirl...
It was me.
I erased my own brother
from our minds.
You lied.
I think you know more about
the Jarrod story
and for some reason
you don't want me on it.
You asked me
to be completely
myself with you.
I can only operate at 100%.
My brother now has
the power to incept.
Make you do the things
he wants you to do
against your will.
The Q-waves somehow
forged a link between
Kelly's mind and Malefic's.
She could see him,
even when he shapeshifted.
We need
to get Kelly to safety.
You should leave tonight.
Take this.
It's one of Lex's
transmatter portal watches.
If you need it,
use it.
You cannot run, human.
I'm no human, brother.
What do you know
of hurt?
When the ones you love
turn their back on you,
that's pain.
But you'll see,
when you suffer
the way you made me suffer.
You can't touch me
without hurting yourself.
That's why he brought me.
We came prepared.
You can't incept
any of us now.
Don't be so sure.
Agent Blake?
-J'onn, now.
-Hey, you okay?
-Yeah.
-We'll be at
Aunt Vi's in a few.
You know, coming here
after dad died,
that's what saved me.
I don't know what
would've happened
if Aunt Vi
hadn't taken us in.
I know.
My God,
what happened to this place?
Is that a prison?
That's definitely new.
Step forward, please.
Eyes straight ahead.
The Martian protocol
is in place.
At least Malefic
won't get in here.
Hey, Brainy.
What the hell happened?
Malefic should have not
been able to phase through
the Phantom Zone projector.
And our psychic inhibitors,
he fried them.
Malefic's brain is unlike
any other Green Martian.
I tried to calibrate both
to his unique physiology, but--
That was our one shot
at tricking him.
He could be after
the real Kelly,
my Kelly right now.
We are not
gonna let that happen.
There's gotta be another way
we can track him.
Something we're missing.
What did he yell
at you, J'onn?
Synd'ar'k?
Uh, I don't know.
It's, um, it's a dialect
I've not heard before.
We can't afford
any more missteps.
I'm having the Verdex Blaster
brought up from the armory.
-What?
-Alex.
That Verdex Blaster
was designed by Hank Henshaw
to kill Green Martians,
specifically me.
It's a last resort.
Hank Henshaw was wrong
about you,
but Malefic is exactly
the kind of Martian
that this blaster
was designed for.
Hang on, wait, wait, wait.
Let's not rush into this.
Because if we had had
the Verdex Blaster,
Malefic could've incepted
one of us to use it on J'onn.
Let's at least have
Brainy try to fix it first.
Okay.
Excellent. I shall adjust
the Phantom Zone
projector's wavelengths
so Malefic cannot
phase through it
while simultaneously
recalibrating the psychic
inhibitor frequencies
all to distract myself
from my broken heart.
- Uh, what?
- What?
Nothing. Why?
What did you hear?
Maybe we should call in Lena
for backup.
Nia, what's up?
I was doing some background
on William,
and guess whose marriage
to a successful lawyer
is a lie? His.
You know that picture of
his wife he keeps on his desk?
It's a stock photo
he got off the web.
And that article
Andrea cleared him
to write from London?
Well, I had a weird feeling
about it.
So I astral projected
and I followed him,
it was like something
out of a James Bond movie.
He got passed this newspaper
from some guy,
and now, all of a sudden, he's no longer going to London,
he's going to Mexico City.
-Who is this guy?
-Well, let's see,
he's a liar who
is literally made of shadows,
and now he's going south
to meet someone named
Elena Torres.
I think she might be
his next target.
Good work.
-It was Nia?
- Yes.
Yes, she has another
lead on William.
Another possible
assassination attempt.
Well, if you think someone's
life is at stake,
-then you should go.
-Are you sure?
-With Kelly?
-I'm sure.
Okay.
Wait, before...
Before you go.
Did Nia ask about me?
-Oh, God.
-Not that I care.
I mean, not that I don't care,
it's not a big deal.
Uh-huh.
I'll call Lena.
Of course, Alex,
I'll be right over.
I believe I've isolated
the problem, Ms. Luthor.
Lex's journals helped us
build the inception tuner
to implement thoughts
into the brain,
but the specific Q-wave
frequency is incorrect.
Unfortunately, that leaves us
with hundreds of thousands
of variables.
I may have
an expedited solution, Hope.
Alex has just asked me
to assist the DEO
in apprehending
a rogue Green Martian.
The brother of J'onn J'onzz?
Yes.
Apparently, he has
the ability to override
another person's thoughts
with his own.
Mind control.
Using Q-waves.
If we were able
to harness Malefic's abilities,
we could use them
to determine what frequency
is needed
to implant thoughts
into the brain.
The study and testing
would require us
to detain the subject.
I doubt Supergirl
or her friends would approve.
No.
I don't think they would.
At least
Aunt Vi's house
is the way I remember it.
- Malefic?
-Wait here.
Hey.
I saw some kids running
into the woods.
Were they stealing stuff?
I think they were
doing homework.
Why would anyone
want to kill her?
She was the lead accountant
for Obsidian Worldwide.
You mean, our parent company?
And William's.
Also, I tracked
that license plate number
you sent me
and got a hit back
courtesy of our friends
at the NCPD.
Meet Sergio Ramos,
known player
in Intergang, Mexico City.
Are you saying that
William is involved
with organized crime?
This is starting
to get a little
international assassin-y.
We need proof.
We have to find out
what he had on her.
What she had on him.
I want to remind you again.
This is liable to be
quite painful.
Until we calibrate
the Phantom Zone projector
to lock onto
a Martian energy signature,
regardless of
the Martian's density,
so they can't
phase through it.
I'm ready when you are.
Commencing phasing
at 25%.
Sprock, sprock, sprock.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
What went wrong?
It was too much,
too much, too much...
I'm almost done
reinforcing the psychic
inhibitors,
so I can help you,
if you want it.
I heard the scream.
What happened?
-How, how...
-Brainy?
Yeah, I'm...
I'll figure it out, all right?
I'll figure it all out.
I'm sorry, J'onn, we need
all of our options
on the table.
I'm prepping the blaster.
Alex.
Alex, please don't.
I don't...
I don't understand
why you are defending him.
He betrayed you
and all of the Green Martians
during the war.
They were slaughtered
because of him.
I'm just really sorry
he's doing this.
Well, you have nothing
to be sorry about.
Okay? This isn't your fault.
It's mine.
It is killing me
that Kelly is in danger
because of me and my job,
and I am terrified
that he is going to use me
somehow to get to her,
and I just keep praying
that she's safe.
I would never let
anything happen to her.
You can't. Promise that.
I know that you are trying
to make me feel better, I do.
-But I won't,
not until that monster
is taken care of.
You do what you need
to do to feel safe.
But I'm not giving up
on Brainy.
So much around here
has changed.
Oh, at least one thing
has changed for the better.
Nelson Stewart?
Isn't that the reporter
you interned for?
Nelson taught me
everything I know about
journalistic integrity.
Publisher? Yeah,
way to go, Nelson.
-That's what I'm talking about.
That's it,
I'm calling the cops.
-I'm gonna pay for it.
-Hey, get your hands
off of him.
-He was stealing.
-Last time I checked,
it wasn't stealing
when you're still in the store.
And besides, I asked him
to get it for me.
I'm paying for it.
Now give him back
the ravioli.
Thanks a lot, lady.
I met you, right?
You're one of the kids
from before
from the house.
Uh, yeah, so?
So, you have a name?
Simon Kirby.
It's nice to meet you, Simon.
I'm Kelly.
-I'm James.
-I know who you are.
I read the news,
CatCo. Guardian. Duh.
Uh, here's your food back.
-I'm gonna...
- Yeah.
So, my sister's planning
a homemade dinner tonight.
She's an awful cook.
You know, you'd be
doing me a solid
if you came by
and ate with us.
I broke into your house,
camped out
in your living room,
and I can make it up to you
by coming over
and eating bad food?
Yeah.
Misery loves company.
So...
What do you say?
Sorry.
It was open.
Elena Torres?
Don't take this personally.
Hey, you really
could've hurt that lady.
Supergirl?
I wonder,
do you need to breathe?
Alex?
Agent Sloan,
Supergirl's bringing
a prisoner in,
-prep a cell.
-Yes, ma'am.
Malefic.
You incepted someone
to bypass the Martian protocol.
-Put your gun down.
-You first.
That's better.
Now my brother's friend
is his enemy.
I tried grilling her
about William,
but she's not talking.
Any news on Malefic?
Nothing yet.
You sure you're okay?
I am, yeah, thanks.
Now it's time you learned
my brother's crimes.
Pizza will be ready
in a few.
That was so cool,
what you did for me
at the store.
Anyone would've done the same.
No, nobody would've done it.
Nobody risks their neck
for anybody around here.
But you did.
It was badass and selfless.
Is it supposed to do that?
-You okay?
What happened?
Nothing, I just... Headache.
Um, I'm gonna get some air,
will you watch the pizza?
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
Oh, it's not that bad.
I like it burned.
Good thing.
So how long you been
living in my aunt's house?
Couple of months.
Sometimes we crash
with friends,
sometimes we just camp out
in the woods.
Where are your parents?
Haven't seen my dad
since I was...
five?
My mom got busted
last winter
stealing a space heater
from the hardware store.
The judge wouldn't even
give her a chance to explain.
They gave her 10 years
for stealing a 30 buck heater.
Since when does petty theft
get you that kind of time?
It's a racket.
The cops, judges, lawyers,
everyone's in on it.
They keep the prison full,
the prison keeps
their pockets lined.
How's nobody
stood up against them?
Called these guys out?
Like who?
Nobody's gonna speak up
and risk themselves.
Anyways, you can't beat
the system,
so what's the point?
There is a point, Simon.
You have to stand up
and fight against injustice.
Everyone's just out
for their own skin.
It's the way it is.
Not on my watch.
Sprock.
I seem to have made the beam
more dense instead of less.
Let's go again.
Just give me
a minute.
Okay, J'onn, you can't
keep putting yourself
through this punishment.
- I'm fine.
-No.
You're not,
you can barely stand.
And we need you
at full strength
-for when we find your brother.
-I told you.
I will help Brainy,
so Alex doesn't have
to use the blaster.
Go clear your head.
Look, Brainy, I know
you haven't asked for help,
-but you're getting it anyway.
-No.
I need my mind consumed
with this problem,
so I don't think of Nia.
What happened
to your little boxes?
Little boxes
prevented me from
having a real relationship.
Unfortunately,
my unboxed self
does not make a particularly
good boyfriend.
So I have been analyzing
myself for days,
searching for a way
to modulate myself
for the woman I love.
Well, I'm not gonna give you
relationship advice.
But as a scientist,
you seem to be stuck
in an infinite loop,
and unless you can escape,
you're headed for a crash.
-That would be cataclysmic.
-So change a variable.
What's the one thing
you haven't tried yet?
Asking for help?
Will you he...
Will you help...
me?
Yes.
And I think a small dose
of that will go a long way
with Nia.
Okay, could you find me
a polarity tuner,
and we can get to work?
Hey.
Somebody get me
a photographer,
we got a celebrity
sighting here.
Nelson, what's up, brother,
how you doing?
-Jimmy Olsen.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I hope you're not
looking for a job,
we can't afford you.
No, I've actually come
with a story.
So I met this local kid
who says his mom is
serving 10 years
for petty theft?
So I did some digging,
and that prison in
your backyard
seems to have a lot of
people serving long sentences
for small crimes.
Yeah, people
have bad luck, I guess.
Bad luck?
It's prison corruption,
wouldn't you say?
It's, um,
it's complicated.
Look, I wish
I could help you, but--
You can help me, Nelson,
that's why I'm here.
Journalism's about
fighting for the little guy,
you taught me that.
It's your job to
point out corruption,
so what the hell's
going on here?
Things have changed
for some people.
Idealism doesn't
feed a family.
And this whole power
of the press thing,
it might work if you've got
the backing of
a media conglomerate
and a certain girl
with a cape.
But around here,
it doesn't mean anything.
Standing up for what's right
always means something.
Nelson.
That prison is stomping
on the neck of
this entire town.
It's also the only thing
that's keeping this town alive.
Look, I'd love to see these
bastards get what they deserve.
But if I call them out,
my advertisers,
they pull their money,
not only am I out of a job
but so are the
30 other people I employ.
Go back to National City.
I like to think of you there.
You know,
I'm just glad somebody
made it out of this town.
And I'm glad it was you.
Listen to this. So my contact
at the Mexico City Herald
said the morgue
had a discrepancy.
Elena's body was burned
beyond recognition,
but they were able
to use an incisor
to confirm ID and...
it wasn't a match.
Apparently, the body
they pulled from the car
had been dead for two weeks
and died of natural causes.
So they faked Elena's death?
Well, that sheds new light
on my news.
I ran the numbers
you found at Elena's apartment
by my accountant friend,
and it turns out it's linked
to an offshore bank account.
Someone's been funneling
money into it
for the past year,
and there are two names
listed on the ledger,
one is Elena's
and the other is anonymous.
Huh.
You think William?
Maybe.
Embezzlement,
is that what this is?
My friend says there's
an address listed
to the account,
but it's encrypted.
Let's call Brainy,
see if he can crack it.
Or I could
ask my friend to do it.
Are things still weird
between you guys?
He did seem a little off
this morning.
I was afraid
this would happen.
I thought that if I was just
honest with Brainy,
it would help solve
our problems,
but it's only
made things worse.
I know it's something that
we could work through together,
but he thinks that
it's his problem to solve,
and now he won't
even talk to me.
Well, you know how Brainy is,
sometimes human emotions
just throw him for a loop.
I think he just needs time,
and to realize
you're not going anywhere.
Okay.
So you get this back
to your friend,
see if she can unencrypt it.
I'm gonna get to the DEO.
Talk to Alex and J'onn,
see if there's any news
on the Malefic front.
Copy that, boss.
We are so close
to cracking this,
I can feel it.
On a clear day, you can see
the moons of Mars from here.
Today's not a clear day.
I found out
what you've done, J'onn.
You lied to all of us.
You put us in jeopardy,
so that you could
protect yourself.
Keep your secret safe.
That you mind-wiped
the existence
-of your own brother--
-Alex, I wanted to tell you,
but I was so ashamed.
I confided in you
how this was tearing me apart.
How I thought that
I was the one
putting Kelly in danger,
and you just stood there,
knowing that
it wasn't my fault.
That it was yours.
You had me convinced
that Malefic was the monster,
but he wasn't just some
bad guy coming after people.
He was some bad guy
that you created
coming after your family,
and again
you just stood there,
and you let us suffer
the consequences.
-I know.
-You may say
that you erased Malefic
to protect your family,
to protect Myr'nn.
Or you did it
because it was easier
-than helping him.
-No.
No, no.
Malefic isn't
the monster here, J'onn.
-You are.
Alex.
Yeah, okay, thanks.
-Hey, so...
The newspaper
might've been a bust,
but good news, the best lawyer
in National City
has decided
to take your mom's case.
For real?
Yeah, I wouldn't kid
about that.
And don't worry
about her fee.
-I'll cover it.
- Wow.
When do we meet her?
I could probably set up
a meeting with you guys
next week.
You mean, you won't be there?
Oh, no, no, I...
This was a visit, Simon,
I can't stay here.
Right.
Of course,
why would you?
This town is a hellhole.
Hey, no, no,
it's not like that.
It's cool.
I get it.
It's not your problem.
Thanks for the help
and the food.
-See you around.
- Hey.
Simon.
J'onn?
What is it?
Is it something
about Malefic?
Synd'ar'k.
A synd'ar'kis a sinner,
that's what Malefic
yelled at me.
I asked Nia to use
her dream power
to help me find
the truth about my brother,
about the mind wipe.
That's when we discovered...
My brother wasn't born evil.
He had a problem.
And we...
ostracized him.
I wiped Malefic's existence
from our minds.
It was me.
I did this.
I failed my people
more than once.
I'm failing you.
No, no, you've saved us
countless times.
I would've been dead
last year,
when the Earth was seeded
with Kryptonite,
if it weren't for you.
Still...
Wiping him
from our mind?
It's like I murdered
my own brother.
But you remember now.
You risked your own life
to find those memories,
and now you can find him
and make different choices.
It was so selfish of me to...
burden Nia
with my secret,
and keep this
from you and Alex.
But I'm glad Nia told her.
She deserves to know
the truth, and so do you.
It couldn't have been Nia,
she's been with me.
That was Malefic.
He incepted Alex.
I can't find Alex anywhere.
She turned off
her phone and her comms.
Where are we with
the Phantom Zone projector
and psychic inhibitors?
Reconfigured and recalibrated.
Supergirl, the Verdex Blaster
is missing
and the armory's cleared out
of anti-Martian artillery.
-It's all gone.
-We have to find Alex now.
There is a way.
I could try
and find her psychically.
Malefic's mind is poisonous
to all Green Martians.
Melding with Alex's
incepted mind
would allow Malefic
into yours.
It could hurt you.
All that matters
is finding Alex.
Alex.
Open your mind for me.
We are looking for you.
We need you to come home.
Please, Alex, answer me.
You did what
you could for him, James.
It wasn't enough.
I mean, when Simon says
it's not my problem,
maybe it should be.
I mean,
this kid's got nobody.
Hey, you okay?
I'm having...
visions.
I thought they were
in my head,
but whatever happened
at Obsidian,
it didn't just allow me
to see Malefic.
I think I'm connected
to him.
I think I can see
what he sees.
And he has Alex. We need to
go back to National City now.
We're not going back
to National City.
We came here
to get you away from Malefic.
James, when you put on
that Guardian suit,
do you think first?
Or do you see someone
in trouble and act?
-That's different.
-The hell it is.
We're going back now.
Damn it, Malefic,
where is she?
J'onn.
Meet me
at the planetarium.
Come alone.
Welcome to Mars,
home to one of the greatest civilizations.
Wiped out by
the Great Martian civil war.
One Green Martian now
lives on Earth among us.
The Martian Manhunter.
A coward who left his family
to face an agonizing death
and worse.
And he's come here
to pay for it.
Alex, please.
Alex.
I know my brother's
making you do this.
And if you can hear me,
so can he.
I never should have
banished you.
I know that now.
I've lived on Earth
for over 300 years.
But I never really found
true peace.
And I believe it's because
of what I did to you, Malefic.
You didn't betray us.
By aligning with
the White Martians,
we betrayed you.
We tried to fix you.
Change you.
When all along,
we should've accepted you.
I accept you now, brother.
-No!
-Yes.
You forced me
to look inside myself
and discover memories
I had erased.
You did it
to try and punish me.
But...
Don't you see you've given us
a second chance?
It's not too late
for us, brother.
It's not...
too...
-late.
-Oh, my God.
What have I done?
No!
On Mars, you had nothing
but cruelty for me.
Where did this love
and forgiveness come from?
From my family.
Family's supposed
to destroy you.
He was supposed
to come alone too.
This ends now, Malefic.
Tell that to my friends.
They've been incepted.
The shield matrix, J'onn.
Yeah, this dome won't last
with all the firepower.
What is that?
We are not going
to lose you again.
The roof.
If it collapses, then everyone
in here is gonna die.
Go. Kara, go.
J'onn, you gotta
get me out of this thing.
Kelly, you shouldn't
be here.
This is exactly
where I should be here.
-What the hell is that thing?
-Oh, my God.
A bomb. A hybrid of Tamaranean
and Pharoid technology.
It's synched
to Alex's molecular structure.
Supergirl,
can you hear me?
Yeah.
When the dome fails,
you and Guardian
gather all of
the stolen weapons.
Kelly, you're the only one
who can see him,
so find Malefic.
-J'onn.
-Do you trust me?
Yes.
Supergirl, now.
It's Malefic
in the blue jacket.
So Malefic's
back in the Phantom Zone?
I'm sorry that
you couldn't save him.
J'onn, I know that that's
what you wanted to do.
But I heard everything
that you said to him.
I just wish
he could've taken it in.
But maybe now
that I remember,
I have a chance to make
things right at some point.
How could you ever think
that I would say those things
or think those things
about you?
I guess because I thought
those things about myself.
Well, I remember you
telling me once that
true character reveals itself
in times of hardship.
And I know who you really are.
We couldn't have
done it without you.
Please, I barely
did anything.
What? You fixed
the inhibitors
and the projector.
It did feel good.
You and me working
together as a team.
-Now that I know
who you actually are.
Well, get used to it,
because you are now
officially a Superfriend.
We have T-shirts
and a handshake.
-I'll teach it to you.
It's not a big deal.
It's a whole thing.
We're going out to get drinks
tonight, do you wanna come?
Oh, I would love to,
but I have been here all day,
so I really should
get back to L-Corp.
Of course. No rest
for the world-saving genius.
Since Malefic is gone,
how about less fighting
on the frontlines
and more...
cuddles and Netflix?
Okay, yeah, I'm in.
Please, take this as a token
of my deepest apologies.
Brainy, this is perfect.
I do not know when or how
I will find a way to be myself,
and yet not succumb
to my more obsessive qualities.
Perhaps we could
work on it together?
I'm not going anywhere.
Dibs.
Did you just say "dibs"?
- I did.
- Well done.
Okay, here is
to always being together.
Cheers.
About that.
You guys all know that
I've been doing
a lot of soul searching
since I left CatCo.
Trying to figure out
what's next.
I knew I wanted to give back,
and I wanted to help people.
But I was driving myself
crazy trying to figure out
where to put those efforts.
And then my extremely
wise sister...
...gave me some
damn good advice.
She said, "Stop trying
so hard to figure things out,
and just be still
and listen."
And finally I heard it.
Only it wasn't a voice
from inside of me,
it was this kid's voice,
this kid that we met
in Calvintown.
Sadly, it's become
this cesspool
for crime and corruption.
And he told me that
no one's there
willing to help.
There's nobody willing
to stand up and
do the right thing.
There's nobody willing
to put their neck on the line.
And just like that,
that's what I knew
I had to do.
Look, I've been fighting
the good fight
from a fancy corner office
for years.
And in the streets
of National City as Guardian.
But I started off
as a guy with a camera.
A camera our dad gave me.
Among the people.
And that is
where I need to be.
For now,
I'm going back to Calvintown.
-I'm going home.
And I'm gonna show that town
that there is somebody
who is willing
to fight for them.
I'm gonna buy
the Calvintown Gazette.
Wow.
Look, Andrea Rojas
may be able to stop me
from writing
for a newspaper,
but she can't stop me
from publishing one.
That's amazing.
And what are
we gonna do without you?
One of the main reasons
I moved to National City
was because Clark wanted me
to keep an eye on you.
But you're the one
that kept an eye on me.
You never needed me.
Not then,
and certainly not now.
Yeah, but we are going
to miss you.
So much.
My feelings are springing out,
and I can't seem to find
a little box to contain them.
Okay, try this box.
To James.
No.
To you guys.
I can't believe James
is really gone.
I guess part of me
always thought he'd come back.
I know.
But I'm happy for him.
He deserves this.
Yeah.
Kara?
What is it?
My friend unencrypted
the address associated
with Elena's account.
It's here.
In National City.
What?
How the hell
did you get in here?
-What is this?
-Kara, walk out of here,
forget what you just saw.
-It's too dangerous.
-What are you?
-An undercover cop?
-I'm a journalist,
like you.
I work for
The Timesin London,
I'm here undercover
to investigate Andrea Rojas.
I'm sorry,
but you've got to leave.
Before you get
mixed up in this.
Be real with me this once,
and maybe I will.
'Cause I already know about
your offshore bank account,
the one you share
with Elena Torres.
I know you were
in Mexico City yesterday,
helping her fake
her own death.
I know that you pretend
to have a wife, but you don't.
I know about Dr. Jarrod,
Dr. Stern,
so why don't you stop
trying to cover your tracks
and just try
telling the truth?
Elena thought
they were onto her,
that they knew she was
talking to someone,
I needed to keep her safe.
And what about your
Intergang friend Sergio Ramos?
Sergio is Interpol,
undercover.
He helped me get her out.
If the Rojases are dirty,
why aren't you saying anything?
Because I haven't found
the proof yet.
Two years' worth of reporting
that suggests
a criminal conspiracy
bigger than Al Capone,
but nothing that connects
the Rojases directly.
It's why I took the job
at CatCo, to get close
to Andrea.
Doing everything I can to get
into the Rojas inner circle.
You have been a toxic jerk
since you got here.
How do I know
you're not just spinning this
to get me off the scent
of what you're actually up to?
Because that jerk
was a lie.
An identity I put on
to keep everyone at CatCo
from wanting to
get
to know me.
-Well, it worked.
-And it killed me.
Every time I was rude to you,
every time I lied about what
I've really been up to.
Now that you know,
at least I can
be honest with you.
At least maybe
you can forgive me.
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
I don't blame you.
I'd hate me too.
Giving you
the cold shoulder.
Being hypercompetitive
in order to get closer
to Andrea.
Criticizing your writing,
instead of telling you
what I really thought.
You mean my work's
not really "sentimental tripe"?
Your articles are honest
and smart.
I could never write
the way you write.
You have two Pulitzers.
It's not from
the writing.
It's from the story.
I have craft,
you have art.
Now promise me
you'll let this go.
I'd never forgive myself
if you got wrapped up in this.
You don't have
to worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
I don't doubt that
you can take care of everything
you set your mind to.
Wow.
Can't believe
you came back.
That you bought the paper.
What can I say?
I like a challenge.
Who knows, maybe you and I
could fix this town together.
By the way,
you know how
to work a camera?
Like, on my phone?
No,
not like on your phone.
Like a real one.
My dad gave me
this camera.
And now it's yours.
Thanks, Chief.
Don't call me chief.
It's Jimmy.
Where am I?
This is not the Phantom Zone.
By now you've realized
you can't phase through
these walls.
But don't think of this
as a prison.
I'm not your enemy.
In fact, I think
we can help each other.