What do you think
it's gonna do?
Whoa!
-Shall we?
-Yeah.
End simulation.
-End simulation.
End simulation!
Why didn't you end simulation?
Yeah, I tried. It didn't work.
And the failsafe button?
What, you mean that giant
red thing that screams
"Push me"?
It's tied to your biometrics.
It appears when necessary.
Yeah, it disappeared
the minute I reached for it.
-What do you mean?
-I mean,
your failsafe failed.
Really? This is the first time
that I've ever encountered it,
but your experience will be
reported to our
development team, Mr. Bates.
I assure you,
this glitch will be fixed.
Long before the launch of
Obsidian Platinum.
I can handle his exit interview
from here, Ms. Olsen.
Dreamer,
I'm sending him to you.
Nap time.
That was incredible!
You beat my record
for defeating a Dominator.
Well, you warmed him up
for me.
Don't you have a date
to get to?
Go! Get out of here.
I want pictures.
Close off the street.
Secure the area.
You're welcome...
Director Dox.
Thank you, Dreamer.
Yes, um...
Thank you.
You already said that.
Hey. What's the emergency?
Blue or purple?
-Oh, your date with
William is tonight.
-Yes.
-Cancel it for me?
-No, I will not.
And, blue. Always go with
the blue. You know this.
I know. I know. But, I...
It's been two and a half years
since I went on a date.
What if I...
forgot how to do it?
You smile, and you laugh,
and your reach for the check.
You make it sound
so easy.
But the way, you should have
seen Nia today.
She was on fire.
Yeah, I did.
She was all over YouTube
and the news,
and every other platform
I've never hear of.
I'm just so proud of her.
And you know what, it just
feels so good to know that if
I want to take a night off,
three's someone there
that can save the day.
After a productive dinner
with Crown Prince
Raakaan el-Farah,
philanthropist Lex Luthor
announced
that Obsidian Platinum's
VR lenses will soon
be available in Quarac.
Gross.
Well, don't book your trip
to Bali just yet,
-we still have to deal
with Lex.
-And we will.
We will stop him
and get him out of the DEO
and we'll get you back in there
where you belong.
You miss it, don't you?
Well, I mean,
I like to think that
the DEO misses me.
But, yeah. Yeah, I miss it.
But, hey, you know what,
I am blazing
a whole new trail here,
and tonight I will be
having a date with this guy.
Oh! Oh, is that,
that Martian weapon
J'onn gave you?
-What do you call it,
the Hand of the Solider?
-Yeah.
How's training?
-Wanna see?
-Yeah.
-Right?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Ow! God, this...
This thing is supposed to know
what I'm thinking,
but it's being
very stubborn.
Well, like soldier like hand.
- Don't scare me!
Isn't that Dreamer
something amazing?
I think she's more powerful
than Supergirl.
I don't know. I think she
probably has her problems
just like everyone else.
Oh, no.
You are not spending
another Friday night
on this couch, in sweats
housing rocky road.
I like ice cream.
Nia.
Sweet little Nia,
you are becoming a...
what's the word?
Loser.
And you're young,
you're vibrant,
but if you sit on this couch,
crying over that weird little
man for one more minute,
you gonna develop
permanent mope face.
I am not moping over...
Barney. I just had
a long day.
So, you need
an even longer night.
Come on.
You going out with me.
I'm meeting my boyfriend
at the club, and
I want you to meet him too.
Wait. I didn't know you were
seeing anyone.
Where'd you meet him?
We've been together
for three weeks.
And we met on Upswipz.
Yvette.
"Loves sunsets,
yachting, and hanging out
with my BFF Dreamer?"
How often do you hang out
with your "BFF Dreamer?"
She waved at me once.
That counts as a hey.
Besides, everybody
embellishes on those things.
-It's Angus.
He says
he cannot wait to meet me.
Wait, you haven't met him yet?
Well, not physically,
but emotionally, it's like
we've been together forever.
Now get dressed.
Okay... all right.
-So, you've never
played 8-Ball?
-What!
Are you kidding me?
I'm from Midvale.
-We have pool halls
on every corner, okay?
-Okay?
Okay, fine.
Maybe I've only played it
once in my life.
Okay, well, then we'll take it
one shot at a time.
For you.
Oh, 'cause you're such
a pool shark?
Oh, yeah. I'm not that bad.
All right.
Let's just take it nice
and soft.
-Beginner's luck?
Ooh! I can't wait to dance
with my man.
I have to go to
the bathroom.
Don't take too long,
Angus will be here any minute.
You know, I was gonna ask
if I can buy you a drink,
but I assume Angus
has already spoken for you?
He sure has.
Loud and clear.
And I just missed
a text message from him.
Ah, he wants me
to meet him outside.
Excuse me.
Angus?
An...
-You leaving early tonight?
-Yeah.
That place is way too crowded.
-Did you find your boyfriend?
-No, he'll be here in a minute.
Oh.
He should have suggested that
you meet at sunset.
What?
You favorite time of day...
is on a yacht
at sunset.
At least that's what
you told me
in our first Upswipz chat.
And I don't think
you'd lie to me.
Would you do that?
Yvette?
Are you okay?
Oh, my God,
what happened to you?
Angus.
Your boyfriend did this to you?
He only pretended to like me.
He targeted me
so I can give this message
to Dreamer.
"The world doesn't want
a trans superhero.
So crawl back under
the rock you came from...
came from, or I'll keep
attacking people like you."
Our profiler put together
this sketch
based on your statement.
Is this the guy?
-Yeah, that's him.
-Thank you.
Now, we're still going over
security footage, and
questioning other patrons
but, please,
do not hesitate to call
if you remember anything
that may help us.
Okay?
I'll show you out.
I'm gonna go lie down.
-Thanks.
-Yeah.
Nia? Nia?
Nia, thank goodness.
Are you okay?
Is Yvette?
Why didn't you call me
last night?
-I would have been there--
-Yvette wanted to be alone.
She's not just hurt
and humiliated,
she's heartbroken.
She thought this guy
really liked her.
And he was just targeting her
because she was trans.
He was trying to use her
to get to Dreamer.
What did he want with Dreamer?
He wants me to stop
being a superhero.
He's going after my community
to bully me into it.
Listen to me, Nia, listen.
We will find this guy.
Yeah, we will.
And when we do,
I'll bury him.
Nia?
Look, I...
I know this is
a personal attack,
but you have to trust that
when we find this guy the cops
are gonna put him behind bars.
Kara, I love you, but do not
tell me what I can
and can't do right now.
There is no catching this guy
and redeeming him.
There is no hope speech
that can make this better.
-Nia...
-No.
Look, my community
is vulnerable.
This happens more than
you could possibly know.
And there are guys just like
this jerk out there
who want to hurt us.
They want us to hide
and to be afraid
to be who we are.
They wants us to disappear,
and it happens...
-every day.
-I know,
and what this guy did
is horrible--
He's not the first,
and he won't be the last.
And we haven't exactly been
a priority for the cops.
So, just trust me when I say
that I am the one
protecting this community.
And now this bastard
is going after
my community,
trying to erase me?
No.
No, this guy is over.
Look, I know that
you're hurting right now,
and I will never
fully understand.
But, between us and the cops,
we will make sure
justice is served.
Nia?
Just give us a chance.
Fine.
A few hours.
But then,
I'm doing this my way.
I said shield!
Alex, the Martian DNA
in your weapon
will code itself to your
bio-electric pulses
allowing you to morph it
with a single thought.
But you have to let it in.
Yeah. Okay, Ollivander.
Is there any kind of
instruction manual
for this thing?
I'm afraid not.
It's instinctual.
Trust the weapon,
and it will trust you.
How am I supposed to trust this
if it keeps changing on me?
All right. Look,
I know things have been
difficult for you
since leaving the DEO.
Life can be challenging
when there's no clear path.
Oh, no, no.
I have a clear path.
Okay, it's stop Lex Luthor
from traipsing around the world
just cashing in on the goodwill
that he never earned,
and get my life back.
Now, let's do it again.
-What is that?
J'onn, Alex, thanks for
seeing me this late.
No problem, Al.
My brother Trevor's missing.
He lives in my basement, but
I haven't seen him
for about a week.
Did you file a police report?
I did... but then the cops
found this on his computer.
An invitation
to a weekend
escape experience
at Obsidian Platinum's
Virtual Las Vegas.
Invite says to get
a hotel room.
So, no disturbances could
pull the players away from
their virtual experience.
So the cops don't think that
he's missing. They think that
he's in some VR party binge.
Right. But that was a week ago.
Look, I'm telling you
this is not like Trevor at all.
Al, do you mind taking me
to your house?
I'd like to take a look around,
see what I can find.
And Kelly works for
Obsidian North, so she can
get me into Virtual Vegas.
And if there's a chance
that Trevor is in there,
then I will find him,
and he can tell me
where he is in the real world.
I really appreciate this.
Hey, no problem, Al.
Kara Danvers.
I hope this is important,
I'm very busy.
It is. It's about...
-Dreamer.
-Yes.
I just saw the coverage
of her victory over
the Dominator.
No, it's not that.
She needs our help.
There's an attacker targeting
the trans community
trying to get Dreamer
to take her cape off.
That's awful.
I mean... it is only logical
that violence begets concern.
Listen, I know
this guy's human,
but can you help me track him?
Consider it done.
So, the last thing that Al
knows is that his brother
checked himself in
to some hotel who knows where,
and that he met up with
some friends at a place
called the Escape Palace?
Yeah, located somewhere
in Virtual Las Vegas.
We figured that Trevor
must have paid cash
for his room,
because there's no paper trail
of him anywhere.
So, I was thinking maybe
I could go into
Virtual Las Vegas, and just
-see what I could find.
-Okay.
Now, these lenses
are very different
than the original.
Okay?
Obsidian Platinum doesn't just
utilize the brain link,
it connects to your biology.
Which means what exactly?
So, in this version,
you're not just
seeing virtual reality,
you're feeling it.
Cold will feel cold,
hot will feel hot,
everything will feel real.
So, once you're in,
you'll be in,
what looks like a lobby.
There you will select
your desired experience.
You will see a panel
of virtual options,
mined from your own
thoughts and desires.
Virtual Las Vegas
is one of these.
Okay, so what happens
when I get inside?
What are the rules?
That's the difference between
reality, and virtual reality.
Inside Obsidian Platinum
there are no rules.
Great. Sounds easy.
You'll get the hang of it.
I promise.
Just remember, if you need
to come out, say
"End simulation."
And if, for some reason,
it gets too intense in there
and you can't say that,
the program will launch
your failsafe button.
You can't miss it.
Just touch it,
and you will be pulled out.
And I'll be able
to communicate with you?
The whole time.
Okay, well...
bottom's up.
I'm in.
Good. You should see
your experience options.
Yeah, I do.
Did you find Virtual Las Vegas?
Yeah, I got it.
Hang on.
There it is.
Vegas, baby...
Vegas.
Well, I know where I can go
to find the Siegfried and Roy
interactive experience.
No, thank you, but
where am I gonna find
this Escape House?
Talk to
the users inside.
Someone must know
where it is.
But stay away from the people
with three lines
on their necks,
-those are NPCs.
-What ae NPCs?
Non-Player Characters.
AIs who populate the world,
not actual users.
-They won't know much.
-Okay.
He said he
was meeting with some
virtual friends in VR?
Yeah, but I don't know
who they are.
I don't even know
their avatar names.
Well, let's see
what we can find.
I just don't understand.
When Trevor and I first came
to this planet together,
we were inseparable.
But, for the last few months,
all he does
is retreat into VR.
What is it?
I managed to track down the
user names of two of Trevor's
virtual friends.
We can get these to Kelly
at Obsidian North,
maybe she can help us
find out who they are.
That way maybe we could
maybe find Trevor.
Look, Al, do you have
anything personal of Trevor's?
Something with an emotional
connection that
I could maybe use
to psychically trace him.
I gave this to Trevor
to mark our first year
on Earth.
He wore it every day.
Till he switched to
a smart watch.
Thanks, man.
Hey, look,
we're gonna find him.
Oh.
Hey, you think
real Vegas buffets
are intense,
you need to try the
all you can eat to get you to
he perfect state of fullness.
No matter how much you eat,
you feel great.
I'll keep that in mind
for the next time. Thank you.
You wouldn't happen to know
where I can find a place called
the Escape Palace, do you?
Escape Palace?
You mean that
spooky looking joint
up on the hill?
Ridiculous add-on
if you ask me.
They don't have hills like that
in the desert.
Right, uh... thanks.
-Sure thing, kid.
- Hey, blue eyes,
bring me the lobster.
So many calories.
He's right. That house is a recent add-on,
customized by a user.
Okay, so what does that mean?
Advanced users can
customize the virtual world,
but it takes time to catalogue these additions in our system.
-So, I don't know what
we can expect.
Well, if Trevor's in there,
then I gotta check it out.
I'm going in.
-I don't like this.
Oh, my God.
This is just like when
Rick Malverne tried
to drown me.
Okay, the user who created
this palace
designed it to tap into
a player's worst fears.
That makes the experience
different for everyone.
And harder to escape.
But, this isn't real,
there's nothing to be
afraid of.
Help. We've been trapped
for days.
Wait, you can talk?
End your simulation.
I can't.
It's part of the game.
Then the failsafe disappeared.
What? I reported that glitch
months ago.
Somebody must have hacked it.
Alex, you need to get them
out of there.
If they've been tortured
for days, there could be
serious repercussions.
I thought you said
this wasn't real?
But they think it is,
and with Obsidian Platinum,
it feels real.
This is why we have a failsafe.
-It's encoded
with a biometric--
-Okay, Kelly,
just in English.
What are you saying?
If you don't break through
those tanks right now,
they could suffer brain damage.
Okay.
All right.
- You did it.
Okay, now give me the names
and locations, so I can send
teams in to eject them.
Tell your teams to hurry.
On it. I'm gonna figure out
why the failsafe
didn't trigger.
Listen, I'm gonna
get you guys out of here.
But we're looking for a man
named Trevor Crane.
Have you seen him in here?
Trevor's done a bunch
of escape rooms with us.
He and the new guy Richard
solved the puzzle quickly
and made it through,
but that door slammed shut.
We were about to follow
when spiders suddenly started
crawling all over me.
And I hate spiders.
Whose idea was it to come
to this escape experience?
It was Richard's.
How well do you know him?
He's new to the group.
I need to get to him
before it's too late.
So, you're saying this
Richard person intentionally
dropped Trevor in VR?
It looks that way.
He's figured out
a glitch in the system
that prevents people from
safely ejecting.
Well, I followed the psychic
trail from Trevor's watch to
a house outside Opal City.
I'll let you know
what I find out.
Excuse me.
-Can I help you?
-I hope you can.
Hi, Detective Rivers,
it's Nia Nal.
I wanted to see if there
was any updates on
Yvette's assault.
We're still reviewing
surveillance footage from the
club and surrounding businesses
and processing
the physical evidence.
So, you're saying
you're nowhere?
I can assure you,
I will do everything in
my power to catch him.
I appreciate that.
I gave you your chance.
Sorry, Kara.
Now it's time to do
everything in my power.
Come and get me.
Mrs. Bates, are you sure
you don't know Trevor Crane?
A number of leads
have led me to this address.
Perhaps he's using an alias?
No. Sorry.
Could he be a friend
of your spouse's?
No, I don't think I've
ever heard Richard mention him.
-Your husband's name
is Richard?
-Yes.
Jennifer, I'm gonna need you
to stop lying to me.
Right now, Trevor is trapped
in a high-level
virtual reality experience
by a man named Richard.
-Possibly being tortured.
-But that's not possible.
-So, you do know him?
-Yes.
Kind of.
We've been spending
some time together in VR.
-Like an affair?
-No.
I have never met him
in real life.
It's just harmless fun.
Does your husband know
about this...
harmless fun?
My husband can be a little...
possessive.
So, I do my thing in VR,
and he does his.
He's a computer engineer
in love with all
the technical details,
and me, I just want to
escape for a few hours.
Regardless, I need to
find Trevor and your husband
as soon as possible.
Or they could both suffer
permanent damage.
Director Dox?
I found over 200
social media groups,
and message boards,
all catering to
trans hate groups.
-They're on this drive.
-Thank you.
That will be all.
-It's no use.
-J'onn located Richard's wife.
Richard's a
computer programmer.
We think that he made
the escape experience
as a way to trap Trevor
because Trevor was having
a virtual affair with
Richard's wife.
Oh, you've got to be
kidding me.
I know, and I need to have
a conversation with Andrea
-about unintended uses
of Obsidian Platinum.
-All right.
Now, any ideas of how
I can get through this door?
If you concentrate hard enough,
you can override
Richard's program.
Bend it to your will,
not his.
-I did it.
Kelly?
It is totally different
in here.
Kelly?
-Can you hear me?
-Alex?
Alex, are you there?
This shouldn't be possible,
but it looks like Richard
customized the room to block
remote monitoring.
Hello?
Trevor?
Okay.
I'm going in.
Maybe put Yvette's quote
at the top of the third graph.
Brilliant.
"Over 24 trans people have been
murdered in this country
in the past year."
The true number's
likely much higher.
Many of these attacks
go mis-reported
because victims are
misgendered in police reports.
Nia was so angry.
I get it,
this is so frustrating.
I wish we could
do more to help.
Hang on.
Brainy, what's up?
I'm sending you
an Upswipz profile Nia created.
It appears she's trying to
lure out Yvette's attacker
by using herself as bait.
I'll talk to her,
and, Brainy,
thank you.
So, something came up,
-would you mind...
-Covering for you?
Of course.
You wanted Dreamer,
well, now you've got her.
Trevor Crane?
I'm Alex Danvers.
Your brother sent me.
Oh, thank God.
It's happening again.
Stay back!
What?
Please make it stop!
Okay, I don't understand,
just talk to me.
-Trevor?
What the hell just happened?
I don't know.
At first, I thought
I was standing on
some kind of a land mine.
If I take a step,
I explode, but
standing still doesn't
work either. I still blow up.
It's random.
And the pain...
-it's horrible.
-Okay, just... focus.
Okay, where is Richard?
I don't know.
I think he planned
this whole thing.
Sometimes he shows up
just to watch me explode.
-It's happening again.
-No, you can fight this.
-You just have to--
-Look out.
End your simulation.
-I am not leaving here
without Trevor.
-Yeah?
Okay, well, then
I'm gonna show you
how real this can be.
'Cause this is my house!
And this is my gun.
You're not getting rid of me
that easily.
Easy, tiger.
Are you okay?
Get back.
I can't control it.
No, no, I'm not going anywhere.
And you can control this,
Trevor. You need to
will it to stop.
All right,
you make the rules now.
Come on.
That's it.
You got this.
-It worked.
-Yeah.
-You were right.
-I knew you could do it.
All right, listen to me.
Give me your location.
I will go out
and I will get help.
I'm at the National City Grand.
-Room 315.
-Okay, you just hang on
and you try to stay calm.
End simulation.
Alex, I couldn't reach you.
What happened in there?
I just fought Richard,
blasted him clean out of VR.
But how?
That shouldn't be possible.
We'll figure that out later.
I found Trevor.
I'm gonna call J'onn
and give him his address.
No, I'll get him.
But I need you to send
a paramedics to
the Coastline Motel.
Room 10.
-Looking for me?
You weren't supposed
to be here.
Got something you wanna say?
Yeah.
I don't think
you're the right kind
of role model.
-That's not for you
to decide.
-Well,
somebody has to stand up
to you people.
You stand up by hiding behind
a fake name online?
And by attacking
innocent people?
It worked, didn't it?
-You make me sick.
-No, you make me sick,
you twisted freak!
You show up on the scene
one day tricking dudes
into thinking that
you're this hot new superhero.
The girl next door,
but heroes are supposed to
be virtuous,
and honest, and here you are
lying!
I get it.
Your fragile ego
was just shattered.
Your sense of self
is so shaky,
that anything outside
your narrow world view
threatens it.
Dreamer, don't.
Stay out of this.
This is my fight!
And you won.
Look at him.
Don't let him turn you
into something you're not.
Why should he get to live?
If you do this, you will take
a piece of his darkness and
carry it with you forever.
When you put that suit on,
you became a symbol.
You give people hope.
Don't let them down
by stooping to his level.
Now, please, let's just
turn him in
and make sure
he faces justice.
You can't promise
that'll happen.
No, I can't.
And I understand...
You feel like you're
the only one protecting
your community,
but you're not alone.
You have me.
And Alex and J'onn and, yes,
even Brainy
in his heart of hearts.
And maybe we all
should have opened
our eyes to the realities
that your and your community
face every day.
But now we have.
And now we will all have
our eyes open
for people like him.
You are going to prison
-for a long time.
And when you're out,
I will be watching you.
And if you ever
make a move against anyone
in my community again,
I will give you a nightmare
you will never
wake up from.
Nia?
Hey. Hey. It's okay.
Kara, I almost murdered
someone tonight...
and I still
kind of want to.
I know.
I don't wanna be a killer,
but...
Kara, I'm not okay.
I am so overwhelmed.
And this guy
just triggered everything.
I had a dream flash
right before Yvette
was attacked and
I couldn't interpret it.
I couldn't save Yvette,
just like I couldn't
save my mom.
I couldn't stop that guy
and my
powers are mixed up
and unpredictable!
And I...
And the one person
who supported me
from day one,
who was always by my side,
who saw me
for who I am, and...
looked at me like
I was beautiful.
It just broke my heart.
And I don't even know why.
I wish I had answers for you.
I'm so sorry.
When that bastard
attacked my community,
the one thing
it felt like I had left...
I snapped.
At least this was something
I could control.
I could find this guy
and stop him.
Permanently.
I could do something
to protect
someone.
I felt that kind of
pressure before.
That anger...
but I wasn't looking at things
through your eyes
and your experiences...
And I'm so sorry.
And I know, I know,
sometimes
being the good guy sucks.
Especially when you know
how easy it would be
to just get rid of
someone so vile
and full of hate.
But, hey,
not doing that...
that is what makes us
different from them.
That's what let's us
keep protecting people,
and your community needs you.
They need Dreamer.
And I'm so sorry. I didn't know
how much pain you were in.
-Oh!
Okay,
relationship talk.
Let's decide right now
that any virtual romance
is cheating.
-Deal.
-Yeah.
Also, virtual torture,
that is definitely real
attempted murder.
Yeah. There are a lot
of open questions
about ethics and morality
in the virtual world.
You okay?
I do truly believe that
what we're...
What I am doing at
Obsidian North can help people.
I just, I feel so guilty
and angry that someone would
take advantage of our
technology like that.
Use our tools as a weapon?
Maybe there should be some
regulations on who can use
Obsidian Platinum.
I agree.
But I flagged that glitch
months ago,
and I was promised that
it was taken care of.
Alex?
Trevor.
Hey, it's...
It's so good to see you out.
I'm so glad that you're okay.
I really wanted to meet you
in the real world,
to thank you.
You saved my life.
Wanna have a drink?
-Yeah.
-This is Kelly.
-Hi.
-She's kind of
part of it, too.
We don't have to worry
about that creep anymore.
He's going to prison
for a long time.
What are you doing?
Deleting my Upswipz account.
And all social media accounts.
Yvette, you can't do that.
I have had it
with putting myself out there.
Making myself an easy target.
I'm done.
He was just one bad person.
You can
tell yourself that, Nia,
like I did,
but I should have known better.
I'm a trans woman of color.
Okay, I know what
we're up against.
I wanted Angus
so badly to be real.
For someone to care about me,
to get me, to adore me.
-It never got to be true.
-It will be.
You will find that kind
of love, Yvette, but not
if you shut down.
They want us to be invisible...
because of their own fears.
They want to erase us
so we need to shine
even brighter.
You are a beautiful woman.
Big beautiful life,
and sharing that life
is what will change this world.
The bigot you arrested,
Gregory Bauer,
belongs to an online hate group
specifically targeting
the trans community.
I took the liberty
of identifying its users.
The group boasts about
future attacks and
takes credit for others.
I believe you will find
some leads to
your cold cases in there.
I... I don't know
what to say.
The DEO takes threats
against our sister superheroes
very seriously.
Ready for another round?
Come on!
I can make you do anything
in the virtual world!
But that wasn't
your real weapon, Alex.
You have to give it time
to bond to you.
Let's do this again tomorrow.
J'onn, really?
Mom, hey.
What's wrong?
Alex?
What is it?
Mom just called me.
They found Dad.
Jeremiah?
He's dead.
There you go, Mr. Bates,
you just rest easy.
I've got you now.