Previously onSupergirl...
My fiancee died fighting
on the front lines.
I saw Alex almost die.
Give me the medallion.
Can you translate
these markings?
I got something
from Rip Roar. A name.
Leviathan.
I can use Supergirl
to achieve my ends.
That is easier to do if she believes there is trust.
Malefic's back
in the Phantom Zone.
You like it here, don't you?
I like it very much.
You're off your game today,
Supergirl.
I could say the same to you.
Not so fast.
I need to be ready.
We don't know when
Leviathan will strike next.
We don't even know
what it is.
And what are they after?
All these unknowns
make me feel anxious.
And when I feel anxious,
I want to punch things.
We've faced
unknown dangers before.
This feels different.
I have a bad feeling about it.
Well, Alex has the DEO
working overtime
on Leviathan.
Are you sure something else
isn't bothering you?
Before I told Lena
I was Supergirl,
I was terrified
how she would react.
I was so afraid
I was going to
ruin the friendship.
Ugh.  I still hate
thinking about it.
Watching William
lose his friend
hit a little too close to home.
J'onn? J'onn?
You can come out now.
Give me the medallion.
I don't think so.
I have the most intricate
security system in the world.
I know all about Leviathan.
No one knows
all about Leviathan.
Leviathan is unknowable.
I'm not afraid.
You will be.
She's gone.
I've reactivated
heightened penthouse security.
You were right
as always, Ms. Luthor.
Leviathan will attempt
to retrieve the medallion
at all costs.
But why would you provoke them
over something of no value?
It has value to me.
The medallion was
special to my mother,
and the fact that Leviathan
wants it makes it useful.
Lex theorized that Superman
kept every weapon
that was ever used against him
in a special facility,
a fortress.
And although he never found it,
I think Lex was right.
I think the perfect
dispersal device
for Project Non Nocere
is hidden there,
gathering dust.
And Leviathan is
gonna help me find it.
Please don't underestimate
the danger of Leviathan.
You should cancel
the L-Corp event at the park.
They will come after you.
Let them come.
Supergirl will save me.
Tell us exactly
what happened.
I already told you, I'm fine.
Alex, you should be
tracking Leviathan.
Yes, and Rip Roar,
but Brainy's on that,
so just stop deflecting.
Before I fell, I was seized
by another vision of Malefic.
"Another"? You've had
more of these?
Yesterday. I felt Malefic
during the psychic attack.
It's as if I can sense him
all around me.
But how? We sent him
to the Phantom Zone.
All I can think is
these flashes are...
maybe symptoms of my guilt.
I know we had no choice
but to send Malefic back
to the Phantom Zone, but...
I mean, he's too dangerous
to be contained here on Earth.
Even so, I can't help feeling
I've wronged my brother again.
This is the third time
he's been sentenced
to confinement by my hand.
No, your brother
made his own decisions.
You can't blame yourself
for that.
But it seems like you're going
through some sort of trauma.
Maybe Kelly can help.
She can't provide
the help I need.
I'll deal with this
the Martian way.
Where's the medallion?
I...
I couldn't retrieve it.
It was a simple task.
It would have been simple
with any other human, but...
she is a Luthor.
Do you know how long that
I've been safeguarding
this planet?
Since the beginning.
And since our ship,
as big as an asteroid,
wiped out the dinosaurs.
Then humanity rose...
and became a scourge
to this planet,
and for eons we have kept
their destructive behavior
at bay, but now...
They're ravaging the Earth
like never before,
and I granted you the privilege
of serving our cause,
and you failed.
Is it her failure,
Rama Khan?
Or is it yours?
You can go, Margot.
Using a carrot
instead of a stick
is not what we need right now.
Well, they are known as
the "snowflake generation."
So what does that mean,
they melt?
Never mind.
You and I both share
the same goal...
of wanting to put a stop
to people who disrespect
this planet.
I'm here to offer my help.
How can you help?
The world is shifting,
evolving.
Moving faster than it ever has.
We have to remain
ahead of the curve.
The old ways aren't working--
Oh, the rising of oceans
and the raging of rivers
will always work.
Give the brute force
a rest, Rama Khan.
Let's try my technology.
Our elder left the caretaking
of this planet to me...
for a reason.
You want something done,
you have to do it yourself.
Thank you all
for coming on
such a wonderful day.
What was that?
Running these trails
has always been my favorite way
to clear my mind.
- What was that?
- Did you feel that?
It means
so much to me
that L-Corp can have a hand
in preserving these grounds.
You have something
that belongs to me.
-What was that?
Leviathan.
Thank God for selfie culture.
Because of this generation's
constant need to
livestream everything,
we've got a clear image
of your attacker.
And I knew I had seen
that face before.
Do you recall Antioch,
526 AD?
It was an earthquake.
It was the eighth-largest
natural disaster
in modern history.
Precisely. It's good
to have you back, Lena.
A myth was born that
this man was the cause.
Now, of course, scientists
insisted that the natural
disasters were natural,
but, in an ironic twist
of history, they were wrong...
and the fearmongers were right.
Several reliable sources place
this man at
the scene of the crime
throughout history.
Pompeii, the Yellow River flood
of 1887, the Bhola Cyclone,
even as far back as
Noah's flood,
this Earth-Bender
has been spotted.
Excuse me, did you say
"Earth-Bender"?
How else would you
describe him?
He... He literally
manipulates the earth.
Wait, Pompeii? Noah's flood?
I mean, what is he,
thousands of years old?
Correct. Which means
that he is an alien
with powers of longevity
this civilization
has never conceived of.
No wonder people
thought he was a myth.
With all this destruction,
his existence is still
shrouded in mystery.
He's managed
to convince the world
he doesn't exist.
It seems so.
The word "Leviathan"
occurs six times
in the Hebrew Bible.
Never once does it appear
in any historical
scientific literature.
So how are we supposed to
fight a highly secretive,
thousand-year-old alien
with powers that we have
no idea how to beat?
Well, I know
one person who spent
his life fighting aliens,
-both real and imagined.
-Your brother.
I know most of
his minor weapons
are in Fort Summit,
but his truly horrendous ones,
they were all destroyed
by Superman.
That's not necessarily true.
A lot of Lex's weapons are
in the Fortress of Solitude.
Oh, it's... It's a place
Superman created.
We keep things there
that can harm us.
Well, you just go
to the Fortress,
and I'll give you a list
of every weapon
that Lex ever created.
Why don't you come with me?
I mean, there's no telling
what weapons we'll encounter.
And then, Brainy and I
will stay here, and we'll
continue our search
for Rip Roar
and this Earth-Bender.
Supergirl, remember
the strongest, most potent
weapon is knowledge.
So send me
whatever you can find
from the Fortress database.
You ready for a road trip?
Are you sure me going
is a good idea?
Of course. Why wouldn't it be?
I don't know. A Luthor
in the Fortress of Solitude?
It's gonna
be great. But you're
gonna need a jacket.
Father,
I haven't been this lost
since after I killed
Manchester Black.
You came to me then.
You helped me find myself.
I need your help now.
J'onn, my son!
Father.
It's good to see you.
I am... I am so sorry.
I know now what I did.
It was unforgivable.
When I wiped your mind
of Malefic...
I committed the greatest sin.
No, J'onn.
It was I who failed.
All you did was ease
your father's suffering.
I forced your hand.
I take full responsibility.
But that's not the reason
I'm here, is it?
Uh, no.
Father, I need your counsel.
Malefic came after my family,
and history repeated itself.
To protect them,
I had to send Mal back
to the Phantom Zone.
I have tried to move on,
but it's like
I can feel him nearby.
That's because he is nearby.
-What?
-Your brother is here.
You mean here in my mind?
No.
I mean, he's across town.
Anything?
I went back to the scene
of Lena's attack and collected
samples of the soil.
I am also scanning
for the Earth-Bender's
seismic wave signature.
Nothing so far.
Earth-Bender?
It's Rip Roar. We found him.
He's not moving.
Did they take him out?
Why?
Fall back.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I am intact.
You're the fragile human.
Are you harmed?
I don't think so...
but I am furious.
They dangled Rip Roar,
knowing that we would
take the bait, and now...
we've got nothing.
Not nothing.
We still have Rip Roar's armor.
We should start
studying it immediately.
-Oh...
-Alex.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah. I'm okay.
Oh, but you have a nasty cut.
There. Perfect as always.
Director Danvers!
Wow! This is... breathtaking.
It's our Krypton on Earth.
Intruder! Intruder!
What's happening?
Luthor DNA detected.
L-Protocol engage.
"L-Protocol"? No.
No, no, no, no, no!
Luthor, relinquish your Kryptonite ring
and your transmatter
portal watch immediately.
I don't have a ring
or a watch.
I'm not Lex!
Hand over
the weapons at once,
or the Fortress will
take offensive action
in ten seconds.
She's unarmed.
-Ten, nine, eight...
-I'll fix this.
-...seven, six, five...
-Come on, come on.
...four, three, two...
L-Protocol terminated.
Sorry. I had no idea
Superman would take
such extreme measures.
No, if Lex knew
about this place,
he would do anything
or kill anyone
to get in here, so...
Well,
you are not Lex.
And you are not your cousin.
We're miles beyond those boys
with their sticks
and their stones.
Yes, we are.
Malefic is in National City,
and he needs your help.
My help!
If what you say is true,
then everyone I love
is in danger.
Your brother cannot harm them.
He is a prisoner.
A prisoner?
Of whom?
That you must discover
on your own.
Father, you have to help me.
How can I find him?
You must make a choice.
Banish your brother
once and for all...
or save his soul.
However, there is only one way
to reach Malefic.
And it requires you to...
risk your own death
by his hand.
Kelly.
What're you doing here?
Brainy texted Nia that
you were both involved
in an explosion.
So I rushed over.
Really, you have...
You have nothing...
You have nothing
to worry about.
No, no. No, don't do that.
Don't cry.
Because if you cry,
then I'm gonna cry,
and you know I really hate
crying at work.
You should have called.
I should have, I'm sorry.
And next time, I will.
I promise.
Okay.
Wait.
What're you doing?
I have to go back to work.
You were nearly just blown up,
and you have a mild concussion.
You can't go back out there
until you're 100 percent.
Okay.
We're almost to
the central database.
Assuming the Fortress
doesn't attack me again.
Thank you for saving me
back there.
I shouldn't have had to,
but it does seem like
dangerous saves
are sort of our thing now.
Yeah, it does.
Of course, it used to be me
being the one
that's saving you.
Imagine, I thought I was
protecting my fragile,
vulnerable friend.
I'm so sorry.
Remember when we went
to Kaznia and the jet
was crashing?
And I was frantic
to try and save us,
desperate to save my friend
before myself...
Little did I know that
that friend could actually fly.
I'm so sorry
I put you through that.
No, it was impressive
how often you saved me
without me realizing...
I mean, you're
an excellent actress.
Telling you the truth
was such a relief,
and I'm so glad that now
we can be honest
with each other
and all of that is behind us.
Me too.
It's this way.
Are you happy now?
No. I've searched the globe.
I can't find them.
With all your power,
you were defeated,
you still don't have
the medallion,
and you lost them?
I will fix this.
Rama Khan,
we're on the same side.
Let me help you.
Your power has kept things
in alignment for ages,
but the world has changed.
Humans are connected
by vast networks,
information flows
across the globe
at the speed of light.
My technology is
a tool we need.
The way to reach them
is beyond you.
They are beyond me.
But if I can't
feel the presence
of Supergirl
or the Luthor girl on Earth,
then that means...
they're in
the one place on Earth...
that is not of Earth.
Is that a polyphasic
quantum processor?
They've long been theorized,
but I had no idea
one actually existed.
I think it is.
My name is Kara Zor-El.
I seek information on
ancient Earth-bending aliens.
The only alien matching
that description
comes from a sister planet
of Krypton, Jarhanpur.
The planet was destroyed
after years of civil wars,
but five of its leaders fled.
One of those leaders
has the extraordinary power
to bend the earth to his will.
How do we stop him?
There are weapons
in the Fortress armory
that can wound him.
Weapons thought to
weaken Kryptonians.
Those created by Lex Luthor,
brother of Lena Luthor.
Thank you, that's all we need.
Well, we better get
to the armory.
If there are more
of these aliens,
we're gonna need
a really big gun.
We should warn Brainy.
-Yeah.
-Do you mind if I do it?
I've never interfaced with
a quantum processor before.
It'd be a bit of a thrill.
Knock yourself out.
Done.
Let's go.
The only chance
of saving your brother...
is to let down
your psychic shield entirely.
Open your mind to him
like a flower.
Complete vulnerability.
Allow him access
to your memories
and innermost thoughts,
so he can see your truth.
If I bond with Malefic...
he can choose
to poison my mind.
How can I make that choice
knowing that he will
most likely murder me...
and kill everyone I love?
Then retrieve
the Phantom Zone projector,
send him back to isolation.
And punish him again?
I'm sorry, my son.
In my lifetime,
I faced this test.
Should I attempt
to reach Malefic
and risk the utter decimation
of my people, my family,
and myself
by his destructive power?
Or should I lock him away
where he cannot harm others?
I made my impossible choice.
There is no such thing
as right or wrong.
There is only peace
in one's heart,
something I never found.
The sins of the father
are visited on the son.
You must make
your own choice, J'onn.
Then ask H'ronmeer
to guide you to your brother.
No matter what you decide,
I will love you for it.
Just as I loved both you
and Malefic...
long ago.
This gun is so tiny.
Yeah, Lex designed that
to fit under
his many human hair wigs.
-Ugh!
-So, yeah.
Right, so the computer said
we need to look for something
that will hurt Kryptonians.
Seems to be a lot
of that in here.
What's this?
That is Myriad.
My... My family created it.
I think I was still
in Metropolis
when Myriad hit.
The news footage, though,
it was pretty horrific.
And reality was even worse.
My Aunt Astra and her husband
turned all of humanity
into mindless zombies
in less than a second.
If there is one weapon
in this room I could destroy,
it would be that one.
Oh, well, this could be
the ticket.
It's a sonic cannon.
It sends concentrated
blasts of high-frequency
ultrasonic waves
at whatever you aim it at.
With a few slight adjustments,
we can maybe use it
to destabilize Rama Khan.
I mean, at least long enough
to put the power-dampening
cuffs on him.
It was designed for evil,
but perhaps we can use it
for some good.
...evidence that the
Psions affected the Czarnians'
evolutionary process.
It's obvious.
Hydrogen molecules synonymous
with Thanagarian atoms...
Good God, it...
It's just...
It's clear!
My inhibitor.
Of course.
I'm less inhibited.
It's spectacular,
truly and absolutely.
Great Scott!
Of course! Tuesday,
croissant... Pilates...
meaning...
Leviathan headquarters
are in National City.
You know, I know I said that
I really wanted
to get back to work,
but this is so much better.
Oh.
Look, I really...
appreciate being taken care of.
I'm so used to doing
all this by myself.
But being with you, it...
It feels like home.
What's wrong?
When Nia texted me
that you were hurt...
my stomach dropped...
and I checked my phone
for a text, and
there was nothing there,
so I assumed the worst.
Because I've been
through the worst,
and this isn't the first time
that I've been terrified.
Last week, I thought
that I was gonna lose you.
But then you got me
that helmet,
and you were so wonderful
and so excited.
And so I pushed past my fears,
and I convinced myself
that I can handle it all.
But I'm not that strong.
And I would never
ask you to change
or ask you to
deny the amazing
and brave woman that you are.
Kelly, what--
What are you saying?
I can't.
Leviathan.
I... I think
I have their location.
We must leave immediately.
Go.  Please, go.
This is it?
Choosing an unobtrusive
structure is how Leviathan
keeps their base a secret.
Except from me.
I must tell you that
in the wake of the explosion,
it is as if
the peripheral vision
of my mind has expanded.
I can now see 20/20
out of the corner of
each metaphorical eye.
Which is how I saw,
when examining
Rip Roar's tech,
some peculiar markings
on his headpiece.
When joined together, it formed
a symbol that can be seen
countless times
throughout history.
A symbol that has been seen
at disasters and catastrophes,
events of mass destruction.
A symbol that has connected
Rama Khan and Leviathan,
but also... every Tuesday
before Pilates,
I get a morning tea
and croissant
at a delightful patisserie
right past this building.
Okay, let's just hope
that you are right.
I mean, look. This is
a fact-finding mission,
so please just... be cool.
I am cool.
You see, I chose
this coffee shop
because of its close proximity
to National City's
ancient tar pits,
a site of great importance
in history, but also
a site of terrible eruption.
You see, despite
its sulfuric scent,
its emitted energy
boosts my brain function.
And I believe Leviathan
has picked this building
for the very same reason.
The ancient energy.
Behold...
The same symbol appears
on this building's cornerstone.
It's impressive.
Not just impressive.
Very impressive.
Cloaking tech.
In order to eliminate
this barrier,
we'll have to hit it
with something similar
to the creator...
something ancient.
I've got it. The dust
from the majestic tar pits
emits Veridian radiation,
redistributing power, and...
No, no, no.
Don't push it yet!
If this elevator leads to
where you think it's going,
we're gonna need Supergirl.
Supergirl, we've located
Leviathan.
Great. Send us the coordinates
and we'll come to you.
Okay,
and I'll have the DEO
start a broadband scan ASAP.
Time to go.
Is that...
It is.
Stay here. Get the gun ready.
You thought
you could hide her from me?
I am ancient. I am the earth.
What are you?
Me? I'm just peeved
you didn't knock.
I don't understand.
Every piece of evidence
led here.
At least we know
my security measures
are working.
Let's get out of here.
I told you, I am the earth!
"The earth."
But the Fortress
isn't made of earth.
I'm curious,
how did you find us?
When I searched
the globe and couldn't
find you,
I went to the one place that
I knew that you could hide.
I think
you overlooked something.
Oh?
You're in my house.
I have home court advantage.
Welcome to Krypton, old man.
Forget about me?
You won't survive me again,
Kryptonian.
Lena?
Lena.
Why do you have Myriad?
Well, you caught me.
I have Myriad
because I'm using you...
like you used me.
I never used you.
Do you remember
when you finally told me
you were Supergirl?
You were weeping.
Big crocodile tears.
Well, I wept real tears,
bitter tears over you
weeks before.
What? I... I thought...
How long had you known?
I found out the day
I killed my brother.
Lena, you didn't kill Lex,
that was me.
I... I watched him...
I saw him fall.
You saw him fall,
but did you see him land?
Did you see him die?
I did, and let me tell you,
it wasn't pretty.
That's impossible.
Anything's possible
when you're a Luthor.
Lex used
his transmatter portal watch.
I knew exactly where he'd go.
To the cabin we loved
when we were children,
so I was there waiting for him.
I had the gun ready... loaded.
I could feel the weight of it
in my hands.
Every fiber in my being
rebelled, but I--
I didn't want to do it,
but I knew I had to
because if Lex lived,
the world wouldn't be safe,
my friends wouldn't be safe.
So I forced myself
to pull the trigger.
I shot my own brother
in the chest.
His final words to me were...
that I was a fool,
that my best friend,
that every friend I had
was lying to me.
With his dying breath,
he told me that
you were Supergirl.
Lena, you have to believe me,
I never meant to humiliate you.
No. When I came to this city,
I promised myself that
I would never trust
anyone again, and...
then I met you.
You chipped away at my armor
with your warmth
and your earnestness,
and you convinced me to trust
in people and friendship again,
and against my better judgment,
I did,
all the while telling you
about my Achilles heel...
betrayal.
I confided in you
that everyone in my past
had betrayed me.
About how much it hurt...
to have someone you love
lie to you and betray you.
I spelled it out
to you over and over again,
essentially begging you
not to violate my trust,
begging you not to prove that,
once again, I was a fool.
You reassured me ad nauseam
that you would never lie to me,
that you'd never hurt me.
And all the while,
there wasn't a single
honest moment
in our friendship--
No! No, that is not true--
No! I killed my brother
for you, for our friends!
Don't you understand
what you've done?
When you found out,
why didn't you come...
to me right away,
so I could explain--
"Explain"? Yeah?
If you hate me so much, why...
Why not out me
at the Pulitzer party?
Why pretend to still be
my friend this long?
Because I wanted you
to experience
what you did to me.
Feel what I felt.
I understand your pain
and your fury and...
And you're right.
I made a big mistake,
maybe the biggest mistake
of my life, but please...
Lena, please don't leave
the Fortress with Myriad.
Please don't let my mistake
push you to do
something terrible.
-You are a good person.
-No!
No, you don't ever get
to tell me who
or what I am again.
Intruder! Intruder!
Did you reprogram
the Fortress defenses
to attack me?
Yes.
And I rigged it to answer
to this little button
I have in my hand.
Are you going to try
to kill me?
No. Supergirl,
I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm not a villain.
You shouldn't have
treated me like one.
And now you've come
to finish what you started?
I have.
But I will not...
send you back
to the Phantom Zone, brother.
I spent lifetimes there,
brother.
Lifetimes of nothing.
No air, no time,
no sight, no smell.
Nothing but my heart...
suspended mid-beat.
An excruciating suspense
that never stops.
A breath you can never exhale.
Is that where you suggest
I send you?
You can if you wish.
But I bring this only now
as an offering...
to show you
that I mean it when I say
that I have come here...
to make amends.
Liar!
Mal,
I wish I could've
broken you out of that cave
when we were children.
Found some way to...
show you.
you were my brother
and I loved you!
You didn't love me.
You were ashamed of me.
You hid me away.
Banished me...
like a monster!
We were afraid of you.
We were all afraid of you.
I was afraid of you.
And we were so wrong.
I destroyed my honor...
when I wiped you
from our memories.
But, Mal, what I did,
I did for love.
Now that I remember...
I cannot live with this pain.
And so, brother...
I beg your forgiveness
by submitting myself...
to the bond.
Look into my mind, brother.
It's that easy?
You hand yourself over to me.
I will look...
with pleasure, brother.
Right before I kill you.
I'm willing
to risk everything...
in order for you
to see my truth,
my heart, my soul, and my mind.
I saw.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-I was--
-No, it's... I know.
Um...
You have been through
an unbearable experience.
Yeah.
You lost your fiancee,
and I can't even
begin to imagine losing
someone that you love...
in that way.
You're just so strong
that I didn't...
I didn't realize
that you were still suffering,
and I'm really sorry that
I wasn't more sensitive
to that.
-No, don't--
-Just... Just...
Listen...
When you met me,
I was just half a person.
I was still hurting
from my own wounds
and you... You helped me heal.
You know, from wounds to scars,
to just memories.
That's... That's all I want
to do for you.
Hey, I want to help you heal.
I want to be with you
and face down your fears
and do it together.
I want to help you heal.
And what if that's
not possible?
Well, I know that it is.
How?
Because you healed me.
I meant it when I said
that you feel like home.
You feel like home, too.