Previously onSupergirl...
It was me.
I erased him from our minds.
I as good as murdered
my own brother.
This is not the Phantom Zone.
Don't think of this
as a prison.
I'm not your enemy.
In fact, I think
we can help each other.
This is an Aurafacian.
This is an alien organism
that attaches to a host body.
All right.
Let's get these down
into holding.
I'm here undercover
to investigate Andrea Rojas.
Two years' worth of reporting
that suggests
a criminal conspiracy
bigger than Al Capone.
I'd never forgive myself
if you got wrapped up in this.
Leviathan is coming.
Imagine you,
anytime of the day,
anywhere in the world,
with all your friends.
Then imagine
that all of you can do
anything that comes to mind.
Well, you don't have to
imagine anymore.
Obsidian North's
"Collective Dream" VR lenses
are now worldwide.
So why are you waiting?
Make your imagination
your reality today.
Brilliant!
Thank you, William.
I'm proud of it.
Which is why I want
every department
to be writing about the launch
right up until it happens
on Friday.
Business, entertainment,
sports, politics,
work it into your stories
as if our financial well-being
depended on it.
Because it does.
-Gross.
-Double gross.
And one more thing.
One of you needs to start
giving continual updates
on our growing sales.
We need to pump this up.
-I'm your man.
-Great.
Now let's get to it.
It's bad enough
that we have to do
journalism-via-tweet.
Now she wants to
turn us into ad hacks?
Speaking of hacks...
Joe Pulitzer is certainly
all for it.
Uh-huh.
I was so sure you were
gonna find something
at that address
listed in his name.
First he is linked
to the death of Dr. Jarrod,
then to
whatever "covert action"
happened in Mexico City.
I don't know,
I find it hard it to believe
there's no connection.
I know. I guess we were
looking for connections
where there weren't any.
I mean, he was just
in the wrong place
at the wrong time
with Dr. Jarrod,
and then Mexico City
was just about
the Miss Mexico pageant.
William Dey's not a murderer.
He's just a grade-A jerk.
-Kara. Hi.
-Kelly, hey.
-You're just who I needed.
-Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's good. I just...
I want to get Alex a gift
for our date-aversary,
and I could
really use your help--
A Schadel XG-1000
motorcycle helmet,
in small, matte black.
Oh. That is very specific.
-So is Alex's Pinterest page.
You know, meeting Alex
is one of the best things
that has happened to me
since moving to National City.
But having you
in the picture...
-That's been
a pretty cool bonus.
Believe me,
the feeling is mutual.
But you know what?
I, uh...
I promised all these
reporters upstairs
a round of coffee.
-And if I don't get it,
there will be a riot.
- Okay.
Uh, remember,
small matte black.
Got it.
What's the deal?
I've been texting you
all morning.
Phones can be hacked.
Call me overly cautious,
but I'm trying to expose
one of the world's
most powerful families
as criminals.
That's why I was texting you.
Morning.
I figured out a way I can help.
Kara...
Just...
Hear me out. Okay?
From what you've explained,
you have all this evidence
suggesting the Rojases
are masters
of corporate espionage,
and have a team of operatives
and assassins
at their beck and call.
But nothing connecting them
directly to the crimes. Right?
Yes, it's a
frustrating failure.
Well, what if I told you
that my sister works
for a small g...
Government agency.
And they just arrested someone
who they think
targeted Elena Torres
in Mexico City yesterday.
Kara, don't tell me
you told your sister
about this.
I-I didn't tell her details,
but now we have a lead.
What's the catch?
Two conditions. One...
You have to sign an NDA
saying you will never tell
anyone where she works.
And, two...
Kara, I told you
you don't want
any part of this story.
I am not in it for the story.
When...
When Andrea come to CatCo,
I thought she was
just a bad boss
and a hack journalist.
But if she really is
actually involved
in a web of murders,
I can't walk away from that.
I am in it for the justice.
You've been going at this solo
for so long.
I could be useful.
What's the harm
in letting me help?
The harm is that
you could get hurt.
-I'm not
just talking physically.
-Mmm-hmm.
This has cost me
friends, family.
It's an obsession
that's taken up
two years of my life.
And I don't want that
to happen to you.
You don't have to
worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
Plus,
if you don't bring me
the offer's off the table.
-Okay.
You win. Let's go.
Ha!
Test subject 0505.
Trial commencement.
Image induce
to human-form 2257.
Now.
Subject induced.
Prep for tracking.
Q-wave sensors locked and ready
to probe occipital lobe.
Ms. Luthor, you realize
if this goes as planned,
we are about to discover
how to do
what it is that doctors,
politicians, even priests
have failed to do.
Rendering people incapable
of hurting each other.
Activate.
You cannot touch me.
Mr. Dey, if half
your suspicions about
the Rojases are true,
then this presents
a huge security risk.
Still, you are here
as observers
so follow my lead.
-Of course.
-Let him in.
Thank you for doing this.
Yeah, well, Obsidian Worldwide
is a big deal.
Plus, working at Obsidian
is Kelly's dream job,
so before I have the DEO
make any moves on her boss,
I need to be certain
that she is guilty.
Right, yes. Speaking of, uh,
Kelly asked me what to get you
for your date-aversary.
She doesn't need to get me--
I told her the Schadel
XG-1000 motorcycle helmet
in small, matte black.
God, I love you.
Is this
some sort of torture device?
It's a Truth Seeker.
It makes it so that those
who are inclined to lie, can't.
For example,
did Andrea Rojas hire you
to target Elena Torres?
I don't ask who hires me.
My jobs come over
an encrypted server
that compensates me in Bitcoin.
Okay. Have you
ever met Andrea Rojas
or any member
of the Rojas family
or anyone that
they are affiliated with?
I only meet
the other contractors.
There was this lady
with killer tattoos,
a guy who could detach
most of his fingers,
and this big dude
with some extra appendages.
-How many--
-How many...
...appendages?
He had four arms.
Like this?
Yeah, that's him.
His code name is Rip Roar.
-When did you last see him?
-William.
-Two years ago
on a job in Darien...
-No time after?
- No.
-Mr. Dey...
So where is he based?
Who are his target?
You have to know something.
I have literally
told you everything.
That's a bloody lie!
-That will be enough!
-William.
Out!
What was that about?
-You have to tell me.
-He murdered my best friend.
What?
My mate from college.
Russell Rogers.
Two years ago,
he got suspicious
of the Rojases,
and the next day,
that monster killed him.
-Never found the body.
-Then how do you know
he's dead?
These are professional killers.
They don't leave evidence.
I have a friend
that could help with this.
I should have
never told you any of this.
Now look how involved you are.
It's why I told you
to stay away.
It's an emotional abyss.
Hold it. Set the case down.
Turn around.
Show me your hands.
Russell Rogers.
I'll look into
his disappearance.
Thank you.
And how are you feeling?
With everything
that happened with Mal...
Well,
I'm still processing it all.
But it gave me deeper knowledge
about myself and...
And my people.
I can learn from that.
How about you? Are you okay?
You've been through a lot.
The reporter you hated
turns out to be a good guy
and Andrea Rojas is potentially
involved in murders.
Yeah, I can't talk about this
with anyone but you and Alex.
I swore to William
I'd keep it secret.
Even from Nia.
But honestly,
I... I'm, I'm reeling.
I never would have thought
Andrea was a criminal
and I was convinced
William was evil.
How could I have been
so wrong about both of them?
And now,
with Obsidian tech everywhere,
I mean, everyone's
just in these
make-believe worlds and...
It's hard to know
what's real anymore.
I just want some certainty.
You know, my biggest takeaway
from what happened
with Malefic,
is when the world is uncertain,
there's one thing
that's rock solid.
It's the people
who love you.
Alex needs me at the DEO.
We had a break-in
at Fort Summit.
Please don't tell me
it is Lex's vault.
Indeed.
And this is the assailant.
It is the same guy
William talked about.
What did he steal?
Mr. Luthor called it
his Marathon Laser.
It's able to launch
a concentrated beam of heat
at a target
up to 26.2 miles away.
It's an assassin's dream.
Is there any way
we can track it?
We are scanning for the weapon.
With any luck, that will
lead us to the man as well.
William said Rip Roar was
a part of the Rojases's
team of operatives.
Now they're stealing
one of Lex's weapons
the day before the launch
of Andrea's lenses?
If William Dey is right
about Andrea Rojas,
there's a high probability
of a connection.
But Kelly did say
the VR launch is virtual.
So people aren't gonna be
gathering in one place.
So what use
is that weapon then?
We've gotta be
missing something.
I'll take another run
at Breathtaker.
No, we tried that.
Even with the Truth Seeker,
she's got nothing.
I might have a solution.
There is always
the other assassin we caught.
What, O'Connor?
-She's dead.
-Yes.
But her tattoos are alive
and sentient.
Wouldn't we need a host?
We would, yes.
Approaching me
while I'm still conscious.
How thoughtful of you.
It seems
we have gotten off
on the wrong foot.
So I have a proposition.
You have the ability
to incept thoughts
into people's minds.
I want to study your brain,
so I can develop a technology
that can do the same thing.
Forgive my skepticism,
but last time
someone showed interest
in my brain,
the High Council sent me
to the Phantom Zone.
You'd be
back in the Phantom Zone
if it wasn't for me.
And yet, now we are
at an impasse.
What's in it for me?
We both want the same thing.
We were each betrayed
by the people closest to us.
Work with me.
I believe you've the ability
to do great things.
I don't want
I want revenge.
So I have a proposal for you.
Martian biology prevents
a brother from
harming his brother.
That's why I've been
attacking the people
closest to J'onn J'onzz.
If you remove
this barrier from my brain
so I can kill my brother,
I will give you access
to my mind.
It is my mission to stop people
from hurting each other.
I will not kill.
Perhaps.
But you've gone
to extreme measures
to bring me here.
And now,
you are at the precipice.
Studying my mind is the key.
I know of desperation, human.
I know the depths you feel.
I would have to develop
the technology first.
Your terms are acceptable.
Let's begin.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
Once we say "the phrase,"
you're gonna augment
the executive section
of your brain
to allow the Aurafacian
to speak through you.
Yes.
And thanks to
my polygraph filter,
it won't be able to lie.
That is the phrase.
I've kept it top secret
all day.
You're welcome.
Seriously?
It's from the oeuvre
of Mr. Keanu Reeves.
"Pop quiz, hotshot."
Brainy?
Release me, human!
You know that
we're not going to do that.
We want information.
Come near, I'll give it to you.
You worked with
a contractor named Rip Roar.
He has a very dangerous weapon.
How do we find him?
Perhaps put an ad in the paper
for a four-armed freak.
There's a chance he might
use this weapon tomorrow.
Do you have any idea
who the target might be?
I never know who's behind it.
All I know
is that someone is spending
a great deal of capital...
...to do
a great deal of damage.
You've committed
dozens of murders
but don't have
the slightest idea
who's responsible?
I don't care to know.
You don't care about
all those people you killed?
Their family, their friends,
all those lives
you've destroyed?
-You have to know something!
-I don't know.
-No, you know something
and we're--
- Hey!
Hey, it's Brainy.
Kryptonia.
Come here! Let me
print myself on your skin!
Pop quiz, hotshot!
Uh, did it work?
-Hey.
-I know. I know. I'm sorry.
-I overreacted.
-No. You're right.
This is getting way bigger
than we thought.
I'm gonna confront Andrea.
Okay, slow down.
We need to be strategic.
Okay? We need to see
the bigger plan here.
Plus, there is still a chance
that she's not even involved.
What makes you say that?
Kelly believes in Andrea,
and the work that she's doing.
It helps people.
And Andrea's never even been
accused of anything illegal.
Even according to Will,
Elena Torres offered
only circumstantial evidence
against her.
Look, Kelly has been
through the ringer.
And I really don't want to
pull the rug out from under her
unless I have to.
Trust me,
I want answers too,
but these are big accusations
and we need to be certain.
I know everything you're saying
makes sense,
but I have this gut feeling
that Andrea's
up to something big.
Lex Luthor had a plan
for world domination
that felt a lot like this.
And that time,
I was almost too late.
I cannot let that happen again.
We won't.
If Andrea's involved,
we'll figure out how.
I have an idea.
Supergirl.
I trust your gut, too.
I have the Marathon Laser.
What do you want me
to do with it?
Do what
Lex Luthor failed to do.
Change the world.
Big day tomorrow, William.
Five million subscribers big.
And counting.
Now that's the news
I wanna hear.
-Careful now.
That's my brain
you're about to play with.
The occipital lobe is where
the Q-waves are generated.
Q-waves are projected
like sonar from a dolphin.
But your waves
are a very special frequency
that allows you
this unique ability
to control the thoughts
and emotions of others.
This is the frequency
we want to isolate.
That "unique ability"
has been my cross to bear
my whole life.
To think
it comes down to something
as simple as a frequency...
All you have to do
is incept
these three test subjects.
All right?
There's a Daxamite Scorpion,
a Terran Oceanic Devil,
and a Maladorian Dendroasp.
As you project
your waves at them,
we'll measure the frequency,
fine-tuning as we go,
'til we hit the magic number.
So, are we ready?
As long as killing J'onn J'onzz
is the final result,
"we" can't wait.
I really appreciate
you bringing food.
It's exactly what I needed.
It's gonna be
another very late night, so...
Oh, no. What happened?
Oh. You know,
just another day at the DEO.
A stolen Luthor weapon
and a conspiracy
of meta-assassins.
Well, I am here for you
if you ever need to
talk about anything.
Of course.
How are you?
Well,
Obsidian is abuzz
with the launch,
and I had my first
patient success story.
Yeah. He was having nightmares
for over a year.
And with VR therapy,
they stopped.
That's amazing.
Oh. And...
I made a surprise reservation
for our date-aversary.
-At the waterfront.
-Really?
-That's nice.
But don't you
have to be on deck
for the Obsidian launch?
Well, since it's virtual,
I can bring
the lenses to dinner,
and then we can join millions
in virtual celebration.
Okay, now that sounds like
one of your boss's
freaky advertisements.
Just because it's freaky,
doesn't mean it's not awesome.
-Well, cheers to that.
-Ah.
Okay.
-William.
I'm looking for clues
to what Andrea's been up to.
Well, I am, too.
But if Andrea sees you in here,
she'll kill you.
-And that's not a metaphor.
-It's fine.
I... I looped the cameras.
I borrowed something
from the DEO.
What are you doing here?
What I should've done
in the first place,
gone straight to the source.
Now, thanks to my friends
at MI-8, I can.
But, well,
you should know first
the DEO got a lead
on Rip Roar.
Where? How?
From what I understand,
he's stolen
a pretty powerful weapon.
And they're afraid
he's gonna use it
in connection
with Andrea's launch.
That means we have
less than a day
to figure out
what she's planning.
- You really think
Andrea would leave
information on her laptop?
I mean,
she's kind of tech savant.
Oh, there's got to be
something in here.
If there is,
don't you think it'd be like,
in a nook or cranny
or under the floor
or something.
You look your way,
I'll look mine.
-Of course
she has a Firewall.
"Access denied?"
I think I hit pay dirt.
How did you know
to look in there?
Lucky guess.
But look what
she has stashed in here.
Foreign currency,
I mean, that's pretty shady.
Uh, some sort of chain and...
Hello.
Isn't that Russell?
Did they know each other?
They more than just
"knew each other."
At least according to Russell
the last time I saw him.
-Wow.
-I'm crazy about her.
I think she's the one.
Man, you are sunk.
Well, almost.
-What do you mean?
-She comes from
a powerful family.
You know, there's a lot
going on there.
And they make a point
about shutting me out.
-What? They don't think
you are good enough?
-Nah.
It's not that.
It's more like
they got secrets.
What, like dead bodies?
Oi, you're not getting
into something dodgy, are you?
Nothing I can't handle.
This doesn't sound good, Russ.
I just don't know
how deep these things go
with these people.
But Andrea
is nothing like her family.
I'll sort it out
with her tonight.
Then tomorrow,
I can figure out a time
when she can finally meet
my best friend.
What, you haven't mentioned me?
If you think I'd let her
anywhere near
that wicked smile of yours
before we're settled,
you're madder than I thought.
-Ah.
That was the last
I saw of him.
Russell?
You need a new lock, mate.
Stop!
-Where's Russell?
-Dead.
Oh, my God, William.
That's horrible.
Let's get out of here.
Well,
I reset the cameras.
No one will know
we were in Andrea's office.
She has to be involved in this.
Rip Roar, Russell.
Do you remember
how she reacted
when it happened?
She is a billionaire heiress.
I didn't have access to her.
The police
couldn't find anything,
so they just presumed
he skipped town.
-There's no body, no leads.
So I tried to find some leads
by researching Andrea
and her family.
I know I'm on
the right track here,
just haven't
been able to prove it.
And now,
with Russ's killer back,
maybe it's time
I just ask her point blank.
William, don't even
joke about that.
We... We have to be certain
of what we're up against first.
Now is not the time
to be rash.
Look who's talking.
You broke into Andrea's office
before I did.
That's true.
But you've...
You've dedicated
so much of your life
to this already.
What's the risk in hanging on
just for a little bit longer?
Is that what you told yourself
when you were chasing
the Lex Luthor story?
To slow down
and "hang on?"
Actually, yeah, it was.
And it was really hard.
But I did it because
I could feel that I was close.
Just like I can feel
we are so close right now.
That's, uh...
Sorry, it's my sister.
Alex, what's up?
Brainy tracked the signature
of the Marathon Laser
to the Socorro
Satellite Station
in New Mexico.
We need Supergirl there now.
I'm on my way.
Something came up
with my family.
But just promise me
you're not gonna do anything.
Rip Roar.
I know who you are.
And I know
you killed Russell Rogers.
You know nothing.
And you're out of your depth.
Alex.
I need J'onn.
Thank you
for helping me.
I'm feeling a lot better.
You know
I'm always here for you.
Hey, look, I tracked down
the apartment where
Russell Rogers lived in London.
I did a psychic sweep.
I did see evidence of a struggle there years ago,
but nothing else.
You mean he's still alive?
Possibly. I'm still looking.
Where are we on Rip Roar
and what did he hit me with?
It's called
a Fusion Cannon.
Or at least it is
100 years from now.
It's the result
of the ingenious combination
of Lex's Marathon Laser
plus a particle amplifier.
That's what Rip Roar stole
from the satellite base.
Yes, the combined technologies
create an energy beam
100 times hotter
than the center of the sun.
If it's capable
of damage like that,
imagine what else it can do.
We need to find it.
Uh, yes, about that...
The amplifier's radiation
obfuscates the cannon's
energy signature,
which makes tracking it
quite difficult.
Well, Obsidian North's launch
is today.
So whatever
Andrea's been up to,
will probably come to a head.
Brainy, is there anything
about the launch
we might have missed?
Negative.
Gotta be connected.
Andrea, Rip Roar, the weapon.
And we've got to find out how
before he hurts anyone else.
He's got to be stopped.
Alex, hi, it's me.
Look, I know you're busy,
so I will text you the address
for the restaurant tonight.
And if you're running late,
don't worry.
Just get there when you can.
And we'll start to relax.
Okay, people.
The Collective Dream launch
is in less than an hour.
William, what is
our user count?
We'll have nine million.
That's more than
the population of most
of the world's countries.
Well done.
And now,
our final test subject,
the Maladorian Dendroasp.
It is 100 times
more aggressive than
anything on Earth.
I want you to do to it
what you did to them.
Sensors are ready
and calibrated.
Now.
Satisfied?
It worked.
Lake Vostok.
Okay, in English, Brainy.
Actually, it's in Antarctica,
where I believe
Rip Roar is heading.
Antarctica?
After cross-referencing
information gleaned
from Breathtaker
and the Aurafacian,
I have discovered
that each of
the three Rojas assassins
all targeted an employee
of the Lake Vostok
Antarctica Base,
all within the last month.
A scientist, an engineer
and a security officer?
What's the significance?
Well, given what
each of the targeted
individuals knew,
it is possible that
every single security protocol
on that base
can now be overridden.
I still don't get it.
Lake Vostok is the largest
subglacial lake in the world.
Now, I'm no super-villain,
but if I were,
and I was right over
an Antarctic lake
with a weapon designed
to fire a beam 100 times hotter
than the center of the sun,
well, it would be, as they say,
"a hot time in
the old town tonight."
Not that that's a good thing.
So you're saying that
he's going to melt the ice cap
around Lake Vostok?
If he did that,
it would unleash a flood
unseen since the time
of Noah's Ark.
This one's still alive.
Rip Roar, no!
Status?
A massive eruption
in the Antarctic water table
has sent shock waves
east and west,
resulting in an unprecedented
number of sea swells.
Based on the seafloor pattern
and the
Antarctic Circumpolar Current,
the biggest is set
to make landfall
on the Pacific coast
in under an hour.
Which part
of the Pacific coast?
All of it.
Leaving so soon?
Smart move.
What have you done?
I do what they tell me to.
They? Who is "they?"
I don't know.
Supergirl,
can you hear me?
Alex, we have Rip Roar,
but he punched a hole
in the lake.
We know. The eruption
just sent a tidal wave our way.
We can deal
with the swell, Supergirl.
You and J'onn
need to seal that geyser,
or else we'll have
bigger problems than a wave.
What do you mean?
That geyser is pumping out
three cubic miles of water
every second.
At that rate,
every coastal city in the world
will start flooding
in 12 minutes.
The loss of life
could be in the billions.
So how do we stop that wave?
Dreamer.
It's too late.
Once it's started
it can't be stopped.
Trust me,
I can stop this.
Thank you.
Welcome one and all
to the most amazing party
you'll ever attend.
Welcome,
welcome to The Communal Dream.
welcome, everyone.
We'll have to
invert the flow of water.
The geyser's pushing it up.
Maybe a whirlpool
could pull it down.
We'll fly around the base.
But we need to do it
in perfect formation.
With this amount of water,
the suction could
pull you under
and suffocate you.
Well then, we'd better
keep our cool.
Why aren't you at the launch?
Did you find something
more important?
Actually...
I did find something.
His name is Russell Rogers.
What?
I saw the photo, Andrea.
I know all about
the two of you.
What did you do with him?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I know about O'Connor
and Breathtaker and Rip Roar.
I know about you
and your family,
and everything
you've gotten away with.
Corruption, theft, murder.
But you're not going to
get away with it any longer.
Because I am
going to destroy you,
if it's the last thing I do.
William...
William?
The launch is going great,
don't you think?
Sure is, Ms. Rojas.
Dreamer?
That's a huge wave!
Brainy, I hope this works.
Everybody get to high ground!
Go!
Right. I got you. Down!
Go! Everybody move, move!
Hmm.
Now!
Did he say anything?
He isn't talking.
Even with the Truth Seeker.
But he said "they."
"They" told him
to do what he did.
He has to know something.
But according to Brainy,
I mean, the tech he wears
is biologically adhered
and it functions as
some sort of mental armor.
We can't get to him.
Also, it wasn't the Rojases.
-What?
-We ran the analytics.
Okay, flooding the West Coast
would've taken out
Obsidian North's
manufacturing hub.
And if you and J'onn
hadn't stopped the geyser,
then they would've
lost billions.
I gotta say, I'm glad that
I don't have to tell Kelly
that her boss is a crime lord.
But this still leaves us
with a case
that doesn't make any sense.
If it wasn't Andrea
and the Rojases,
who was calling the shots?
Someone has to be behind this.
I agree.
And whoever it is,
we're gonna find them.
It just might take longer
than we thought.
There's something
you both should see.
-Kelly, you okay?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Yeah.
Yesterday was just, um,
a lot.
With everything that happened
at the waterfront.
And Alex was...
She was amazing.
But I was there
and I almost saw her die.
I guess it triggered me.
I'm so sorry.
Look, I know that Alex
can take care of herself.
I do. But...
My fianc died
fighting on the front lines,
and I never got over it.
This brought it all back.
I just... I can't shake
this feeling of...
...dread.
Well, it sounds to me
like you could use a friend.
Do you wanna
grab lunch sometime and talk?
I'd like that.
Thank you.
It is finished.
What is?
I have clarity on how
to dispose of my brother,
now that you've removed
my mental block.
But I didn't remove it.
I could never let you
hurt another person.
We had a deal.
If you intuited anything
about my research,
you'd know that.
You like it here, don't you?
Yes.
I like it here.
I like it very much.
You look beautiful.
Well, I did wear
your favorite color.
Um...
I'm so sorry that I missed
our date-aversary
and your voicemail.
But you know what
we're up against.
You were incredibly brave.
-Well, I've developed
a few skills over the years.
Um...
Hey. Uh, come here.
I... I got you something.
Oh, I got you something, too,
but I forgot to bring it.
Oh, that's okay. This isn't
our real date-aversary.
So when it is,
you can give it to me then.
Close your eyes.
-Close them.
-Okay.
Okay, open.
A Schadel XG-1000.
So you can be
my riding partner.
This is amazing.
I'm just so glad that
we can be together right now.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I didn't confront Andrea.
Though, believe me,
I wanted to.
Now, I'm even more
confused than ever.
The Rojases
would've lost everything
if Rip Roar had succeeded.
If they're not the villains,
then who?
And now it gets
even more confusing.
Um...
The DEO caught Rip Roar
and they were able to ID him.
It's Russell.
No. What?
That's... That's not possible.
I thought they killed him.
All of this
was to avenge his death.
I don't believe it.
What could they have done
to turn him into that...
monster?
I'm so sorry.
I know how painful this is.
But now that
we have him in custody,
the good thing is
we can finally
get you some answers.
About him, about Andrea,
about any other questions
we might uncover.
Thank you.
You know I didn't want you
involved in this.
But I don't know how I would've
done it without you.
Thank you.
You've really outdone yourself
with those contact lenses.
I hear they're as omnipresent
as one of our plagues
or floods.
That was you yesterday?
Leviathan is everywhere.
And now a problem has come up.
We need you to fix it.
It's Rip Roar.