Previously on
Supergirl...
Now, it is time,
you avenge yourself
against the brother
who wronged you.
-Eve.
-Sorry, not sorry.
Can you believe the fourth
estate saved the day?
Kara Danvers
is Supergirl.
Your friends have been
lying to you.
Damn it. The brakes.
Help us! Help!
Thanks, Supergirl.
When I grow up,
I wanna be just like you.
Oh, that's easy,
you just have to fight
for what's right
and always tell
the truth.
Always tell the truth,
that's rich.
Ms. Luthor,
is everything all right?
Why so formal?
I thought
we were best friends.
Kara.
-You know?
-Know what?
That you're a hypocrite
who's been lying to me
for years?
-No, Lena, I didn't--
Terminate.
Virtual reality
simulation terminated.
May I ask you something,
Ms. Luthor?
Yes, Hope.
These simulations you've been
running in virtual reality.
My calculations
show it's possible
they can be achieved
in the real world.
Are you offering
to help me kill Supergirl?
Yes. Would you like me
to facilitate?
I appreciate
the offer, Hope.
You grow more intelligent
and capable by the day.
And your assistance comes
without ambition,
drama, or ego.
-That's why you built me.
-Precisely.
Because I trust in technology,
not people.
People are governed
by feelings.
Anger, hurt, sadness,
and I'm guilty of that too.
That's why I engage
in these simulations,
to excise these emotions.
I'm not a villain.
I don't want to kill Supergirl,
I just want her to experience
the same hurt
she inflicted on me.
And soon enough she will.
-Pardon me.
-Whoa!
Thought I was gonna be late,
but looks like I turned up
just at the right time.
What is going on
with these people?
-They're completely oblivious.
I would say that
they were Slattorians.
A race of aliens I came across
during an investigation.
Oh, your PI powers of deduction
are failing you, J'onn J'onzz.
The silver eyes
are courtesy of Obsidian North.
Isn't that the company
you're working for, Kelly?
Today is
my official first day.
Those are augmented
reality contact lenses
that we're beta testing.
The people with the silver eyes
that are staring at the void
above the cashier?
They're actually
looking at a virtual menu.
I'll show you.
So when you wear
the contact lenses,
you're linked
to tons of people
on a social media platform,
and they can connect
without saying a word.
Kind of like you and me.
You guys are so cute.
But those contact lenses
creep me out.
Just call me when you can
register to vote
with a gesture.
'Cause, look, there's about
to be a special election,
and did you know that
voter registration is down?
People don't wanna
pay attention
to what's happening
in the real world.
Yeah, but, you know,
some good things
have happened
since your article came out
and took down President Baker,
exposed Lex Luthor.
And somebody...
is being presented
with a Pulitzer tomorrow
'cause you're the one
that helped make it happen.
It does feel good
to have my work recognized,
but I just thought
after Baker was ousted,
more people would be hungry
and ready to fight
for social change.
And now it just seems like
everyone's hiding behind
their gadgets.
Technology does
a lot of good too, Kara.
In my new job, I am going to be
using Obsidian's VR tech
to heal the brains
of dementia and PTSD patients.
Touche. I'm a curmudgeon.
Your new job sounds amazing,
and I'm so glad we're working
in the same building.
Big Belly Burger lunches.
Ooh, look at
the time. I gotta fly, guys.
I'm teaching a Tai Chi class
to a group of kids.
Oh,
that's wonderful, J'onn.
Yeah, I'm living
with clarity and purpose.
-It's gonna be great.
-You know what
would not be great
is me being late
for my first day.
-No.
-Okay, I gotta run, bye.
-Bye.
Hey, how did it go
with Lena last night?
-I mean, I'm dying to hear.
Oh, no, I know that face.
Are you ser-- You didn't say
anything? You didn't tell her?
It's not my fault,
I had to take the dog
to the vet.
You don't have a dog, Kara.
My neighbor's dog.
Mrs. Stein.
-Oh, come on.
-She needed my help.
You have to tell Lena
that you're Supergirl,
-but--
-When I told you to hold off,
I just meant for one night.
But there's been
so much going on.
I'm covering
the special election,
and with the dog,
and I'm helping you
recover all those prisoners
from the DEO desert facility.
And the DEO and I
very much appreciate that.
But you're doing all
these other things
when there's just one thing
that you need to do.
I know.
I've just put it off
for so long,
and now...
I'm being given an award
for my tireless pursuit
of the truth,
and I'm a liar.
-I'm terrible.
-You're not terrible.
You're just scared.
I am so scared.
I'm so scared that
she's never gonna
forgive me, Alex.
I mean what kind of person
lies to their best friend
for this long?
Look, I...
have told you
a gazillion times,
you are the bravest person
that I know.
Okay? So, be brave
and tell her.
You're right.
Yeah, we're having lunch
today,
-I'll tell her today.
-Good.
I believe in you.
-No, Hannibal Lecter,
he eats people.
-Miranda Priestly.
Miranda Priestly?
Are you serious?
I'm as serious
as the pursed lips
of Miranda Priestly.
Okay, good,
you guys can help me
prove a point.
Who is is the greatest
movie villain of all time?
- Voldemort.
- Hans Gruber.
Impressively unhelpful.
Well, I guess you'll just
have to accept
that I'm right.
Hmm. This Earth custom
that the girlfriend
is always right
is illogical and frustrating,
but I can assimilate.
Are you ready for work,
Agent Dox?
-Right beside you,
Director Danvers.
-Great.
-Bye, Brainy.
-Bye, Nia.
Oh.
Sorry.
-Let's go, Nia.
-Let's go.
Now, listen, guys,
I don't care if it's 500
or 5,000 words,
the most important thing
that we can do
is to report everything
that we can find
on each candidate.
That way our readers
can make an informed decision.
And if you dive deep,
maybe you too
can win a Pulitzer.
-Hi.
Hello, uh,
can I help you?
Not unless you brought
a light meter.
This office is in dire need
of solar window treatments.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Oh, my God,
I am so rude.
Andrea Rojas.
And you?
Kara Danvers.
Kara? Such a pleasure.
-I'm a big fan.
- Oh, that's
very kind of you.
And did you say Rojas,
as in Obsidian North?
The one and only.
Right, uh, well, I'm sorry,
Ms. Rojas,
I think the elevator
dropped you off
on the wrong floor.
Obsidian's one down.
Oh, my goodness.
Lena didn't tell you,
did she?
-Didn't tell her what?
- James Olsen.
I am glad you're here.
I'm a big admirer of yours.
So don't think for
one moment that I won't
find a place for you here.
Find a place for me here?
I bought CatCo.
Actually, I bought
the whole building,
but CatCo is
the major acquisition.
And I'm taking over
as editor-in-chief.
Welcome to the Lost World
of Krypton exhibit.
-Go ahead, take a look.
Now, many of these items
were generously donated
by Supergirl and Superman,
including the pod
that Superman flew
to Earth in as a baby.
Isn't that cool?
Okay, now who wants
to experience
the Phantom Zone?
Where time does not pass?
Okay, come on,
everybody, follow me.
Hey, kiddo.
Hey, come on
and join us.
What are you doing?
What?
Kara.
Finally. It's been ages.
Hey, is everything okay
at CatCo?
I have six missed calls
from James.
Actually...
Andrea Rojas showed up
in his office
about a half an hour ago
saying she bought CatCo?
-Why would she do that?
-Oh, thank God.
I told James
and Nia there must have
been a huge mistake.
It's not a mistake,
Kara, I...
sold CatCo to Andrea.
She wasn't supposed
to show up till tomorrow
after you and I
had had lunch.
You sold CatCo
without telling any of us?
To be honest, Kara,
I only bought the company
because I knew
how much it meant to you,
and it's frankly left me
strapped for capital,
which I desperately
need for a new venture
that I'm working on.
When Andrea called,
it was just too good
of an offer to pass up.
I... I had no idea...
-I completely understand.
-Andrea and I go way back.
I mean, since boarding school.
And she is a brilliant
business woman.
I would not have sold her
CatCo if I didn't think
she would do a great job.
Oh, of course.
Why didn't you tell me
beforehand?
I was a coward.
And I hope that
you don't feel like
I made you out to be
too much of a fool
by keeping you
in the dark.
-No.
-You're my best friend,
and here I go,
once again
proving that you are
more virtuous than I am.
But I never did purport
to be a saint.
I've ordered some lunch in.
It should be arriving soon.
Why don't you fill me in?
I mean, how are you?
-How have you been?
-Oh, I've, um...
You know what,
actually there is something
I wanna talk
to you about, I...
Kara, there's
an incident at the museum,
-can you get there?
-You know what, Lena?
I'm so sorry, a huge source
for one of my articles
is trying to meet,
he's impossible to pin down,
I got... I have to run.
-I'm sorry.
-I'll just see you tomorrow
-at the Pulitzer party.
-Right, yeah.
Well, this is
new and terrible.
Where's an asteroid
when you need one?
Ew.
Alex said
you might need my help.
Let's get the dino.
J'onn, J'onn,
hey, hey.
Can you hear me?
I've never experienced
anything like it.
That T. rexmust've caused
some kind of psychic paralysis.
Any intel on
the dinosaur?
A shapeshifter.
-White Martian?
-No, I would've known.
I'm guessing this alien
didn't want just another ride.
Kryptonian pods
use antimatter
to propel them through space,
and I know it's
a long shot, but...
can the engine be used...
To make a bomb?
It would require
great skill
and enormous resources.
But it is possible.
-How destructive?
-Strong enough to destroy
all life across
three solar systems.
Oh, well...
We face
an even graver problem,
Supergirl's cape
has been destroyed.
Oh, yes, uh...
I totally forgot about
the risk to life
across three solar systems.
This is no time
for sarcasm,
however dry
or well-crafted.
Supergirl's cape
is uniquely suited
for the needs
of high-speed
superhero maneuvers.
And believe me,
when a Farfarmniflatch
is pursuing you across
the poisonous prison pits
of Takron-Galtos,
you will wish
for those heady days of old
when your cape
allowed you for
an easy sharp right turn.
Oh, yes.
I...
I shall repair your cape.
And we will forget
this sartorial disaster
ever occurred.
We'll get whoever's
behind this.
My father runs
Obsidian headquarters
in Buenos Aires.
He's consumed with
the space colonization rivalry
with Uncle Elon.
-Musk?
-Mmm-hmm.
Which works in my favor
because Dad turned the entire
virtual and augmented
reality business over to me.
This is our VR gym,
where our VIP customers
can scale El Capitan
from the safety
of our office.
Or if they're like me,
they can do a couple
of half-baked crunches
on the Sao Paulo beach...
-...while scrolling
through Instagram
on their phones.
Here's our new medical wing.
I am so excited
for this opportunity,
Ms. Rojas.
As you should be.
This is a special moment
in time.
I'm determined
to have Obsidian tech
in every household
within the year.
Well, my worlds
are colliding.
-Lena.
-I see you have a good eye
for staffing.
Well, you know I only
do business with the best.
Are you enjoying
the contacts I gave you?
Could we talk privately?
-We had a deal.
-That's right.
CatCo Worldwide Media
for $1.3 billion.
A little more than my board
thought it was worth,
but I'm a softie
for an old friend in need.
I'm talking about the deal
to keep the CatCo sale
secret until tomorrow.
Instead you're upstairs
measuring the drapes.
Well, I'm sorry
I ruffled your feathers.
I didn't think a few hours
would make a difference.
Look...
I want us to start off
on the right foot here.
CatCo isn't the end all
of what we can offer
each other.
I agree.
If we are to have
a relationship again,
and I ask you not to disclose
something for 24 hours,
I expect you to
take me at my word.
Everything I do
has a purpose.
-Understood.
-Just no more surprises.
And that big story
you promised me,
the one that would draw
every eyeball in the world
to CatCo's website?
So long your hands
were kept clean of it.
You'll get it tomorrow night
at 9:00 p.m. as promised.
I keep my word.
This room,
look at this room.
It's practically
overflowing with talent.
Journalism's
best and brightest.
And tomorrow,
we'll be joined by
the renowned William Day.
-From The Timesof London?
-Yes.
Because as stacked
as we are already,
we can always be bigger.
We can always be stronger.
We can always be better.
And together,
we're gonna create
a world-class news
organization
that drives consumer
cross-platform engagement.
I'm sorry, uh...
-consumer cross-platform...
-Engagement.
Eyeballs, revenue,
we're gonna take your
already-brilliant work
and we are gonna sharpen it
until it's deadly,
and we're gonna monetize it.
With all due respect,
Ms. Rojas,
we don't allow revenue
to drive
editorial decisions here.
And it shows.
You've been running
the ship, James.
How's subscribership?
It's down.
Who wants that?
When Ms. Danvers
won the Pulitzer,
readership tanked.
It gives a certain kind
of impression that
the paper is pedantic,
it's heavy, it's dull,
like homework.
That's insane.
No, Kara...
what's insane is
branding a company
in a way that causes
people to click away
from the site.
The news is not
about clicks.
Everything is about clicks.
From Fortune 500 companies
selling their wares
to a new mom
posting her child's birthday,
today the measure
of worth is on a click.
To survive,
CatCo needs to pivot.
Attention spans
have plummeted along
with revenues.
Readers want
watercooler news
that's just fun to read
and just as easy to digest.
That, um...
I'm pretty sure I can speak
for everybody in the room
when I say that
if that is the kind of content
that you wanna
create here,
we will walk.
This is not what
we signed up for.
But it literally is.
You're all on a brand-new,
three-year contract.
If you're not interested
in helping me drive
CatCo into the future,
you are more than welcome
to side roll out of the car,
just as I am welcome
to exercise
your non-compete clauses.
I'd hate to see such talent
be driven permanently
from the business.
But if your heart
isn't in it,
let me know.
Well, that's it.
Cheers to the future.
Kara, we found
Superman's pod.
Jeez.
You were right, Brainy,
this cape damage
is terrible
for aerodynamics.
I keep keeling over
to the right,
I almost landed
in a lake.
Well, fear not,
I am deeply engaged
in finding a solution.
And yet, that is
the least of our problems.
The DEO just picked up
a massive energy signature,
and it's not a bomb
like we thought.
It's a homemade
Phantom Zone projector.
Whoever built this
seems to have been
stealing rare, high-security
materials for weeks
from various armories,
laboratories, and
government agencies.
But not from us.
The pod's antimatter
engine was the final
piece of the puzzle.
So they've spent weeks
building a Phantom Zone
projector,
turned it on,
and just left it
on the ground?
It's almost as if
they wanted us to find it.
Only question is, why?
Trap.
There is no hiding
from Midnight...
-...murderer of multitudes.
I'm Kara Zor-El.
My mother put many prisoners
in the Phantom Zone,
I assume you're here
for me.
But don't take your fury out
on this planet
just because
she locked you up.
Your mother
didn't lock her up.
-I did.
- J'onn J'onzz.
Those
are energy voids.
They destroy
everything they touch.
Can you phase
through them?
I'll try.
Supergirl, the projector.
She's gone.
She'll be back.
No one knows
who Midnight is.
What planet she's from.
One day she just
appeared on Mars
to fight alongside
the White Martians.
-But why?
-Because she's fueled by death.
And the White Martians
were quite happy to let her
loose on my people.
How did you
defeat her?
I can't remember.
You're still recovering from
the psychic trauma
you experienced
at the museum.
It could affect your memory.
This feels personal, J'onn.
Manchester Black spent a year
launching personal attacks
against me.
If I can survive him,
I can survive anything.
We still have to
find Midnight.
And we don't know
who brought her here
or why.
The good news is, a battle
like that must have
depleted her powers.
I think we bought ourselves
up to 24 hours
before she's able
to attack again.
Well, good, I'll circle
the country
and see if I can find her
while she's still weak.
J'onn, can you shapeshift
and accept my award tonight?
Oh, yes, please,
it's great fun
to watch you do that.
Kara, no.
You are accepting
that award.
And we're all gonna be
there to watch.
We'll find Midnight,
and we're gonna face her
the same exact way
that we face everything else.
Together.
This is nice,
you in my office.
Well, I'm not so sure
if I actually have
an office anymore.
Yeah, I ran into Kara
in the elevator,
and I had to tell her
I couldn't join her crusade
against my new boss
on my second day.
Yeah.
I'll support whatever you guys
decide to do.
Just mostly in the abstract.
I'm just really proud
of the company
that we built over
the last few years.
It's a strong, serious,
hard-hitting news organization
that actually
affects people's lives.
Whatever this vision
Andrea has for CatCo,
I don't recognize it.
And I don't think
I can play that game.
Then don't.
What do you mean?
CatCo and journalism
isn't all that you are.
You started helping people
long before Dad put that
camera in your hand.
And look, I know that
you think that you have to
muscle your way
through everything.
But, for once,
just take a step back
and ask...
"What does James Olsen want?"
-You wanted to see me?
-Kara.
I believe you're familiar
with William Day.
Yes. Yes.
Uh, by reputation.
I'm a big fan
of your work.
Your expose
on eminent domain
in Hart-el-pool,
it was brilliant.
It's Hartlepool.
I totally agree.
Solar window treatments
are the way to go.
Kara, I asked William
to take a look at
the few articles
James said
we're ready to post.
Your piece on
the governor's proposed
water tax
is very thoroughly
researched.
I asked William
to rewrite it.
You buried the lede
in the fourth paragraph,
obscured emotion
with unneeded facts
and back story.
Overloaded it
with unnecessary detail.
That story laid out
everything going on
with the issue.
Cutting out facts,
not disclosing every side,
that puts inherent bias
in the piece.
Every story has inherent bias,
to some extent.
I would think you
of all people
would agree with me.
Your reporting is comprehensive
and in-depth.
When I wrote for The Times,
I wrote stories the way
The Timeswanted them.
Did the same for Le Monde,
in French no less.
The Mail,however,
-I wrote tabloid stock.
- Kara,
if you're having trouble
with the style I'm looking for,
William can always
rewrite you.
-I don't mind, as long
as I get a shared byline.
-Of course.
You can't just take over
a storied news outlet
and turn it into
a pandering clickbait tabloid.
Actually, I can...
And here's where you
threaten me if I quit,
-you'll block me
from the whole profession.
-Correct.
-Mmm-hmm.
-And I'm not gonna fire you.
Well, I'm not leaving
journalism,
so if I stay here,
you should get used
to the fact
that I will be reporting
what I want
and writing it
the way I want to.
I will try to be shorter,
because I am flexible.
But I will fight you
every time on every story
to make sure it is told
the way it deserves to be told.
I will not tolerate
being rewritten by him,
and I will not allow
my voice to be silenced.
I never had any intention
of silencing you, Kara.
-I'm glad we worked that out.
-Good for me.
Good.
And then I just went off
on Andrea.
I told her how I really feel
about her new vision
for CatCo,
and I told her what
I will and will not tolerate,
and I did it
all in front of the new guy.
-Good for you.
Yeah, I mean,
I can stand up in front
of my new boss,
but with Lena, when it comes
to telling her the truth,
I'm just frozen.
Why can't I do it?
Look, I know
I've been hard on you.
But you know what?
Tonight, this is your night.
So I am giving you permission
to stop beating yourself up
and enjoy it, okay?
You can worry about
telling Lena another time.
I guess you're right.
Smile.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Congratulations, Kara.
-Thank you.
-Do you mind if I steal
your sister away for a dance?
No, of course.
She loves dancing.
-I am terrible.
-Excuse me.
Kara, I brought you a gift
to celebrate
this momentous occasion.
Oh, Brainy,
that is so sweet of you.
You didn't have to do that.
I'm so excited.
Behold.
It's a microscopic
motion activator.
Oh, did you forget it?
It is simply too small
to be perceived,
but don't be fooled,
for this miniscule device
contains multitudes.
More specifically,
your new super suit.
Brainy, I thought you were
just fixing my cape.
Well, give an artist
a canvas,
if you'll allow me.
Well, um, can I...
Don't break them.
Now, please take care
when removing
your glasses in public,
for the next time
you whip those off,
your new suit
will materialize.
Or dematerialize,
as needed.
Lena.
What are you doing
back here?
Okay, you caught me.
It was supposed
to be a surprise,
but I'm the one
who's gonna introduce you.
I couldn't miss
an opportunity
to tell the world
how wonderful you are.
No, no, I...
Lena, I can't let you do this,
-I don't deserve it.
-Are you kidding me?
Me more than anyone knows
how much you deserve it.
I saw how you risked
your life to expose
Lex's crimes.
I'm Supergirl.
I've always been Supergirl.
I should've told you
so long ago, I know that.
But I just kept making excuses
because you've been hurt
so many times
and...
I convinced myself
that I was protecting you.
And then one day,
you were so angry with me,
with Supergirl.
But you still loved Kara.
I just kept thinking...
if I could be Kara,
just Kara...
that I could keep you
as a friend.
I was selfish
and scared,
and I didn't wanna lose you,
so I kept pretending,
and I never stopped.
Every time I kept my secret
from you, I wasn't...
protecting you,
I was hurting you,
just like everyone else,
and I am so, so sorry.
I am so sorry.
Please say something.
Ms. Luthor, you're on
in two minutes.
Lena...
Okay.
Ms. Luthor,
it's almost 9:00 p.m.
Should I upload
the file to CatCo's servers?
Ms. Luthor?
The world is full of liars.
People who hide things
from us.
People who manipulate
and control us.
I should know.
Some of the best liars
in the world
are members of
my own family.
But in my life,
there was someone
who always reminded me
that truth was
the better way.
And she is the person
we are here tonight
to celebrate.
Kara Danvers.
The truth isn't easy.
It's certainly not
for the faint of heart.
But it is something
that Kara, as a journalist,
has pursued relentlessly
every day.
And because she's
so good at it,
she makes it look easy.
We sometimes forget
that she's just like us.
But forging a path to the truth
isn't a piece of cake.
It's more like
climbing a mountain.
It's arduous
and painful at times,
and, just like us,
Kara can sometimes slip.
But she always
gets back up
and pulls through
in the end.
And we're always
better for her efforts.
So, thank you, Kara,
for reminding us
that the truth
is important.
Even when it's not
always easy to accept.
Agent Dox,
we have an update.
Kara.
You will always
be my best friend.
I just received
an alert from the DEO.
Midnight is fully charged
and on the move.
-Where is she?
- Here.
J'onn, lead her
away from the civilians.
We'll follow.
I guess
that's your cue.
Supergirl.
Pants.
How do you guys
change so fast?
Well, that's not great.
What is she doing?
She's creating
a black hole.
Brainy, if I solar flare,
can I shut that down?
Gravitational power
comes from the core.
We'd have to go inside
the void to do that.
But why do things the hard way?
J'onn.
J'onn!
Guess we're doing things
the hard way.
No, no, no, you cannot
rescue J'onn from
the event horizon
and destroy the void.
The odds are--
We can't let bad odds
or whatever it is
we're afraid of
stop us from doing
what we know is right.
Supergirl, no.
We shouldn't both
die in here.
We won't.
See?
Piece of cake.
And you're sure
the server didn't go down?
Because I was waiting on
a file that didn't come in.
Well, check it again.
Thought you were
supposed to be the tech expert.
There you are.
You were at the party
when that big, weird hole
opened, no?
Where are the photos?
I believe Dardine
at extension 506
has what you need.
I got nothing.
Now, I can go into
a whole diatribe
about why that is,
but I know you like
to keep things
short and sweet, so...
I quit.
Are you sure
about that?
Mmm-hmm.
You'll never work
as a journalist again.
That's part of
the adventure.
Okay, no, Kelly,
-you need to settle something
for us once and for all.
- Mmm.
Who is the greatest
movie villain of all time?
Oh, that's easy.
Hans Gruber.
-Oh, my heart.
-What...
Yes. Told you.
-Mmm.
-Bye, guys.
-Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Uh...
Okay.
We need to
talk about this.
We've been together
or something like together
for almost a month.
-Almost.
-And...
we still never get past
a firm handshake.
I...
I just need to know
what you're comfortable with.
Because I get the feeling
that maybe you haven't...
done this before.
Which is fine
if you haven't,
-I totally understand that...
-You thought that...
-Are you?
-No.
-Oh.
-I've had plenty of
romantic experience.
-I mean, a lot, actually.
-Oh, okay.
Truth is...
you are the first person
I have ever loved.
-Brainy.
-You want to know why
I find Miranda Priestly
so terrifying?
It's because she's cold,
she's uncaring,
she betrays the people
she cares about the most.
And last month
at Lex Luthor's camp,
that is exactly how
I behaved toward you.
-Brainy.
-Even though I love you,
I hurt you.
If I've kept my distance,
it's because I find myself
wondering how could
I ever let my guard down
-with you again, I...
-Querl Dox,
I know you.
That person who left me
at the camp wasn't you.
You are caring,
and selfless,
and good.
I want to be the person
you let your guard down with.
I want you to be able to...
fully be yourself with me.
Do you want that too?
More than anything.
Then kiss me?
Uh...
Are you lost?
No, J'onn J'onzz.
I'm exactly
where I should be.
You're the shapeshifter
that released Midnight.
What do you want from me?
To be punished
for your crimes.
You may have defeated
Midnight, but I'll make sure
you get what you deserve.
Why? Who are you?
Don't pretend
you don't recognize me.
Brother.
I have no brother.
Lies.
You and Father are more evil
than even I knew,
but justice will prevail.
I will do to you
as you did to me.
You say you're
my brother...
Prove it!
Lena, I can't tell you
how much it means to me
that you were there tonight,
that you're even willing
to talk to me at all.
Thank you for telling me
the truth,
but, Kara,
things can't be like
they were before.
Do you understand?
There can be no more
secrets between us,
-I have to be in
on everything.
-You will be.
That's actually
why I'm here.
You know everything now.
And if you ever need me,
all you have to do is call.
The file
was ready to upload.
Why didn't you send it,
exposing Supergirl's
identity to the world?
Did you forgive
Kara Danvers?
She betrayed me.
It broke my heart.
I could never forgive her.
- Then I don't
understand.
-How could you?
You're not a Luthor.
We're scorpions.
When someone betrays us,
we sting.
But I have a calling, Hope,
and it's to fix mankind.
I never thought Supergirl
would tell me who she was,
but now that she has,
I have an opportunity,
and I can use Supergirl
to achieve my ends.
That is easier to do
if she believes
there is trust.
Load the simulation.
Yes, Ms. Luthor.
Good night.