♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Growling continues]
Uh...
Hey, guys?
♪♪
[Screaming]
[Panting]
♪♪
Make sure
they don't get out.
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
Aah!
Damn.
You okay?
I almost had it.
Daryl: Nah,
it's too high.
You risk
breakin' your neck.
We need to find
a better way.
[Growling continues]
You got something?
Groundwater's
deeper in here.
That water's
coming from outside.
Carol: I don't see
a way across.
Whoa, whoa.
Go back, go back.
We could use those
to jump across.
Nice.
Wait.
For real?
♪♪
All right.
You ready?
Let's go.
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
♪♪
Come on.
Let's go!
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunts]
Do it now!
No!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Come on!
♪♪
Hey, hey!
Come on!
Come on.
I gotcha.
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Hey! Hey!
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Hey,
hand me that thing.
♪♪
Knock yourself out,
dude.
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
Alright.
I need you to stay here,all right?
Keep everyone together.
Should I even askhow we're doing on food?
Not great.
Food?
How long do you think
we gonna be here?
Hey,
no worries.
Walkers got in here
somehow.
We'll get out.
I think we knowexactly how they got here.
Alpha put them here.
These are theirs.
We have to assume
we're not alone.
♪♪
I'm fine.
Just a little winded.
She's claustrophobic.
Why didn't you
think of that
before you got us alltrapped down here?
Hey.
It's not the time
for this.
Why not?
Seems likewe have plenty of it.
♪♪
What the hellwere you thinking, huh?
Running off like that
by yourself.
Daryl: Hey!
We ain't got time
for this shit.
We got
in this mess together.
We're gonna
get out of it together.
Now follow me.
I think
I found a way out.
♪♪
[Insects chirping]
The enemy
are watching us.
A small group
crossed the border.
They went straight to the edge
of the national forest.
The horde...
They knewexactly where to look.
Did they find it?
We underestimated them.
We have to assume
they've been sending spies
across the border.
I want more patrols
around the camp.
♪♪
I want you
to take a message
to our eyes
along the border --
they have failed.
♪♪
[Water dripping]
[Wind whistling]
Hey. Can I --
Can I get matches?
You should try to take it easyfor a minute.
I can't.
I need
to do something.
Thanks.
I never told you
I was claustrophobic.
If I only knew
what you told me,
I wouldn't know shit.
Look who's talking.
It's like I can't eventurn my back on you anymore.
It's bad enoughI got Aaron running around
with that skin freak.
Now I gotta worry about you
all half-cocked
every time
you go outside.
I'm sorry.
I begged you
to talk to me.
I wanna be there
for you.
I do.
I don't know
what to do anymore.
[Sighs]
I can't stop
thinking about it.
I know I have to,
but I can't.
[Breathes deeply]
♪♪
Oh, God.
I don't want
to just kill Alpha.
I want to hurt her.
♪♪
I want to make her
regret everything.
I want her to beg
for forgiveness,
and then
I want to kill her.
If I went through
all the shitthat you went through...
I'd probably feel
the same way.
♪♪
Unless you tried
to stop me.
♪♪
You gotta quit
all this.
You gotta.
People you care aboutare starting to get hurt.
♪♪
I didn't mean for any of this
to happen.
I know I have to --
I know
I have to s--
You gotta
not bullshit me.
♪♪
Don't bullshit me.
You gotta promise.
I gotta knowwe're on the same team.
♪♪
We fight
for our future.
We don't fight
for revenge.
I promise.
♪♪
Alright.
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Wind whistling]
Skins!
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Let's go.
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
If we don't follow each other
in the dark,
we're gonna
get split up.
She's right.We stick together.
At least we know
there's a way out now.
Yeah,
but where?
I think
they went this way.
You see
where they went?
Not exactly,
but...
I know a road sign
when I see one.
♪♪
Hey,
come on.
♪♪
[Match strikes]
Negan:
Sorry to butt in.
No pun intended.
[Zipper zips]
The latrine is at the edge
of the camp for hygiene,
not privacy.
Ah, well, actually,
I, um...
just wanted
to talk.
About?
Well, I hear we're supposed to
be keeping our eyes peeled
for a spylurkin' in the woods.
I have an alternate theory
to run by you.
The spy
you're looking for?
Right here
in your camp.
My people know the enemy have
nothing to offer except lies.
Maybe they do.
Maybe they don't.
Believe it or not,
I have beenwhere you are right now.
And if you don't want to end upwhere I am right now,
I suggest you zig
where I zagged.
You and I --
very different.
I had people.
I had a system.
I thoughtthey believed in it,
just like you.
See, the thing is,
you stay king or queenlong enough,
with people telling youall day, every day
that your shit
don't stink,
eventually,you start to believe it.
The thing is...
it still stinks.
Who?
Well, based onmy own personal experience,
I'd saylook closer to home.
And, no,I am not talkin' about
Frankenstein's Hemorrhoid.
That big dudeis clearly a goose stepper.
But the little one...?
You see,she is close enough to you
that she knowsexactly where that horde was.
But she guards
the border,
which meansshe's close enough to the enemy
that they could've
gotten to her.
♪♪
[Grunts]
I will not have you
sowing paranoia.
[Grunts]
If you breathe a word of this
to anyone,
I will take these.
Aah!
[Body thuds]
[Groans]
♪♪
This is it!
Oh, God.
♪♪
Alright,
just give me one minute.
I'll be fine.
♪♪
Or not.
Ooh, boy.
[Sighs]
"You are...are...
O-K."
"You are..."
"You are okay."
[Chuckles]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
Oh, man.
Hey.
You all right
back there?
Yeah, sure.
I'm just a 6'2" dude
that had trouble fittinginto airplane bathrooms.
[Grunts]Why wouldn't I be okay?
[Grunts]
Fair enough.
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
Alright, I'm out.
Follow my voice.
Come on.
That's it.
♪♪
[Grunts]
Alright.
Come on.
♪♪
[Grunts]
I'm good.
♪♪
[Panting]
[Grunting]
Carol?
Carol!
[Panting]
I'm here.
You hurt?
I'm okay.
Can you see
my light?
Yes.
Just follow my light.
[Panting]
♪♪
I can't.
I can't!
Yes, you can.
Come on.
We're gonna
get through this together.
Come on.
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Grunting, panting]
♪♪
Go ahead.
I gotcha, I gotcha.
[Breathing heavily]
Hey, guys...
Aaron:
What is it?
[Crank whirring]What is it?
Just be quiet
for a second.
[Whirring continues]
[Walkers growling]
Go, go, go! Go!
Go, go, go!
♪♪
[Growling continues]
Jerry, come on!
[Grunting]
♪♪
Come on!
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Jerry!
Come on!
You're almost there!
Guys!
I'm -- I'm stuck.
[Growling continues]
Here --
take my hand!
[Grunting]
Aah!
[Growling continues]
My feet!
They got my feet!
They're biting my feet!
[Grunting]
My feet!
Take your gear off!
Take it off!
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Come on.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Aah!
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Panting]
You good?
It's okay.
They didn't bite through.
You're good.It's alright. It's okay.
[Grunting]
[Walker growling]
♪♪
Hey.
Look!
Wait!
[Gasps]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Walkers growling]
[Boards cracking]
Why are we standing aroundlooking at it?
Kelly: We got to be
very careful.
We take out
the wrong piece,
this whole thing
is gonna collapse.
♪♪
Where's Gamma?
She never made it
to the border.
I've sent four scouts
to find her.
If there are spies
among us,
maybe she's been captured.
Or she is the spy.
You believe
she has gone over?
I suspect.
♪♪
I want you
to track her down.
Bring her to me.
And if she has betrayed us,
I will kill her.
♪♪
I will
deal with her.
And the pack
will watch.
♪♪
Alright,
find something to dig with.
[Grunting]
Hey, Aaron,
can you help me with this?Yeah, yeah.
[Gear clattering]
Kelly:Hey, check this out.
Yo.
Somebody leftthis crate of dynamite.
Yeah, okay,
that's really cool.
But maybe
somebody left it there
because it's obviously
insanely dangerous.
That thing's sweatier
than I am.
I need you
to put it back.
Very carefully.
♪♪
Just -- Just...
Want to
take a break?
I can rest when --
when we get home.
You in a hurry?
I just
don't wanna hang out here
any longer
than I have to.
Do you?
No, but...
you barely rested,
haven't eaten anything.
You never stop.
I didn't leave things goodwith Yumiko.
♪♪
I'm sorry.
Me too.
♪♪
You.
Looks like
Mom's mad at me.
♪♪
Keep walkin'.
You know, this feels like
some sort of...
fraternity initiation.
Is that
what this is?
Huh?
Am I gonna get
my skin suit
and finally get to learnthe secret Whisperer handshake?
Eyes front.
Alright.
You don't wanna talk?
I'm down with that.
We just won't talk.
You know, I...
I'm big enough to admit it,alright?
I...
I am not good with long,uncomfortable silences.
Stop here.
I said...
eyes front.
Shit.
[Sighs]
Take off your clothes.
[Breathing heavily]
You know what?You were -- You were right.
[Sighs]
We are different.
I made myself
into a monster,
because that iswhat the world needed.
[Sighs]
I built something.
I saved people.
My name --
it meant something.
Turn around.
Whoa.
You're a crass man.
I reckoned
you might appreciate
a crass reward.
A reward?
For what?
The spy.
Gamma.
It took courage
to do what you did.
And I want
to express my gratitude
in a way
that you will understand.
Wait.
Are you just gonna...
leave that mask on?
Does my true skin
disturb you?
Not at all.
Weirdly the opposite.
Wait.
This isn't some sort of, uh,praying mantis situation, is it?
You cut off my head offafterwards?
Yeah, sorry.
I can't help but noticethat you didn't say no to that.
Ah,
you know what?
It's been
a long time.
I reckonI will take my chances.
♪♪
Stop...talking.
[Crashing]
Come on, go.
[Birds chirping]
Just a little more!
[Coughing]
Where's Carol?
♪♪
Damn it!
[Grunting]
[Walkers growling in distance]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Match strikes]
Oh.
Aah!
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
Daryl:
Take my hand.
Come on.
[Both grunting]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
What the hell
are you doing?
[Breathing heavily]
We can take out half her hordefrom here.
You're gonna
get yourself killed.
♪♪
[Voice breaking]
She killed my boy.
♪♪
[Crying]
I know.
But you gotta
come back with me.
Please.
Come on.
♪♪
Aah!
[Gasps][Crashing]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Come on!
Hey! Move!
[Grunting]
♪♪
Hey! Hey!
Come on!
What are you doing?!
♪♪
Come on!
Ohh!
♪♪
We got freaks!
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
[Crashing]
[Coughing]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Rumbling]
♪♪
Magna:
Come on!
Hurry!
I can't --
[Grunting]
♪♪
Aaron:
Come on!
Come on, guys!
♪♪
[Wood creaking]
Give me your hand!
I'll pull her up!
Come on!
Give me your hand.
[Rumbling]
♪♪
[Grunting]
We've got more skins!
[Screaming]
♪♪
[Shouts]
Get outta here!
Jerry!
Aah!
Jerry,
give me your hand!
Aah!
♪♪
Jerry, now!
Come on!
♪♪
[Explosion]
[Coughing]
No!
[Crying]
♪♪
Aaron: Daryl...
Daryl.
♪♪
It'll take us a weekto clear this.
[Groans]
Then help me!
[Crying] No.
We can't!
♪♪
That blast is gonna call
walkers and Whisperers
from a hundred miles
from here.
We don't want our backs
pressed against this mountain
when they come.
We can't save them
if we're dead.
[Sniffles]
Come on.
♪♪
[Crying]
[Voice breaking]
Go ahead and say it to me.
I deserve it.
Just say it to me.
You were right
about everything.
Just say it.
No, please.
You cared about her.
And now she's gone
because of me.
Please,
just say it!
Please say it!
[Crying]
Go home.
Tell the others
we found the horde.
Where you gonna be?
They got out before us.
There's gotta be
another way in.
♪♪
Carol: No.