Vamos ter um bebê.
Bom dia, Shaun.
Você estava
me observando dormir?
- Sim.
- Hmm.
Vamos ter um bebê.
Milímetros.
E esse bebê
está me fazendo sentir
tipo ... Eu comi
sushi de três meses.
(Suspira)
Bom dia, berry.
Por que você está fazendo a mamãe se
sentir assim?
Vamos ... chamá-lo de Berry?
Por enquanto, porque
ele é do tamanho de um mirtilo.
Eu posso apenas imaginar
seu rosto
em um
bebezinho do tamanho de um mirtilo.
Na
semana sete,
o feto desenvolveu
mãos e pés palmados,
e você começou
a formar um tampão de muco.
Ooh, sua respiração
está me matando, Shaun.
Eu escovei meus dentes
duas vezes
porque pensei
que poderíamos fazer sexo.
The mint from the...
The toothpaste is, um...
It's... Mm-mm.
(SNIFFS)
[♪♪♪♪]
Stop smirking like
you're picturing me naked.
Don't have to picture it.
Saw it already.
You're running a little late.
Did I keep you up too long last night?
Don't flatter yourself.
I'm not late,
and it wasn't that long.
What are you doing?
Shielding us
from the rain.
What do you think this is,
The Notebook?
It's raining,
and I shared my umbrella.
Having sex
doesn't make us a thing.
We need to make
clear boundaries.
I don't need romantic
gestures from you.
I shared my umbrella.
I didn't propose.
But I hear your message
loud and clear.
You hate me,
I hate you.
See you tonight?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Can I help you?
Hello, Claire.
My name's Miles Browne.
I'm...
Your father.
What are you
doing here?
I've owed you a lot of answers
for a long time, and...
Go home.
Um, whoa.
I just, uh...
Well... Well, I wish
I... I was a... A better...
Um, uh...
I don't want you to...
(STAMMERS)
Can you lift your arms?
Uh...
Keep them up.
Okay. Repeat after me.
"Don't cry
over spilled milk."
D-Don't...
F-fry...
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Oh.
We need to get you to the hospital.
I think you're having a stroke.
Theme music playing...
*THE GOOD DOCTOR*
Season 04  Episode 13
Episode Title: "Spilled Milk"
Aired on: March 29, 2021
Sync corrections by srjanapala
The quickstep
is my nemesis.
I lost my footing and landed
on a 90-year-old judge
with very sharp elbows.
And he insisted I come in
even though I'm fine.
Just a little sore.
Yeah, but Maya's
"a little sore"
is a normal person's
excruciating.
Take the compliment, babe.
You're shivering.
The abdomen is tense
and distended.
She's hypotensive.
We need to do
an ultrasound
to check for
acute abdominal injury.
I'm fine.
When did you start
feeling lightheaded?
About an hour ago.
There is significant pressure
in the abdominal contents.
What does that mean?
She has
a retroperitoneal bleed.
We need to get you
into surgery right away.
[♪♪♪♪]
Hi, Mr. Browne.
I'm Dr. Allen.
This is Dr. Park.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
I see where Claire
gets her good looks.
BP looks good.
124 over 83.
Have you had
these symptoms before?
Happens sometimes
when I get migraines.
Migraines come
when I'm stressed.
Don't cry
over spilled milk.
Look, I don't want to take up
too much of your time,
but is it possible we can
go somewhere quiet and talk?
Maybe we could grab
a coffee or dessert.
You know, you used to love
rocky road ice cream.
Is that still
your favorite flavor?
You just had a major
neurological event.
We need to run some CT scans
to identify the cause.
DR. ANDREWS: Found
the bleeder. Clamp.
Need to open up the
retroperitoneal space and pack.
BP's still dropping.
She's not clotting.
She have any history of
hemophilia or bleeding disorder?
No. Push FFP,
TXA and fibrinogen.
Pack more lap pads
and evacuate the hematoma.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(RAPID BEEPING)
ENRIQUE: Pressure's rising.
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
This young lady almost died
from a collision
with an elbow.
There must be something else
going on here.
Find out what it is.
We'll start by scanning
your abdomen.
I'll help you up
on the bed.
MILES: You were right.
(OVER INTERCOM)
It wasn't a migraine.
I have terminal cancer.
[♪♪♪♪]
His oncologist
started him on chemo.
It shrunk the tumor,
but Miles didn't finish it.
The location
of the metastases
still likely leaves it
inoperable.
JORDAN: I don't know.
If we use transcatheter
hepatic artery
chemoembolization,
we might be able to attack
the tumor and spare his liver.
Claire?
What do you think?
It's the patient's
decision.
You should
take it to him.
Let him decide.
(DOOR OPENS)
You have abnormally
large platelets.
It's a rare condition called
Bernard-Soulier syndrome,
which makes it very difficult
for your blood to clot.
It's why you almost bled out
during surgery.
LEO: Is it treatable?
Will she be okay?
There's no cure,
but it is manageable.
Keep an eye out
for pain or bruising
or any other symptoms
that don't go away.
That can be a sign
of a larger problem.
It's just
a pulled muscle.
You don't know that.
My left leg has been
bothering me for a few weeks.
LEO: Months.
I'm not overreacting.
[♪♪♪♪]
We'll need to run CTs
of your hip and femur
to rule out osteoarthritis
or an occult fracture.
[♪♪♪♪]
How does that feel?
Weird.
Oh.
Better?
Sure.
Why do I need this?
Back pain is a common
symptom of pregnancy.
It's preventative.
You should take these twice
a day with food or milk,
preferably food.
I already have
prenatal vitamins.
You have the chewable
gummy kind.
Tablets are better
for the fetus.
Will you please stop
calling it a fetus?
It is a fetus.
It's our baby.
I don't need you
to do any of this, Shaun.
What do you
need me to do?
Just be the dad,
not the doctor.
Do you think
I'm gonna drink this?
What's in it?
Urine? Saliva?
Tropical fish?
Coffee.
Dr. Park, need to talk to you
about our implant patient.
Let's do an additional
split-thickness skin graft.
That's a pretty long and
complicated procedure. - Mm-hmm.
If you're gonna scrub in,
you'll probably
need the caffeine
more than I do.
I hear you've been keeping
some pretty late nights.
Too much caffeine before
surgery leads to unsteady hands.
I can assure you,
I'm well-rested.
I don't need the coffee.
[♪♪♪♪]
Your father
refused surgery.
His slurred speech
was a side effect of chemo.
Treatment
almost took him out.
He doesn't want
to try again.
Thanks for
letting me know.
[♪♪♪♪]
I know a lot of girls
who didn't have their fathers,
but yours did something
theirs didn't.
He came back.
(CHUCKLES) He came back
to absolve himself of guilt.
It's a gift
I'm not giving him.
That's his burden to carry.
Forgiveness isn't for
the one you're forgiving.
It's for you.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(GASPS) It's Miles.
His liver's bleeding.
Go.
[♪♪♪♪]
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
They seem like
a very nice couple.
Very... Connected.
I wish I knew
how to be like that.
They're not a couple.
Leo's gay.
Can gay people really
detect other gay people?
You can if you check out
their Instagram.
Dr. Murphy...
I don't think
she has arthritis,
but I don't know
what this is.
Her disorder caused blood-filled
pseudotumors in her leg.
The blood
ate away her bone.
JORDAN: Your liver
was bleeding
because your tumor
exceeded its blood supply.
It puts you at risk
for serious complications,
even a fatal one.
Please reconsider
the surgery.
I'm not afraid
of dying.
Where's my daughter?
Why isn't she here telling me any of this?
(MONITOR BEEPING)
[♪♪♪♪]
I think it's time
for me to go home.
What about
3-D-printed scaffolding?
We could re-create the shape
of the bone, graft new stem cells,
and allograft onto it
to generate new growth.
Her underlying disorder
would eat away the new bone.
Everything I do upsets Lea
and makes her mad at me.
Oh. That's what I'm
doing here, I'm guessing?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
You're both here because
I have two questions.
When I tell my patient
her femur bone is destroyed,
she is going to ask
if I can save her leg,
and I don't have
an answer to that.
Lea and I are in love.
We're going to have a baby.
We should feel
very happy right now,
but I feel like I'm living
with a stranger
who doesn't want me
to breathe on them.
We could do
an expandable
osseointegrated
limb replacement.
- Too risky.
- Too many surgeries, yeah.
Well, you're gonna
have a kid, Shaun.
You... You can't expect
everything to be the same.
Lea's going through
a whole lot of changes.
You both are.
N-No, I'm the same.
Well, maybe that's
the problem, Shaun.
You're in a relationship
with three people now.
You're gonna have to
make some adjustments.
Both of you.
Okay.
We could use
high-density polyethylene
on the distal femoral segment
to anchor it to the tendons.
I don't like adjusting.
[♪♪♪♪]
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
You wanted to see me?
If we discharge him,
he's going to die.
I don't expect you would feel
anything but contempt for Miles.
He was supposed to take
care of you, and he didn't.
And now I'm asking you to do
for him what he never did for you.
No, he did
take care of me.
He just quit.
He used to pick me up
every day after school.
And then, one day,
he just... stopped showing up.
And for years after,
I would come home,
I'd make sure the curtains
were open, and I'd wait.
If a car slowed down
in front of the house,
I'd imagine it was him coming
to grab me up and rescue me,
and I thought if I wanted
it enough, he'd come back.
So I just... I just had to
want it more, you know?
And finally, I gave up. I
stopped looking out the window.
I grieved and buried my father
a long time ago, and I'm just...
I'm not interested
in getting to know him
just to grieve him
all over again.
But he's still your father,
and you're still you.
Some day you'll hate yourself
if you turn your back on him.
[♪♪♪♪]
We would secure
the titanium prosthetic
to the hip socket and tibia
using cement augmentation
for stability and support.
You would have full
flexibility and range of motion,
and with physical therapy,
you should be able to dance again.
If you survive the surgery.
I could die?
Yes.
There is a 10% to 15%
chance, approximately.
Femur replacement is
a very complicated procedure,
made even riskier by
your underlying condition.
The safest route
is to amputate.
Very little chance of major
complication during surgery,
and there have been great
advancements in prosthetics.
My dance career
would be over.
Most likely, but you would
still have your life.
My life is dance.
I...
Do whatever it takes
to save the leg.
Oh, My.
It's too big a risk.
You know
what this means to me.
Hey.
But if there's a chance
I could die tomorrow,
there's something
I have to do first.
♪♪ Maybe I played
My cards wrong
♪♪ Oh, just a little bit wrong
♪♪ Oh, baby, I-I-I
♪♪ Apologize for it
♪♪ I could fall, or I could fly
♪♪ Here in your aeroplane
♪♪ And I could live
♪♪ I could die hanging
On the words you say
♪♪ And I've been known
To give my all
♪♪ Sitting back
♪♪ Looking at every mess
That I've made
♪♪ So don't call me baby
♪♪ Unless you mean it...
It is very hard to believe
these two are not having sex.
♪♪ If you don't believe it
♪♪ Let me know the truth
♪♪ Before I dive
Right into you
Right into you ♪♪
[♪♪♪♪]
DR. REZNICK: You should
come over tonight.
Unless you need to rest up
for your Franken-penis surgery.
You embarrassed me
in front of a superior.
Did you get fired?
Did you get pulled
off the surgery?
I was just getting you back
for giving me that rancid coffee.
It was coffee.
Plain coffee with one
cream and one sugar,
the exact coffee
I've seen you have
every day
for the last three years.
I was being nice.
Same reason I put an
umbrella over your gigantic head.
I was being
a decent human being.
When did we start
doing that?
How was I supposed to know
you didn't dose my coffee?
Because I'm not an emotionally
stunted person. You are.
Anything that resembles
intimacy freaks you out,
and you start throwing
blows... Low ones.
And if hooking up causes you
to cross boundaries like that,
it's better to go back
to the way things were.
Barely friends, no benefits.
[♪♪♪♪]
(MONITOR BEEPING)
You're in love with him.
Aren't you?
Is that why you're
having the surgery?
You're afraid that if you
lose dance, you lose him?
You are risking your life
to save something that...
Isn't real.
Leo and I
share a life together.
We're partners in every
sense of the word...
Except one.
My best friend growing up
was a girl named Rachel.
She and I lived in
a very religious community,
so it was kind of assumed
we'd get married.
Which was fine with me,
because Rachel was...
Beautiful...
And smart and funny.
And I loved her.
But then I fell in love
with the boy down the street.
He never knew. Nothing
ever happened between us.
But it's like
all of a sudden,
the world...
Lit up.
And I realized
Rachel and I wasn't enough.
I had been lying to myself
and to her.
She deserved to be loved
and wanted in a way that...
Lit up someone's world.
And she spent years
loving someone
who could never
give her that.
You need to tell Leo
how you feel.
[♪♪♪♪]
We share our secrets,
our pain.
He listens to me
when I've had a bad day.
He holds me
when I'm scared.
[♪♪♪♪]
I don't want anything
to change between us.
James arthur's falling
like the stars playing...
♪♪ I swear to God
When I come home
♪♪ I'm gonna hold you so close
♪♪ I swear to God
When I come home
♪♪ I'll never let go...
Would you like me
to spin you?
Okay.
♪♪ Like a river, I flow...
♪♪ To the ocean I know...
Ow.
♪♪ Guiding me home...
Okay, the s-swaying is making
me feel really pukey right now.
Can we maybe try this
at another time?
Ooh.
♪♪ We're fallin' like the stars
♪♪ Falling in love ♪♪
(MUSIC STOPS)
I feel...
Disconnected from you
and the baby, which...
Yes, you are very
connected to already,
but I don't
feel anything.
Because it is
not a baby yet.
It is a fetus, and...
it is making my girlfriend
sick and mad at me.
And I feel very...
Alone.
[♪♪♪♪]
(SIGHS)
You are being so...
Selfish.
I'm growing your baby,
Shaun,
and reading books
and making appointments
and taking vitamins
the size of my face
and working
a full-time job.
And on top of that,
you just dropped on me
that you don't feel
anything for our baby
and expect me to make you
feel love and connected and...
(SIGHS)
Mm. No. You know...
(DOOR SLAMS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Dr. Lim suggested
I come talk to you.
I know you deserve
better than me.
You deserved a father,
and I failed you,
and I can't
make up for that.
Breeze and I were
high school sweethearts.
We thought we were gonna
take over the world together.
We were young
and naive and stupid.
And we got pregnant
before graduation.
I had a scholarship
to Howard,
but it didn't cover
family housing.
So I gave it up, because
I wanted to be there.
And yet, you left the family
you gave it up for.
You should have taken
the scholarship.
We got married,
and we gave it a go for a while.
But I could not handle
Breeze's mental illness.
When we broke up, she
made it hard to see you.
Don't blame her
for what you didn't do.
I am not blaming her.
I was immature.
At least she was there.
At least
she stuck around...
Drunk and sick
and out of her mind.
I... I waited for you, and
I loved you, and you left.
Claire,
I've always loved you.
Nothing
could change that.
I thought about you
every single day.
You know, I don't care.
Thinking about me
wasn't enough.
It didn't do anything
for me at all.
You...
You could have
fought for me.
You could have come back
before now.
I ran away.
I was a coward.
And I stayed away because I
was running from my own guilt.
[♪♪♪♪]
Whether I'm in your life or
not, you should get the surgery.
Because if you don't...
Then you're still
a coward.
[♪♪♪♪]
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
I feel scared, too.
What are you
scared of?
Everything.
And I don't want
to go through this alone.
I don't want
to go through nine months
knowing you
view this baby
as a medical condition
you don't feel anything for.
I'll resent you.
And that scares me
more than anything.
And I want to help you
feel connected.
Oh, no, sorry. We're
not having sex right now.
I realize
that was misleading.
I want you to put your head
on my belly and talk to Berry.
About what?
Anything.
[♪♪♪♪]
Hello...
Berry.
My patient is a 26-year-old
ballroom dancer
with Bernard-Soulier syndrome.
She presented with
a retroperitoneal bleed
but now needs
a total femur replacement.
It is a very risky surgery.
I am your father,
and I am a surgeon.
Did that make you feel
better to talk to him?
No.
A fetus can't hear any
sounds until 18 weeks,
and we don't know
if it's a him yet
because it doesn't have
fully formed genitals.
I will see you at
your appointment later.
I don't think
you should come.
There's a chance it's too
early to hear a heartbeat,
which will make me
feel sad and scared.
And if I can hear it,
I will feel happy.
And either way,
you will
probably feel nothing.
And... that'll make me feel
more alone than I already do,
so... you should just
not come.
Okay.
[♪♪♪♪]
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Isn't it possible Leo loves
Maya as much as she loves him?
Does it matter that he doesn't
want to have sex with her?
Sex isn't just
about sex.
It's about intimacy
and desire
and a deep mutual
physical connection.
And she thinks
she has that.
That's the last
of the proximal femur.
Let's get
the distal end out.
SHAUN: Maybe Maya and Leo have
such a strong relationship
because it's based entirely
on an emotional connection.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
ENRIQUE: She's hypotensive.
SHAUN: There are secretions
around her breathing tube,
and her oxygen levels
are dropping.
She's rejecting
the platelets.
DR. ANDREWS:
Stop the transfusion.
Increase her oxygen
and respiratory support.
Start dopamine
and epinephrine.
(RAPID BEEPING)
BP's 87 over 52.
She's stabilizing.
But without
the transfusions,
her risk of bleeding out
goes way up.
Are we going to move
forward or amputate?
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
Her partner's
her proxy, right?
He's got a decision
to make.
My God.
(SNIFFLES)
She trusted me
to protect her wishes.
And she wants to dance.
Y-You should try
to save her leg.
[♪♪♪♪]
Maya's in love with you.
That's why she's having
the surgery.
She thinks if she loses dance,
your relationship will end.
And only you know
if she's right.
If she is...
If losing her leg means losing
the two things she loves most,
then maybe you should
honor her wishes.
But if she's wrong...
If you do love her and will
stay with her no matter what,
then you should do whatever
it takes to save her life.
Of course I love her.
There's no question
that I love her.
(SIGHS) So,
the only question is...
How much?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Miles is stable.
But we found significant polyp
burden not detected on his CT,
and we sent to biopsies.
His cancer was caused by
familial adenomatous polyposis.
That's genetic.
50% chance
of carrying the gene
if you have
an affected parent.
You need to get
a genetic test.
Even if you have the gene,
with regular colonoscopies,
we'll be able to catch it...
Thank you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
What's this?
Male, late 20s.
Needs bilateral carpal
tunnel release surgery
that he got playing in the
United States Chess Federation.
You like to play chess
with Kellan.
Your game sucks. Figured
you might learn something.
[♪♪♪♪]
This is you
being a decent human.
Maybe sometimes
it's not terrible.
This is delightful.
I can give it
to someone else.
Thanks.
[♪♪♪♪]
Are you glad you went to see
your father before he died?
No.
My father hurt me.
He was a bad man
who did bad things.
I already knew that.
My father hurt me, too...
By leaving me.
(SIGHS)
He didn't even try
to be a good dad.
How can you be sure
he didn't?
Maybe he did try
and he couldn't.
(SCOFFS)
Well, if something is important
to you, you make it happen.
But what if you can't?
What if you're trying
to connect with your child
and it just doesn't work?
It is difficult
to feel something
for someone
you don't know yet.
Do you want to know what kind
of man your father is?
[♪♪♪♪]
Why... Why would you
do this to me?
(VOICE BREAKING) I told
you I was willing to take the risk.
I wasn't.
I love you.
I couldn't risk your life.
I'm so sorry.
But I'm here.
(SNIFFLES)
I'm not going anywhere.
You're not
gonna lose me.
We're gonna
get through this, My.
We'll be okay.
(SOBS)
I sleep all the time
and I'm still tired.
When was your last
bowel movement?
I don't know.
A couple days.
Shaun, what are you
doing here?
SHAUN: Smile.
Uh, what?
There is something
in your teeth.
Shaun.
Do you eat a lot
of black licorice?
Uh, yes.
You should stop.
Eating too much black licorice
can lower potassium,
which causes fatigue
and constipation.
Stop eating it.
That's it?
Yes.
[♪♪♪♪]
Lea doesn't want me
at her OB-GYN appointment.
There's a woman
in the waiting room
with a very
interesting mole.
The year Maddie was born,
I took on
twice as many surgeries.
I... (LAUGHS)
I hid at the hospital.
I was afraid that I was
gonna piss off my wife.
Sound familiar?
Upset my daughter.
I thought you liked
being a dad.
I did. I...
I just didn't think
I was very good at it. I...
It didn't come naturally
to me. Not like...
Not like brain surgery.
I missed a lot.
Sometimes I think if I had
been there for the swaddling
and for the changing
of the diapers and...
See her first steps,
you know?
(SIGHS)
Shaun,
do yourself a favor
and be there for as many
moments as you can.
[♪♪♪♪]
(RAIN FALLING)
DR. PARK:
Taking the scenic route?
Car needs brakes
and Uber's taking forever.
Chess guy's super cool.
He's gonna teach me Petrov's
Defense while he heals.
I didn't mean to take things
so far in front of Andrews.
I guess I had
a tiny overreaction.
It's okay for us to be nice
to each other... Sometimes.
Headed home?
I wouldn't mind some
company, if you're up for it.
See?
Nice is good.
Sometimes.
I'll see you
at your place.
[♪♪♪♪]
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Where's Leo?
I don't know.
I asked him if this
could be enough.
If I could be...
He loves me.
I knew that.
But not enough.
I suppose
I knew that too.
(SNIFFLES)
As long as he was here,
I would never make room
for anyone else.
So I asked him to go.
[♪♪♪♪]
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sure there are a ton
of great guys
who'd want to be
with a one-legged,
unemployed former dancer
with chronic nosebleeds.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SNIFFLES)
[♪♪♪♪]
I've been mad at you
for so long.
I...
That I couldn't feel
any other emotion.
Just anger.
Angry at you.
Angry at myself
for secretly wishing
you would turn up on
my doorstep my entire life.
(SIGHS) I thought
I'd outgrown it.
But when you went
into surgery today...
I didn't feel anger.
I felt...
Fear.
[♪♪♪♪]
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SPEAKS HOARSELY,
INDISTINCTLY)
Get some rest.
When you feel better, you...
You can take me
for rocky road.
Esse ainda é meu
favorito. (Risos)
[♪♪♪♪]
Eu amo Você.
Você está pronto?
Mm-hmm.
Você veio.
Olá.
Sou o Dr. Shaun Murphy.
Eu sou o pai.
Prazer em conhecê-lo, pai.
Acabamos de começar.
Onde você
estudou medicina? - Shaun.
O diploma dela
não está na parede.
Eu gostaria de saber.
Apenas seja o pai.
Sente-se, fique quieto,
não faça nada.
(BATIMENTO CARDIACO)
É esse o...
OBGYN: Esse é o batimento cardíaco.
Ali.
Estamos tendo um bebê.
[♪♪♪♪]
(Risos)
Correções de sincronização por srjanapala
Fechando a reprodução da música do tema ...