[Fly buzzes]
[Chains clinking]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Gunshot]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
Shit.
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
Aah! Aah!
♪♪
Oh, no, no, no, no!
[Screaming]
♪♪
You couldn't have done that
five hours ago?
Why would I do that?
[Grunting]
Come on.
Family's inland.
And the munitions?
Everything's inland.
♪♪
I need
to get back.
We headed in?
Well, I can't show up
empty-handed.
Wife wouldn't like that.
Oh, my God.
This garden's her baby.
Got herbs and teas
for everything --
pain, nerves, sleep.
How 'bout focus
and speed?
Well, those Whisper folkreally got you percolatin', huh?
There's a lot of lives
at stake.
Where are these munition depots
you spoke of?
Is this one of them?
Nah, that's just
an old lab --
some structural damage.
Wild animals
get in there sometimes.
Best to stay away.
[Grunts]
♪♪
My kidswould run riot in here.
My boy
seems to think
maybe the sailors
must've left
a buried treasure
in the grain silos.
I can barely get himnot to claw his way up the thing
and jump inside.
♪♪
Kid's 5.
[Chuckles]
He's just like
his mom.
♪♪
Once they decide
to do somethin',
ain't a damn thing you can do
to stop 'em.
I remember one time I --
Stop the bullshit.
Now, where the hell
is your family?
♪♪
When I said I had to
come home to my family,
I meant it.
I promised her
when we got married.
Flowers every day.
How are you gonna wait till nowto tell me this?
[Scoffs]
Those words
don't come easy.
I don't like
to bring people here.
Don't trust 'em.
I was scared.
Are there any weapons hereat all?
I promised
I would help you check,
and I will,
but --
Ugh, I'm gonna
find 'em myself.The island's not clear.
No shit
it's not clear!
It was
until the others came.
They brought violence.
The sickness
came with it.
Killed my family.
We never had
a lotta Rippers.
So I never really
got good at...
doing [Sighs]
what it is you do.
You're good
with a sword.
What are you askin' me?
My family's
still in there.
My wife.
My babies.
That's why
I asked you to come.
Needed you to come.
♪♪
[Growling]
[Metal clinks]
♪♪
[Banging on door]
[Flesh tears, growling stops]
[Thud]
[Growling in distance]
♪♪
[Growling stops]
[Growling in distance]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Metal clanging]
Shit. Sorry.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Exhales sharply]
What do we do?
♪♪
Follow me.
Stay close.
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Get behind that --
now.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Growling stops]
Thank you.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
Virgil: I wanted to give them
somethin' they loved
to take with 'em.
And Jasmine
loved that book.
Look, I know that this is hard,and I am sorry,
but I have got
to get back.
My wife,
whenever I had a hard time,
she'd talk me
through it.
Without her,
I don't know who I am.
It's not too lateto find out. Look --
I wanted
to ask you...
It's been
a long time
since I had a reason
to say thank you to someone.
Don't thank me.
Just show mewhat I came here for,
and I'll go.
No,
it's gettin' late.
Tide's low.
Oh, God.
I'm not sure the boat'll make itthrough the channel.
Might wanna stay here tonight
and not risk it.
Virgil, I need you to hold upyour end of the bargain.
Yeah. But...
[Grunts]
It's gettin' dark,
and some of the buildings
aren't safe.
Could we do this
in the morning?
We can do it
first thing.
[Walkie-talkie clicks, static]
[Walkie-talkie turns off, thuds]
[Owl hooting, crickets chirping]
[Door clanks, creaks]
[Door creaks, closes]
[Door clanks]
[Sighs]
Man: [Whispering]
Stay still. Everyone quiet.
Is it him?
Woman:
I don't know.
[Indistinct whispering]
What is that?
I don't know.
Quiet. Stop moving.
It might not be him.
Shh.
No,
I don't know.
Be calm.
Stop moving.
[Sighs]
♪♪
Virgil!
Virgil: Why couldn't you
just wait until morning?
I told you
it wasn't safe.
Virgil,
open the damn door.
I trusted you,
and you ruined it.
Open the damn door,
Virgil!
[Banging on door]
[Grunting]
[Panting]
[Water dripping]
[Gasps]
[Breathing heavily]
Oh, shit!
[Panting]
[Grunting]
[Banging on door]
Damn it.
Man:
Calm down.
Hello?
Woman: We've been tryingto talk to you.
How long
have I been in here?
A day maybe?
[Sighs] A day?
Why didn't you answer me
when I called out to you
the first time?
He blows up
at us sometimes.
Gets in
one of his moods.
When he's angry
like that,
it's best
to be quiet.
You guys know this building,
right?
What's the layout?
Don't bother
trying to escape.
Whole place
is booby-trapped.
What's his routine?
How often does he come around?
As little as possible.
He doesn't like
to see us.
[Sighs]
Celeste and I were researchers
with Virgil.
We wrote the papers.
Yeah,
and I swept the floors.She assisted us.
So you had a life here.
You knew each other.
Yeah,
we were friends with Virgil.
Tell me
what went wrong.
Stragglers used to comeby boat,
stumble on us,
and we took 'em in.
We took 'em all in.
One night,
it got really bad.
Food supplies
were gettin' low,
and a fight broke out
over the rations and --
And somebody pulled a knife,and this newbie died.
Virgil was late
gettin' there,
panicked.
Said we need
to lock all the doors.
He didn't know.
Virgil didn't know.
Know what?
His wife and kids
were inside.
[Sighs]
He snapped.
He was never
the same.
We've been in here
ever since.
You okay?
I will be.
I'm not
stayin' here long.
You need some rest.
Eat something.
The food
should be okay.
Save your strength.
You can't kill him if
you don't have your strength.
Celeste: You haven'ttold us your name.
It's Michonne.
[Clank]
[Panting]
I'm glad you ate.
Open the damn door!
I can't do that.
Why the hell not?!
Because you'll kill me.
I know you will.
Well, we reap what we sow,asshole.
[Echoing]
I don't wanna fight.
I want you
to understand.
♪♪
[Grunting, whimpering]
The island has a gift.
It can help you
the way it helped me.
♪♪
[Echoing] Aah!
[Breathing heavily]
[Grunts]
♪♪
What the hell
did you do?
[Water dripping echoes]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
What did you --
what did you...
[Echoing]
Jimsonweed.
Makes a nice tea.
Calming.
I want you to see.
You don't think I see it,
but I do.
You're in pain,
like me.
You need peace,
Like you? No.
I don't drug peopleand toss them in cells.
"Toss them in cells"?
Yes, you've said.
We've had that conversation
three times.
I need you
to hear me.
I need you to think aboutmy daughter and my son.
"Think you about
my daughter and my son."
Yes,
I said those words, too,
but no one listened.
♪♪
Everything I did
was to protect my family.
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho, I'm surethey're realproud of you now.
Siddiq: [Echoing]
What about mychild?
My family?
♪♪
You're no angel.
[Walker growls]
[Breathing heavily]
I'm so cold.
It's cold.
So picture the sun.
[Breathing heavily]
Let the medicine
do its work.
♪♪
Siddiq.
You were supposed to
protect us.
I did my best.
You let me die.
No!
And Rick and Carl.
What happens to Coco?
What happens
to my family?
[Crying]
You are my family.
Well, this is how it feels
to be your family!
♪♪
[Growls]
Stop! Stop it! Stop!
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
Siddiq?
[Chains clinking]
♪♪
Virgil's Voice:
Stop fighting it.
♪♪
[Echoing]
She's waiting.
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
Oh, no, no, no, no!
[Screaming]
♪♪
[Shouts indistinctly]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
Michonne:
[Echoing] Hey!
♪♪
Help!
Help! Please!
Help me! Please!Come on. Let's go!
[Shouts indistinctly]
Please!
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Growling stops][Grunting]
♪♪
Well,
looky what we have here.
♪♪
[Grunting]
Goddamn.
This chick
has some cojones.
[Normal voice]I don't want any trouble.
Well, then,
you probably shouldn't have
taken a swing
at me.
Or I probablyshouldn't have missed.
[Chuckles]
[Groans]
[Sighs]
You know, I'm not much on
savin' people on the road,
especially those
that try to take my head off,
but I gotta say,
I like you
and your big,
ol' massive lady nuts.
Besides,
be a waste
to have such a nice sword
and no strength to use it.
♪♪
[Echoing]
Name's Negan.
♪♪
[Flesh tears]
[Grunting]
[Gunshots]
♪♪
[Alarm blaring]
[Breathing shakily]
[Negan whistling]
♪♪
Negan: Eenie...
meenie...
miney...
Nah.
Just kiddin', assholes.
See, I was gonna do
this next part myself,
but, see, my right-hand gal,
[Echoing] Michonne,
is on a wicked-ass tear
these days,
and who the hell am I
to stand in her way?
♪♪
[Normal voice] Mm.
You wish 'em a happy new yearfrom us, will ya?
♪♪
[Scoffs]
You didn't know
who they were...
[Breathing shakily]
...or where
they were from.
♪♪
[Echoing] You didn't know shit
about them.
But you came
in the dead of night
and slaughtered them anyway
in their sleep.
♪♪
Like cowards.
Ah.
♪♪
And you remember...
you did this.
What happens next...
it's your fault.
♪♪
Welcome to the new world.
Ha!
♪♪
[Gunfire]
[Grunting]
♪♪
[Breathing shakily]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Gun cocks]
[Gunshot]
[Retching, coughing]
[Breathing heavily]
[Keys jingle]
You feel better?
[Breathing heavily]
You will.
Aah!
[Both grunting]
♪♪
[Blade clangs]
Lucy: Michonne.Jeremiah:
Don't leave us.
Celeste:
Let us out. Please.
Michonne.
♪♪
[Fire crackling]
Oh, shit.
[Panting]
[Grunting]
♪♪
I was gonna ask you
to help me.
I wanted
to let them go.
I wanted you to be there
so they wouldn't kill me.
Then you
found 'em first,
and I knew
you were gonna kill me, too.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?"Sorry" doesn't cut it.
[Screams]
She always told me
the right thing to do,
and then she was gone
and I didn't know
what to do.
And I couldn't
let you leave,
and I didn't
wanna kill you.
Move, Michonne.
You have as much reason
to kill this asshole as we do.
I do.
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Sighs]
Celeste:
Do it or move.
♪♪
Look at him.
He owes you more
than he can ever make right.
Taking his life...
you'll lose
more of yourself.
It doesn't settle it.
But your mercy
gives you something.
You get something.
What?
Peace.
♪♪
[Lucy and Virgil grunt]
[Sighs]
Michonne:There's nothing here.
I checked
every building,
even the ones you saidhad structural damage.
Not a Goddamn thing
anywhere.
I know you don't have
any reason to believe me,
but I never lied to you
about the weapons.
You said
you'd seen them.
I told you
I could show you the spots.
I got no reason
to go in them.
You have gotto do better than that.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Sometimes we find
a stray shell,
but never
any more than --
I --
I find a stray shell.
[Chuckles]
I'm notgoing back empty-handed.
Take whatever you want.
Clear my debt
with Oceanside.
[Keys jingle][Sighs]
You took the risk.
Didn't have a choice.
I had to find out.
And there's no tea,
so don't even ask.
What do you see whenyou're trippin', anyway?
Lisa with that damn camera
pointed at everyone.
My babies.
[Chuckles]
Jasmine sittin' by the fire
with that book,
askin' a million questions
about a world
she'll never know.
♪♪
Bobby and me lyin'
on the roof of that Annex,
lookin' up
at the stars.
Heaven.
♪♪
I wanted --
hoped that
you would see that, too.
♪♪
It took my family
from me.
I saw hell.
I'm sorry.
Only world I ever wanted
was one they were in.
I don't know how to do this
without them.
You try,like the rest of us.
Now, how 'boutyou try to find my stuff?
♪♪
[Door creaks]
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
[Grunts]
Where the hell
did you get these?
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
Virgil:
It washed up. [Grunts]
It washed up
during the big storm.
I don't know
where the hell it came from.
[Grunting] Wait.
♪♪
No!
Michonne.
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Breathing shakily]
Holy shit.
That's you.
And the kid?
♪♪
You knew.
You came to find us
at Oceanside.
No. [Scoffs]
What?
Uh, uh,
why would I do that?
Because of this.
I have never seen that before
in my life. I swear.
But why are his things here?What was he doing here?
How the hell
would I know?
You knew that this boat was herethis whole time.
Virgil:
The world ended.
Boats wash up.What do you want me to say?
[Grunts]
You knew
that there were no munitions.
Were you setting up a trap
for us?
Did you lay a trap
for him?
What did you do?
What did you do to him?
[Breathing rapidly]
Who are you
talking about?
♪♪
[Sniffles]
Virgil: I don't know what it is
you think I have
or who
you're looking for, but...
maybe it wasn't an accident
that we met.
If the others
will help me,
I think
we can mod the engine
and get it
workin' again.
♪♪
If this person
was on this boat,
then maybe you can
find them again.
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
Gonna take some time.
We're out of time.
They're willing
to let you come.
They say that?
There's only
one boat left.
You leave now
or you don't leave.
After everything,
I can't believe
they would do that.
Sometimes the most injuredare the most forgiving.
They're good people, Virgil,and they're trying,
giving you a chance,a way off of this island.
I promised her flowers
every day.
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Michonne crying]
[Sniffles]
Shoto.
Shoto, are you there?
It's Daito.
Shoto?
Are you out there?
Anyone?
Judith:
I'm here, Daito.
I've been trying you.
[Inhales sharply]
I'm sorry.
I'm here now.
Are you still
with Virgil?
No, but I found three peopleon the island,
and I'm helping themget back home.
I've missed you
and your brother so much.
Mama.
Judith:
No, no.
Call signs for safety.
Daito.
You're Daito.
Hey, baby.
And who are you?
I'm Little Brave Man.
Oh.
I love
"Little Brave Man."
He picked it
all by himself.
How long have you been with
your sister, Little Brave Man?
Tia Rosita brought me.
Judith...
how are Tia Rosita
and Coco doing?
Okay, I guess.
Better.
How's home?
Anything with
the Whisperers?
We got 'em, Mom.
We got
most of the horde.
[Exhales sharply]
Alpha can't
hurt us anymore.
[Exhales sharply]
You're doing it again.
You always make that sound
when you're worried.
Do not.
Do, too.
[Sniffles]
Um...
I found something.
Not what I was looking foron the island,
but something else,
something that...
could be really importantto all of us.
What do you mean?
I found somethingthat belonged to the Brave Man
in a placethat he might've been recently.
I don't knowwhat any of it means yet
or -- or if it means
anything at all.
Mom...
is he alive?
I-I don't know,
[Sniffles] baby.
That's what I'm saying.
I-I-I don't know.
But if you think
he's alive,
then you have to
go find him.
No. No. Not now.
You and your brotherneed me,
and everything going onin Alexandria --
Mom,
you have to go.
You have to.
♪♪
We're okay.
What if
he needs you more?
♪♪
What if he's trying
to come home, too,
but no one will help?
Ah, God.
♪♪
[Sniffles]
If I go...
♪♪
Whenyou go
and when you find him.
Okay, okay.
When I go...
and find
the Brave Man...
[Pounding]
Jeremiah:
We're at the coast.I have to go.
Listen to Uncle Daryl.
I know.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
Okay, baby girl,
I'm gonna try.
♪♪
I'm gonna head north.
And I'll try youevery morning on this walkie
for as long as I can.
I'll take it everywhere.
[Sniffles]
I love you and your brotherso much.
Love you, too, Mom.
Go get him.
Shoto, out.
♪♪
[Sighs]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Wait, wait, wait.
♪♪
Wait.
Can you help us?
They'll leave
without us.
Who?
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
Please.
♪♪
They won't wait for us.
Carl:
Should we help her?
♪♪
Rick: You wanna
tell us your name?
Who are you?
♪♪
[Walkers growl]
Come on.
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Horses neighing]
♪♪