Princess: Yo!
'Sup?!
Yumiko: Who are you?
What do you want?Excuse me?
You guys were the onescalling out and making a racket.
I thought you needed help,
but now you're acting
like I'm the one
causing a problem here?
Damn. I haven't seen anyone
in over a year,
and the first ones I find
seem like a bunch of meanies.
You just caught us
off guard.
We didn't know
if you were attacking --Seriously?
If I wanted to attack,
I'd hold the gun like this --
with the dangerous part
pointed at you, see?
That's for attacking.
The other way,
that's for hello.
So, as we can all agree,
I wasn't attacking.
But now...
Now I'm not so sure.
Maybe that's up to you.
Are you gonna hurt me?
Keep pointing the damn gunat us, and you'll find out.
No one has any intention
of hurting you.
We were just admiring
your displays.
Are they yours?
Crap. Sorry.
Do you like 'em?
Yeah, not many rotters
left in the city,
so I put these up
as my decorations.
Pain in the ass
to put together,
but they make the place
feel more alive.
Although now that I've met
actual live people again --
Hold on.
You guys are real,
right?
Is that supposedto be a joke?I dunno.
I mean,
I never hallucinated before,
but there's a first time
for everything.
Uh, say something
I wouldn't know.
Like, uh...
what's the capital
of Pennsylvania?
Harrisburg.
Did I know that?
I think I knew that.
Ha!
Maybe I am hallucinating.
This is --
This is wild.Hey.
You certain
it's just you out here?
Didn't I already
tell you that?
I've been on my own
for over a year,
and it totally sucks.
Da-- Damn.
I should be nicer.
Talking to
possibly real people again
is making me freak out.
You -- I'm just --
I'm just gonna shut up.
I'm Juanita Sanchez.
But I never liked
the name Juanita.
You can call me Princess.
Why "Princess"?
Because "Queen"
makes me sound old.
And pretentious.
Ezekiel: It's a pleasureto meet you, Princess.
I am...Ezekiel.
And these are my friends,Eugene and Yumiko.
Wow!
Let me show
you guys around.
We got plenty of space
for you to chill out,
put your feet up.
Y'all need supplies?
You need food?
Hair dye?
I've got a neat place
for us to swim
a couple blocks away.
We appreciate the hospitality,but we can't stay.
Oh. O-Okay.
We're ona very important mission.
Ohhh?!
What sorta mission?
Uh,
that's our business.
Well, let me least show you
the best way through the city.
No, thank you.Oh, come on.
Why not?
[Scoffs]Because we don't know you.
[Laughs]
Of course you do.
Princess?
I'm great.
You'll see.
[Walkers growling]
Watch how helpful I can be.
No, wait. Please!
Don't --
[Machine gun fire]
♪♪
[Horses whinny]
Eugene: No! No!
♪♪
Damn.
Uh...
Sorry about that.
♪♪
Ezekiel: At least
it's not a total loss.
And we can still find
the horses tomorrow.
Not to be a naysayer,
but our rendezvous windowis tighter than a tourniquet.
I have doubtsthat it'll be possible
to make the journey
by foot.
Any additional dayspent on an empty search
would place us onthe failure side of that window.
So, if it's possible to walk,
we start now.
Missing this meeting
isn't an option.
We've got way too many people
counting on us back home.
What about Princess?
She offered to help.
Why don't
we take her up on it?
Absolutely not.
What could it hurt?Plenty.
Anyone alone for this long
ends up selfish, crazy --
in her case, definitely both.
We can't trust her.
I'm not suggesting
that we follow her blindly.
But if she knows how to find
transportation --
Then she wouldn't
still be here, alone.
Look, if she had a ride,
why hasn't she left?
It's a trap.
Is Princess a few bananas
short of a bunch?
Possibly.
Does she have access
to automobiles and working fuel?
Unlikely.
But at present,we possess limited options,
so even a slim possibilityis worth investigating.
Apologies, Yumiko.
My vote's with the king.
[Clears throat]
Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
I feel really bad about
what happened.
Let me make it up
to you guys.
You mentioned you had accessto some transportation?
A whole garage full.
Tons of choices.
I'll take you there.
You want us to follow you,
you hand over your gun.
[Exhales sharply]
Really wanna spend time
with living people again,
but I'm not sure
I trust you, either.
I mean, I'm outnumbered.
I could probably take out
one of you,
two if I'm lucky.
But then he'd still be left
to kill me anyways.
So why even try?
Unless I have a death wish,
which, clearly, I don't
because I have been living herealone for so long.
See?
Fine. You can have it.
I know where to find
more guns, anyway.
So, then -- the garage?
Right. Yeah. Of course.
All those in the marketfor a new set of wheels,
follow me!
♪♪
Selfish.
And crazy.
♪♪
[Growling]
Whispering Voice:
Wherrrre aaaaarrre theyyy...
♪♪
[Sighs]
He's keeping
the cats away.
Mostly.
Your turn to watch.
Jules: How are you?
Everybody's counting on me.
You'll come through.
You think so?
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
Uh, I need somebodyto run an errand for me.
♪♪
I'll go.
Daryl: Don't go home.
They'll only find us
if you answer me.
We got a plan to end this.
One I think you'd like.
Man, being on the run
like this,
barely scraping by...
reminds me
of the old gang.
Seems like ages now.
♪♪
Michonne?
Can you hear me?
♪♪
[Growling]
No sign of them.
They left quickly.
Couldn't have gone far.
Do we search elsewhere?
Where...
Whispering Voice:
They have nothinggggg...
Theyyyy fleeee...
theyyyy hiiiiide...
Ocean.
♪♪
Beta:
Prepare the guardians.
We walk.
♪♪
I thought
all the cats left.
Not this one.
I'm sorry about your mom.
You don't have to be.
You miss her?
No.
♪♪
Not everyone gets to havea mom like yours.
Hi.
Everything okay?
Yeah, running
to the road for Luke.
And give them
some exercise.
[Growling]
♪♪
Judith.
What're you doing?I'm fine.
Who you with?
No one.
Come on. We're going back.Let's go.
Please, I wanna stay.No.
I left Father Gabriel
a note.
I swear, it's fine.
No, that wasn't a question.Let's go.
No.
I hate it up there.
Smells like cat pee.
I wanna learn what you do,
how to keep us safe.
In case something happens.
I walk the perimeter.
I look for anything
that looks wrong.
If I find something,I go somewhere safe,
and I radio it in.
There's no room for mistakes,not right now.
I know.
All right.
If you do this with me,
you're gonna do
everything I say,
you're gonna stay
right next to me.
All right?
Promise.
All right. Come on.
♪♪
[Growling]
This is wrong.
They are not fools.
[Sighs] They expect us.
The path is not clear.
The pack believes
in your wisdom.
They follow the Alpha.
Beta, I mean.
Apologies.
We see her within you.
[Breathing shallowly]
Waaaaaaait.
♪♪
Show me.
Show me the path.
♪♪
Patience...
Haaaave faith
in your strennnngth...
Watch...
Learnnnn...
We walk.
We wait.
♪♪
[Radio static]
Tower, do you copy?
Gabriel: Yes, we copy.
They're heading towardOceanside...as expected.
Any sign of slowing?Not yet.
We'll stay on them.
If anything changes,we'll send word.
Copy that.
Be safe.
Same. Over.
♪♪
How much longer
do you reckon?
Almost there.
If this is a waste
of our time...
It'll be worth it.
Don't worry!
Make sure you guys
stay close to me,
and please watch your step.
Tres...
Cuatro...
Cinco...
Starting to wonder
if you were right about her.
Oh, I am.
But let's figure outwhat she's up to first.
Cincuenta y cuatro...
Cincuenta y cinco...
Is there
a particular method
behind this
navigational technique,
or are you just
meandering about?
Holy crap.
I think I just
found your horse.
Did walkers eat it?
No, it probably just
stepped on one of the mines.
♪♪
What do you particularly mean
by the term "mines"?
You know,
those things you step on
and then they go boom.
Are you saying you brought us
into a minefield?
Well, yeah.
But it -- it's a small one.
What's wrong with you?
Why would you keep thatfrom us?
I just didn't
want you to worry.
I told youwe couldn't trust her.
I walk this all the time!
It's no big deal.
I got the route right up here.
So you can get us out?Of course.
As soon as I figure out
where we left off.
Excuse me?
Well, I don't normally stop
in the middle,
so I kinda lost count.
I Just need a minute
to think.
Either you get us
out of here safely,
or I'll kill you
myself.
That's fair.
♪♪
[Explosion]
Ah. Guess not.
Anyone have
an extra canteen?
Carol: Damn it.
Almost have it.
[Clanks]
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Thanks for coming.
You don't have to do that.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
If I could go back...
I'm so sorry, Kelly,
for everything.
She's not dead.
She's not.
Maybe it's because
she's so...tough
to survive anything.
Maybe there's justthis part of me that...
won't accept
that she's gone.
[Inhales sharply]
And, uh, so...
I understand you.
Why you did...all of it.
It doesn't mean
I should have.
♪♪
When I startedlosing my hearing...
my sister told methat it wasn't my weakness.
It was my...
superpower.
♪♪
And now look.
Everyone's learning signbecause of me.
You think that the way you areis -- is a weakness?
[Scoffs]
I heard the stories about you,in the old days.
We all have.
[Chuckles]
That you --
you'd just go off.
And do the thingthat only you can do.
♪♪
Lone wolf.
That's your superpower.
You can't give up everythingabout yourself because...
[Sighs]
...bad things happen.
♪♪
I gotta believe that.
Hey.
I, um...
I don't think you've eaten
anything today.
I'm good.
You know, I can't tellif it's just one of those things
or the craziness of us allmoving to an abandoned tower...
or if you're just
avoiding me.
I'm avoiding you.
Well, shit, that --
that's honest.
You want me to lie?
Make you feel better?
No, I don't.
Okay. Well, you can givesomeone else the rat stew.
It's not rat.
It's possum.
I mean, yeah, basically
a big rat, but I, um...
I just wanted to say...
that I liked her.
Your mom, I mean,
she did some horrible shit
that there's no excusing
any of it, but...
I liked --
I liked a lot of things
about her.
And I wish to God I didn't
have to do what I did.
But if there's something
that you wanna say to me,
then you should say it.
Most of us wish
you'd died, too.
We never should
have followed her.
This is exactly
the kind of thing
I was afraid
would happen.
I have been afraid
of many things.
But this one's new.
Just as an FYI,
we're running out of time
on multiple fronts.
[Walker growling]
Fence instability
being the most pressing.
But I'm also concerned
with improper mine placement,
which could lead
to a cascade.
Yumiko:
What's a cascade?
Chain reaction.
You don't want to be
stuck in the middle
when more of these puppies
start popping off.
Maybe there's something
I can do.
I'm kinda blowing this,huh?
It's not ideal.[Sighs]
But leading us to safety
could go a long way.
Of course.
I just wanna say
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry, y'know?
[Exhales sharply]
Eeeny, meeny...
What is she doing now?
...please no mine-ys...
Moe.
[Inhales deeply]
Whew!
I'm still here.
Cool.
We should be good
from here, guys.
A hunter moves,
everything else
moves around it.
Try to spot things
that don't belong,
things that just don't
feel right.
Now take a look.
Tell me what you see.
Living or dead?
Walker.
They could be
roundin' more up.
Stay behind me.
♪♪
[Growling]
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
[Grunting continues]
Daryl: Come on.
♪♪
Hey! You put our livesin danger back there.
For what?
I didn't.
Let's all just take a --No, no, no, no, no.
Our friends, our families,are depending on us.
She may not have anyoneleft to care about,
but we sure as hell do.
I'm sorry.
Fleetwood Drive.
Ezekiel: What?
We passed Fleetwood Driveearlier.
Uh, must've been
a different Fleetwood.
We've got like five of them
all over the city --
streets, avenues, roads --
it's super confusing.
No, it was most certainlyFleetwood Drive.
I remember seeing the signand saying to myself,
"Granddaddy used to drivea Fleetwood."
Yumiko: You've led us
around all day
when we could've
walked straight here?
Is that true?
Um...
Yumiko --Yumiko: You better tell us
what you're up to,
and maybe
I'll leave you here alive.
Okay, okay, okay.
I might've maybe sort of
missed the turn
onto Fleetwood earlier
but only because I was
having too much fun!
And then I figured,
we could take the scenic route
instead of turning around
and keep the fun going!
Into a minefield.Which looks bad --
I know.
But I'd been through it
like a billion times before,
and I never thought
it was gonna to be a problem
until it was.
All I wanted
was to show you the garage,
and then you'd be like,
"Princess, you're amazing!
We want to stay
and be friends!"
But, no...
I screwed it up.
I see that now.
Yeah.
Shit.
♪♪
When I was first here,
by myself,
I figured somebody else
would show up eventually.
Odds are, right?
And then days
turned into months.
And it was so empty.
But then I realized,
this isn't that different
from how I felt
before all this.
[Chuckles]
This one time,
someone told me,
"You're hard to love."
So maybe it's me.
Maybe I deserve this.
And all day,
I kept hearing that little voicein my head --
"It's me."
And I know I should've...
turned around,
or told you guys the truth,
but I didn't want that voice
to be right.
So...
I am sorry.
♪♪
I have an all-too-familiarsense of how you feel.
I've made poor decisions.
Lied to folks.
The inevitable alternativemeant being left alone.
No one wants that.
Yeah.
Just to clarify --
you do have accessto those wheels, correct?
♪♪
[Breathing shallowly]
Throw it over there.
Now.
[Breathing shallowly]
I will if you pull this
outta me.
I can't die like this.
It ain't natural.
You drop the knife,I'll think about it.
[Breathing shallowly]
Where're your people?
A few miles east.
Headed to the ocean.
Are they with the horde?
You a scout?
I was...
going off on my own.
Why?
I had no choice.
I love those people,
but he's...
I couldn't stay there.
He's what?
Lost it.
After what you did
to her.
Will you take this out?
Does he know where we are?
I don't know.
But he's gonna keep
coming for you.
[Breathing shallowly]
You took too much.
No, please.
Please.
I want to walk...after.
Does he know
where we are?
I don't know.
I mean it.
[Breathing shallowly]
[Breathing stops]
You didn't have to do that.
She didn't have any informationfor us, anyway.
She was gonna die.
Better to be quick.
We're gonna leave her?
Come on.
Maybe she has a family.
Look, if they're only
a few miles away,
maybe we can spot something
from the top of the tower.
♪♪
[Growling]
Faith. Faith.
Faith. Watch.
Learn.
Whispering Voice: Theyyy fleeee
beforrre youuuu...
Strength...
♪♪
Waaaaatch...
Faaaaith.
Yesssssss...
Faaaaaaith...
will beeeee rewarrrrrded...
♪♪
[Laughs]
Still no sign of slowing?
You think this can work?
This plan?
Has to, doesn't it?
I guess so.
♪♪
Always thought,
once Alpha was dead...
it'd be easier
to see light.
Past what we lost,
y'know?
I don't know about
seeing past.
But I can fight here,
try to make surewe don't lose again.
For Gracie, Adam.
Whatever it takes.
♪♪
Then, all this loss will maybe
add up to something --
Hold on.Are they slowing down?
No.
They're changing direction.Toward the tower.
Call it in.
Yeah.
[Radio static]
It's no good.
We got to leave -- now.
♪♪
[Gun cocks]
You don't get to tell me
what to do.
You're right. I can't.
Hey.
I thinkthat you should hit me.
And it will make you
feel better.
I feel fine.
You have to mourn her.
You know,you need to say goodbye.
Otherwise, it's gonnaeat you up from the insides.
Just --Just trust me on this.
Look,she was still your mom.
You know?And we only get the one.
So you --you should hit me...
and just try
to let it out.
Otherwise, you are gonna driftfurther from these people,
and I knowyou don't want that.
The hell do you know
what I want, huh?
Tell me.
You're a selfish asshole.
You only killed her
so they'd think
that you're a hero.
But nothing you do will ever
make you that here!
Because you only care
about yourself.
Even now,
trying to get me to do this?
You liked her?
How the hell can you tell me
you liked her, huh?!
I hated her!
I want to hate her,
so screw you for telling me
I can't even do that!
It's okay, Lydia.
[Crying] No!
It's not okay!
It's not -- not --
[Sobbing]
It's okay.
♪♪
[Garage door opens]
Wheels.
Yeah.
Not exactly the kind of ride
I was picturing, but...
15 miles per houris a significant increase
over walking.
[Clears throat]
To be fair, she wasn't
lying about the garage.
She came through.
[Chuckles]
Oh, man.
[Clears throat]
Listen, I --I'm not a bad person.
I want you to know that.
And you had every reason
not to trust me.
It's so hard to take a chance
on people in this world.
And when those people
lie to you, well ---
Yeah. I know.
It sucks.
I blew it.
I know.
And I'm sorry.
I guess...
I wish I had
done things better,
but I guess my people skills
are pretty rusty.
Well, that's something we'regonna have to work on, then.
I was coming over here to seeif you wanted to join us.
♪♪
Wait. For real?
Yeah, as long as you don'tlie to us again, okay?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes!
[Laughs]
Yes, yes!
Oh, okay.
Well,you know the area, so...
[Laughing]
Do we have enough time to grab
stuff from my stash?
I-I-I've got food
and clothes
and a cool spear
and some candy.
Does this mean
I get to have my gun back?
Can I know
where we're going?
Is there a map?
Do I get to hold it?
What is it?
I can't believe
we just left her.
In a ditch.
What if you were lost...
and no one could find you?
Or RJ was.
Or Mom.
You gotta tell mewhere this is coming from.
I just want us to be
back together again.
At home.
That's all.
I radioed your mom
so she knows not to go home,so she's safe.
And that way,
she can find us.
You talked to her?
No.
But I'm gonna
keep trying.
♪♪
It doesn't matter.
I talked to her
after the fire.
And I'm worried...
maybe she won't
come home.
♪♪
What'd she say?
She went to go help
some people she met.
Who needed her.
I didn't wanna tell you.
Why's that?
♪♪
'Cause maybe
you'd leave, too.
♪♪
I won't.
You promise?
I can't.
Why?
Because I can't
lie to you.
I don't knowwhat's gonna happen.
And there ain't no onethat can tell you that they do.
♪♪
And there's one thingI know.
There's a whole bunch of peopleback there
that'd do anything
for you.
And one day,
when you're older,
they're gonna need you to doanything for them.
You gota whole lot of family.
♪♪
Nothing can take the place ofsomeone you love being gone.
But that doesn't meanthat everything that follows
is gonna break your heart.
♪♪
Hey.
We gotta go, kiddo,
all right?
Come on.
[Radio static]
Gabriel?
Gabriel: Daryl...
where are you?
You're breaking up.
I can't hear you.
Come back...
they've...
surrounded the --
Gabriel?
We need...wagon...Gabriel!
[Growling]
♪♪
Faith.
Faaaaith...
Reward.
All:
Rewaaaaaaaaard...
♪♪