[Clock ticking]
♪♪
[Windmill creaking]
[Timer bell ringing]
♪♪
[Pills rattle]
[Gate squeals]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Walkers growling]
[Growling stops]
♪♪
Hyah!
[Laughing]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Growling stops]
[Panting]
[Groans]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
Aaron: They keep coming from
the direction of the border.
Just a constant
wave after wave.
This is her.
You know your training.
Lock it down.
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Walkers growling]
Woman:
There's more coming!
♪♪
[Indistinct shouting,
walkers growling]
Man:
There's more coming in!
[Indistinct shouting]
♪♪
[Panting]
[Walker growling]
[Growling stops]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Sword rattles]
It's not smart to go to sleep
unless it's safe.
No.
It's not.
Well?
"Well" what?
Is it safe?
[Walkie-talkie clicks]Man: Michonne, do you copy?
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
How long
till the next wave hits?
One hour from the north,
two from the south.
Northern wave's thicker
than fleas on a farm dog,
but the southern's
more dispersed.
By my estimation,
we'll be fighting
into the night again.
Yeah, can't push 'em
too much further.
I have eyes.
Sorry.
I'm just tired.
We all are.
[Insects chirping]
♪♪
Hey, heads up.
[Flies buzzing]
♪♪
The north border.
Now.
Call off your walkers.Not us.
Yeah, right.
Not.
Us.
♪♪
Go to the border,
lay down your weapons,
and wait.
Wait for what?
Her.
[Fly buzzes]
[Indistinct conversations]
All right!
Is this your mother?
No.
I don't think it is.
Why's she want
to talk with us?
You crossed
into her land.
Again.
You have to answer for that.
We don't have to
do anything.
We could just not go.
That's a bad idea.We're already
under attack.
Yeah!Yeah!
It isn't her.
If she wanted you dead,
she'd send the horde.
All of it,
not just a few waves at a time.
Maybe she's trying
to wear us down first.
Or, as I relayed
to you all
at the beginning of this
meeting, there's plausible
reason to believe
that the satellite
and fire --Margo: I don't want
to hear about
the damn satellite anymore,
Eugene!
My friends died
trying to save yours
and ended up
with their heads on spikes.
[Chair scrapes]
The Highwaymen
want justice!
Yeah!Yeah!
So all I want
to hear from you
is that you're gonna take
a dozen of us
to meet these freaks
at the border
and that we're gonna take
that lead bitch's head off!
Gage:
We cut it off![Whimpers]
And then we'll put
theirheads on spikes!
[Indistinct shouting]
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah, I just need
to get some air.
[Indistinct talking]
[Talking stops]
How many walkers did you see
in Alpha's horde?
Tens of thousands.
Ah.
So...
What's your plan
for taking them out?
Oh,
that wasn't rhetorical.
I don't have one.
Ah.
Does anybody else?
If she sends that horde,
that's it!
Right now,
all she wants to do is talk.
And we are going to listen.
Now, while we are doing that,
everyone here needs to focus
on what's coming in
from the north and the south.
[Sighs]
We're tired.
We are on edge.
And it is going to get worse
before it gets better.
But we aren't gonna
get through it at all
if we do not act as one.
♪♪
Three objectives
means three groups.
Gabriel will take point
in guarding the gate
from the northern wave...
while Aaron
will take some troops
and handle the southern wave,
breaking it up
before it hits the wall.
[Mace cranks]
That leaves us,
and the border.
Unarmed.
You're really
going in there unarmed?
We got no choice.
♪♪
[Tape rips]
[Gun clicks]
[Pills rattle]
♪♪
We're good.
You're low
on soldiers already.
The ones you have
are fighting fatigue.
Negan has only
been on cleanup duty.
I said we're good.
Hey, uh, Gabe.
Can I...
Look, man,
if it's all the same to you,
I'd rather
just stay here
and pick tomatoes
and bury corpses.
Gabriel: He needs you
out there.
Yeah,
I need me in here,
especially on
a day like today.
I mean, look around --
everybody's amped to 11,
pissed at the skins,
stirring shit up
with each other.
I told you,
I don't want
any of those hateful vibes
taken out on me.
It's Aaron.
He's a saint.
Look,
I just want to stay here.
Can you just
do me that solid, Gabe?
You can fight.
You are low
on fighters.
Peanut butter,
meet jelly.
You're taking him.
End of discussion.
So...
That's awesome.
Good on you,
puttin' the ol' stump to use.
♪♪
[Gate squeals]
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
Oh.
Oh, lookie here.
Oh, God.
Drop it.
Come on.
I'm pretty sure that God
put this here for a reason --
to help me,
help you--
Put it down.
Look,
we both know
that this broomstick
ain't cutting it.
[Sighs]
I am trying
to make things better,
and I am not
that guy that you think --
There's three coming in.
[Walkers growling]
They're on your side.
Right. Okay.
I am on it,
boss.
[Growling continues]
[Crickets chirping]
[Sword rattles]
♪♪
[Thud]
You all right?
♪♪
I...
need a minute.
♪♪
[Wind blowing]
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
Thanks for
coming out with me.
I could --
I could go all night.
[Growling continues]
You wanna go back,
don't you?
[Growling continues]
I'm good. [Grunts]
[Insects chirping]
Heads up.
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
Alpha: There was one rule
between our people.
One law.
Stay where you are.
Yet you disobey.
Daryl: That fire would've
destroyed your land.
Fire's nature to burn.
We have no conflict
with nature.
It could've wiped out
one of our communities.
We were not gonna sit back
and let that happen.
You can understand that.
We crossed one time.
Three times.
♪♪
During the fire,
you walked my land.
And during the winter storm,
During your search
along the river,
you and the man with
the metal arm walked my land.
That's three times.
We are always watching.
♪♪
What did I tell you
about crossing my border?
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
You have to be punished.
[Knives unsheathe]
♪♪
But...
I consider context.
There will be
no bloodshed this time.
So what do you want?
♪♪
Land.
The creek
that winds into the valley.
That is
your new southern border.
We will mark the new border
to the north.
That'll cut off
our hunting grounds.
We don't have to stand here
and listen to this --
Carol!
"To this"...
what?
♪♪
To this bullshit.Daryl: That's it.
Come on.
We're done.
Let's go.We're not.
♪♪
Not until this one
lowers her eyes to my feet.
♪♪
You should fear me.
I don't.
I look at you
and I feel nothing at all.
[Walkers growling in distance]
Is that right?
The blonde boy...
screamed your name
just before we took his head.
♪♪
[Gun cocks, gunshot]
Stop. Stop!
[Grunts]
I apologize...
for my friend.
We have not slept.
And you know
what she lost.
♪♪
I forgive you.
Mother to mother.
♪♪
This is my land now.
You better run.
Daryl: Come on.Let's go.
♪♪
Let's go.
[Crickets chirping]
Listen.
I know that
you're dealing with --
The bitch has to die.
She ain't been the same
since she got off that boat.
Maybe she's better off
on it.
Found some peace,
you know?
Michonne: Hey.
She belongs with us.
She ain't sleeping,
either.
She's out all night
looking for them.
[Gun cocks]
[Branches rustling]
♪♪
[Gunshot]
[Grunts] Shit.
What happened?
Whisperers.
Three of them.Walkies on.
Split up -- north, west.
We'll take east.
Capture!
Do not kill!
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Growling stops]
[Sighs]
[Inhales sharply]
Hey, you, uh --
What did I say?
[Sighs]
I had to.
Did you not see this...
[Chuckles]
What, do you want me
to hang myself?
Tie up.
I'm taking you back.
Taking me back?
That is the best freaking news
I've had all day!
But I am not tying up
like some P.O.W.
Yes, you are.
Or what, cowboy?
Ah.
You know what I see?
I see someone
that's pretending.
Come on, man.
Let's go.
Aah!
Jesus.
Did you just
trip me?
What,
are you 12?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I've been puttin' my neck
on a block for you people
all goddamn day!
You don't give a damn
about us.
If you gave a shit,
you'd leave.
That's what
everyone needs.
I did
what I had to do back then.
What did you say?
No, no, no.
Open that up.
Tell me why
the love of my life
had to die.
Okay.
One simple fact.
One truth
kept my people going --
if you don't protect
what belongs to you,
then sooner or later,
it belongs
to someone else.
That goes for your land,
your wallet,
your home, your country --
everything.
It is your job as a man
to protect it.
That's the story
of America,
the story
of the whole goddamn world.
And ain't nothing
changing it --
not you,
not me, nobody.
Are you saying that
Eric's death
was my fault?
Well...
If I failed Eric...
then you failed
your wife.
♪♪
Careful.
Yeah.
She, uh...
died hating you.
And you will never
see her again.
[Chuckles]
You wanna say something?
Yeah.
Behind you.
[Walkers growling]
[Groaning]
[Growling stops]
[Grunts]
[Groaning]
[Spits]
♪♪
Negan!
All right.
I'll meet you back at the creek.
Woman: Copy.
[Pills rattle]
No sign
of them anywhere.
No traces, no tracks,
nothing.
You're sure
you saw three?
Yeah.
I'm sure.
Carol...
how long you been
taking those pills for?
Since I got back.
It's fine.
They're like coffee.
We can't stay out here.
All right.
Find a place
with walls,
hole up
for a little while.
Get some sleep.
♪♪
[Glass crunching]
[Door creaking]
♪♪
[Glass crunching]
It's clear.
♪♪
[Book scrapes]
[Rattle in distance]
♪♪
Daryl: Hey.
[Gasps]
Come on.
♪♪
[Book thuds]
Michonne: You two,
get down here.
Man: Gotcha.Keep watch
on the east end.
I'll take first watch.All right.
♪♪
Negan!
[Door opens, closes]
[Panting]
♪♪
What?
Nah, just thinking
'bout my dad.
[Chuckles]
He was a trucker.
He used to
tell Merle and I
all these crazy stories
about his trips.
This one time,
he was flying through Kentucky
on I-66,
and it's
pitch-black outside.
He sees this girl
up on the side of the road,
looks like
she's crying.
As he gets closer,
the girl steps right out
into the freeway,
right in front
of his truck.
He slams
on the brakes,
calls the local PD,
gets out,
and goes lookin' for her.
Only she ain't there.
He looks
under the cab, nothin'.
Under the tires,
nope.
She's not around.
No dent in the grille,
no blood, no nothin'.
How's that possible?
There was no girl.
See, my dad
didn't sleep much, either.
Sometimes he'd stay up
24 hours
just to make
one of his runs.
You stay up that long,
you start
seeing things.
Daryl, I'm not a meth-snorting
truck driver like --
Not that your dad,
uh...
I'm sorry.
No, you're right.
Doesn't mean
I'm wrong, though.
[Alarm bell rings]
Shift's up.
[Pills rattle]Don't take that.
You need to sleep.
I can't.
[Bottle clatters]
Why's that?
Bad dreams?
[Clattering]
♪♪
[Glass shatters]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Clattering continues]
[Banging on door]
[Grunting]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
Negan?
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
You all right?
Yeah.
How did you --
Your light switched on.
[Grunts]
I can't see.
Flowers growing outta
the walkers is hogweed.
Hogweed?
Nasty shit.
Causes rashes,
blindness.
Is it permanent?
Sometimes.
You wash
your eyes out?
Yeah.
I used, uh...
It's gone.
Parched?
Yeah.
[Canteen lid squeaking]
Here.
Here we go.
[Grunts]
All right.
Right here.
Wait.
Where you going?
I'm gonna keep watch.
We'll leave
first thing in the morning.
I mean,
if that's okay with you.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's okay.
[Clang in distance]
♪♪
[Glass crunching]
Henry: Mom?
♪♪
Mom.
Daryl: Hey.
You all right?
Where'd you go?
What?
You've been gone
a half-hour.
Uh...patrol.
Thought I heard something.
I'm fine.
This isn't your dad
seeing a ghost.
What?
The story
of the girl
when your dad
was a truck driver.
My dad
wasn't a truck driver.
[Alarm bell ringing]
Shift's up.
[Timer cranks]
[Pills rattle]
Come on.
Don't take that.
One more hour.
One hour.
All right.
♪♪
[Chain rattling]
[Glass crunches]
♪♪
[Glass shatters]
[Glass crunches]
♪♪
Aah![Crashing]
[Rope creaking]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Glass crinkling]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Gunshot][Walkers growling]
Help!
Daryl! Help!
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Wood creaking]
[Thud]
♪♪
[Alarm bell ringing]
[Flashlight clicks]
Daryl: Carol!
♪♪
Doc!
Siddiq:
What happened?
She fell.
She cut her arm real bad.
Easy.
Gonna need you all
to leave.
Okay,
you pull the shard,
clamp open the wound,
and I'll go in.
Dante:
Say the word.
♪♪
[Woman screaming]
Good.
[Breathing heavily]
You clamp.
I'll go in.
I'm fine.
You're not.
[Groans]
Hey.
It's okay.
Here.
[Crickets chirping]
[Door opens]
Is she all right?
She, um...
I...
He got it out.
She's all patched up
and out like a light.
Great.
[Birds chirping]
Can you see me?
Yeah.
Good.
[Insects buzzing]
Rosita: Ugh!
Damn.
I'm tired.
You should be.
You were mean
as a mama wasp out there.
Yeah?
You were, uh...
You were tough
as a...
A stewed skunk?
[Sighs]
Batshit badger?
Pissed-off penguin?
[Laughing]
All of the above.
[Chuckles]
Rosita,
where's Coco?Probably sleeping.
I think you confused my query
for "action"
when I was trying
to discern "locale."
She's with Barbara.
Is that okay?
It's just...
that little nugget can't grow up
without her mama.
I went out with you today
to protect you
because I care about you.Protect me?
I taught you
how to fight.
[Scoffs]
Rosita, I --
Damn it, Eugene!
You and I
are never going to happen.
You are not
Coco's father.
We are not together.
I need you
to hear that.
[Sighs]
I...
I'm sorry
that was harsh.
I'm...
I'm just --
I'm so tired.
I feel...drunk.
[Sighs]
Oh, God.
Are you familiar
with the expression,
"A drunk mind
speaks a sober heart?"
No.
When under the influence,
inhibitions are lowered.
Secrets and truths
pour out.
Pun intended.
Sleep deprivation
lowers inhibition,
enhances impulsivity
in a similar manner.
Thus, when you say,
"It's not gonna happen,"
it's unfiltered truth
straight from your ticker.
I've been trying
to tell you that.
And I did not listen.
'Cause I thought that,
perhaps someday,
there might be
something special
between you
and yours truly.
But there's nothing there.
There never was.
You think that our friendship
is just nothing?
Is that
your unfiltered truth?
I don't mean to eat sorrow
by the spoonful in front of you,
but I'm in the midst
of experiencing
a crushing moment of clarity.
Our --
Our whole friendship
is premised on
my mistaken belief that,
perhaps someday, I could
change your mind, that...
you would see that
I was worthy enough
of being re-zoned
into love-town.
What kind of friend
is that?
I'm sorry.
Eugene...
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
Michonne:
Still awake?
Yeah.
You and me both.
[Sighs]
How you holding up?
I should
be asking you that.
I'm a mother.
Lack of sleep
is my baseline reality.
You had that look
in the meeting hall...
[Scoffs]
I'm a father.
[Sniffles]
I'm just -- I'm tired.
Tired.
Yeah.
Okay.
See you later?
Yeah.
We'll be
good as new.
Speak for
your damn self.
[Scoffs]
Okay.
Come on, man.
I -- Look,
I gotta go to sleep.
Oh, no.
That's why
I brought it over.
[Chuckles ]
[Liquid pouring]
You know
I saw combat in Iraq?
Yeah,
I was a field medic.
And you are
telling me this now?
Well, I don't like talking
about it unless I have to, so...
[Glasses clink]
Cheers. [Sniffles]
[Slurps]
[Sighs]
You go in one person,
come out different.
♪♪
I knew this one guy --
[Chuckles]
Shit,
everyone knew him.
Cocky.
Broad-shouldered,
Adonis-looking cat.
[Chuckles]
Like, this was the dude
that never broke.
♪♪
Until he did.
Lost his squad
in Fallujah.
Blamed himself.
♪♪
Came back with the shakes,
the thousand-mile stare,
the flashbacks,
going in and out of VAs.
He was a mess...
"He was"?
"Was"?
What -- What happened
to this guy?
♪♪
You're having a drink
with him.
[Laughing] Sorry.
[Chuckles]
"Adonis-looking cat"?
Oh.
God of beauty, baby.
I'm just
being humble.
[Laughing]
[Elliott Smith's
"Care of Cell 44"plays]
♪ Good morning to you
♪ I hope you're feeling better,
baby ♪
♪ Thinking of me
while you are far away ♪
Hey.
♪ Counting the days until they set you free again
♪
[Sighs]
Oh. We need jam.
Oh. There's probably some
at the store.
Hold on.
There you go.
Thank you.
You sure
they're open right now?
[Watch ticking]
Henry: Mom?
Where you going?
[Ticking echoes]
♪♪
[Sighs]
How is it?
Hurts.
Being back here
hurts, too.
And that's her fault.
You shouldn't have
stopped me.
There were seven of us
out there.
I had to
think of them.
I know.
But I did see them.
Only you did.
♪♪
Is it safe?
For now.
♪♪
[Door opens]
Pink suits you.
[Chuckles]
She doesn't believe me.
Do you?
Yeah.
♪♪