[Birds chirping]
♪♪
[Kettle whistling]
[Whistling stops]
♪♪
[Sighs]
[Gate creaks]
Daryl: Hi.
Hey.
Feelin' better?
Yeah. Thanks.
Where you goin'?
Mm, gonna do another sweep
for Negan.
Cool.
You want company?
[Birds chirping]
Think Negan
crossed the border?
He'd know we couldn't
follow him over there.
I can't see him
puttin' on a mask.
Or staying quiet
for long.
Still, stranger things
have happened.
We takin' a break?
Nope.
This is
our spot today.
Gonna stay here...
see what we see.
He ain't
gonna wander around,
waitin' to get spotted.
He ain't that dumb.
Neither are you.
Gee, thanks.
You wanna tell me
what we're doin' out here?
Lookin' for Negan.
Right.
You gonna tell me
what we're really lookin' for?
♪♪
Alpha's horde.
[Sighs]
We're gonna find it,
and we're gonna destroy it.
♪♪
Come on.
Admit it.
There's a tiny part of you
that's thrilled to be sick.
Just so you
can spend more time with me.
You think I'm pukin'
because I got
a little crush?
Textbook case
of butterflies in the stomach.
I want
a second opinion.
Oh, it's simple science,
darlin'.
Bodies
manifest emotion
in all sorts
of different ways.
The heart wants
what it wants.
Right?
Inhale for me.
[Inhales deeply]
Good.
[Door opens]And exhale.
[Exhales]
Alright.
[Door closes]Seriously, though,
don't you think we'd make
a bitchin' couple?
Son, I would break you
like a twig.
Siddiq: How's he doin',
Cheryl?
Jury's still out.
Ouch.
I thought we were havin'
a moment here, Cheryl.
Is she okay?
Everything alright?
Yeah.
Couple more cases
of that stomach bug.
[Sighs]
So that
makes it seven.
Yeah.
You know,
maybe I should just
put Coco down
for a minute --
Don't worry about it,
man.
I got it.
Sure?
Yeah.
How's Rosita?
Ah, same as everybody else,
it seems.
The most we can do
is keep 'em hydrated
and wait it out.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, lap up the daddy/daughter
shit while you can,
because they grow
so damn fast.
[Babbles]
[Coco coos]
Okay, a-alright, easy.
Dude, easy.
Have some boundaries.
Okay.
My bad.
[Chuckles]
You two should go out,
have some fun.
[Pen clicks][Clears throat]
[Sighs]
Alright, thanks.
And if you need me
to peek at Rosita later,
just say the word.
Happy to,
you know,
make sure
she's on the mend.
[Chuckles]
That's one of
those boundaries again.
Yep.
Yeah.
Noted.
Carol: Alpha's been sending
waves of walkers
to screw with us,
right?
Well, I've been tracking walker
movement along the border.
Small groups.
Some of them might have
Whisperers in them.
But they all connect right back
to this general area,
so I figure
we stake out this spot.
See where
the Whisperers go.
Might lead us
back to the horde.
That's smart.
I thought so.
She's gonna need a place,
though,
like the canyon
they used to be in.
Only spots I know are on
Whisperer territory, though.
Not gonna be able
to sneak in there
without startin' up
some kind of shit.
We only need to figure out
where they are,
and then we'll tell the council.
I swear.
Why weren't you
straight with me before?
After what happened
at the border and with Alpha,
I didn't want you
to worry.
Sorry.
I get it.
Just wanna
keep us safe.
[Sighs]
So,
you gonna stick around?
Well, if you
spot somethin',
you're gonna need me
to track it, right?
I dunno.
Picked up a few things
over the years.
[Chuckles]
Yeah,
we'll see.
Honestly,
fellas -- or ladies.
Kinda hard to tell
underneath the outfits.
I wanna join,
alright?
I am a joiner.
Get me
a damn application already.
I mean,
look at you guys, right?
Cool-ass outfits,
the whole
back-to-nature paleo vibe?
You are
a survivalist's wet dream.
Not to mention
the number-one selling point --
no more
bein' eaten by the dead.
But just, out of curiosity,
'cause it's killin' me,
what do you got
goin' on down low?
Are you flyin' around
commando-style,
or do you got, like,
walker long johns
with the la-- flap?
Whoa.
Cool your tits there,
Jolly Green Giant.
Noise.
Constant noise.
I should just
slit your throat,
be done with it.
Okay.
You know what?
You're right, big man.
I am sorry.
I never
properly introduced myself.
Hey, I'm Negan.
♪♪
For the last
eight years,
I have been locked up
by your enemy.
So you take me
to your leader,
and I will spill
every Goddamn secret I know.
♪♪
[Indistinct conversations]
Eugene?
I got
the supplies ya asked for.
Well, feel free
to deposit those
in any location
of your choosin'.
Gotta say, your assist
on the radio relaunch
has been a boon,
and I thank you mightily.
Well, I'm happy to be a part
of the Hilltop AV club.
Care to take the new setup
for a spin?
Some primo
choice upgrades.
Transmitter's been
properly souped up
with Soviet satellite guts,
and...
You don't
parlez-vousRussian,
by any chance?
Nyet.
Well,
that's all I got.
Hmm. Solid.
Well,
just checkin'.
Relocatin' the antenna
to the apex
provides unobstructed L-O-S
to the secondary repeater,
exponentially expanding
our range.
You haven't lived
till you've bounced a
transmission off the ionosphere.
Gives me gooseflesh
each and every time.
Well, this sounds really cool,
Eugene,
but I gotta get back
to the kids.
Oh, yeah.
Understandable.
Bambinos,
they take precedent.
No expiration
on that invite, though.
Cool. Thanks.
Have fun.
[Footsteps depart]
[Door opens, closes]
Solo trip it is.
Let's see how far you can fly,
little lady.
[Switch clicks]
[Clears throat]
[Sighs]
Rosita:
Calling for Hilltop.
Come in, Hilltop.
[Buttons clicking, static]
Hilltop.
Calling Hilltop.
Copy that,
Alexandria.
This is Hilltop.
Eugene?
Um, yes.
Were you lookin' for someone
in particular?
No, dumbass.
I'm looking for you.
Oh.
Okeydokey.
♪♪
Just wanted to see
what you were up to.
I figured I'd call.
But I'm also running
a 102-degree fever,
so I could
just be delirious.
What sort of ailments
are we wrestlin' with?
Just a bug.
I'll be fine.
And Coco's okay.
What about you?
What are you up to?
♪♪
Oh, just some garden-variety
engineerin' advice,
structural
stability checks,
a total revamp
of their radio setup.
Um, everyone wants
a slice of Eugene.
♪♪
Are you coming back
anytime soon?
To be honest,
I haven't given much thought
to a timetable,
but it is mighty good
to hear your voice.
You, too.
♪♪
[Electricity crackles]Hold on.
We got
a malfunction.
Mother of pearl.
Everything okay?
Bad solder.
It was a gaffe
on my part.
I'm gonna have to
fix this pronto
before the whole thing
goes FUBAR.
I should
get back into bed anyway.
Do you want me to call you
this afternoon?
Are radio waves sinusoidal?
Um, [Chuckles] yes?
Yes.
Yes, they are.
Ugh.
So close.
Ew.
Ugh.
Mr. Crossbow,
I thought aiming was your thing.
[Scoffs]
It's definitely
not your thing.
Mnh-mnh.
Sorry, it doesn't count.
'Course that counts.
No, you gotta
knock the can over.
You can't just
kiss it.
Oh, my God.
You're such
a sore loser.
I'd have to lose
in order to be a sore loser,
so since
that didn't count,
I'm gonna
take my turn.
Oh,
it's a double-capper.
They're good luck.
Maybe it'll help
your aim.
Very funny.
But I'll keep it.
You should watch
your own throws, though.
Boom.
How was Hilltop?
It was fine.
King sends his best.
Connie fine, too?
[Sighs, chuckles]
What?
I see things.
It's not like that.
No?
Not at all.
Why not?
[Sighs]
Aren't that many people left
to find out there these days,
much less
good ones like her.
Yeah, I know.
Well, then why not?
What's it matter?
'Cause it does.
You don't
have to be alone.
Years pass,
Daryl.
You can't hide out
with your dog forever.
♪♪
[Chuckles]
Oh, see?
Your aim's
better already.
I'm hungry.
You got food?
Yeah,
I'll get it.
♪♪
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
♪♪
Mmm.
Hey,
you see that?
♪♪
[Herd growling]
It's a Whisperer.
♪♪
He cannot be trusted.
Dispose of him.
♪♪
Test him.
If he is worthy,
I will hear him.
If not,
then I kill him.
♪♪
You have other thoughts?
It is a mistake
showing him our ways.
♪♪
Your questionin'
of my judgment
has become
a regular occurrence.
He is a threat.
♪♪
To Alpha or to Beta?
I think
only of our people.
♪♪
Is it finally time
for the Beta
to become the Alpha?
♪♪
Never.
[Sighs]
How long you and the boss lady
been together?
Is this, like, a
Beta-with-benefits situation?
Do you slide her a little omega
on the side?
You'll respect
the Alpha,
or I end you
where you stand.
I didn't mean
to offend you.
I mean, hell,
you keep things professional.
I respect that.
Think I was just thrown off
by the whole kneelin' thing.
Not that
there's anything wrong
with the whole
kneelin' thing.
I mean,
that has tickled the dicks
of many a fine man
over the years.
Me, myself, I used to
have people kneelin' for me
all the livelong day,
so I do understand
the benefits
that sort of shit
provides.
Just actually
never done the deed myself.
And I admire
your self-restraint,
and I'm sayin' this
totally respectfully,
but there is somethin' about
that whole bald-head thing
that just
[Inhales sharply]
tightens my britches.
[Knock on door]
Rosita? Gabriel?
Just wanted to swing by to grab
a change of clothes for Coco.
Hey, you.
I think I need
a house call, Doc.
Hm.
I thought we were
supposed to be in bed.
I was,
and then I was feeling better,
so I came downstairs.
And then
I was feeling even worse,
so now I'm stuck.
Well, you shoulda called Gabe
to come get me.
Ah, the Good Shepherd
is out on patrol.
Overnighter.
[Sighs] Okay.
Well, field trip
to the infirmary.
No, come on, Siddiq.
I have so much to do.
I know,
like going to the infirmary.
No, no, no, no.
If you just help me
get to the garage so...
Yeah.
Shit.
No. Okay.
Look,
it's a crazy idea,
but how about we all go
to the infirmary?
Mm? Yeah?
Coco says yeah.
Let's go.
[Coco coos]
Easy.
♪♪
This is Hilltop callin' over
to Alexandria.
Do you copy?
♪♪
Alexandria, let us know
if you are receivin'.
♪♪
Alexandria proper,
please respond.
♪♪
[Static]
[Clears throat]
Greetings.
This is Tater Bug,
callin' live over open channels.
Anyone out there,
give us a copy.
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
Carol:
It's getting bigger.
Yeah, looks like they're
gatherin' up all the strays.
Well,
once the sun goes down,
it's gonna be tough
to see where they go
unless
we can get closer.
What makes you think
they're goin' anywhere?
If you and me
were Whisperers,
that's when
we'd move 'em.
You know I'm right.
You wanna cross the border,
don't ya?
I wanna find the horde.
If that's what it takes...
♪♪
Sure this isn't you
just tryin'
to take another shot at Alpha?
The horde is our shot.
You changin' your mind?
Nope.
I didn't say that.
Then what's the problem?
[Sighs]
Alright, we do this,
we gotta be smart about it.
None of this "runnin' off
in the middle of the night,
no backup, just us"
stuff, alright?
♪♪
Since when
are we not enough?
♪♪
You know,
we mess this up,
everyone else
is gonna pay for it, right?
We've already paid.
We keep paying
no matter what
side of the line we're on.
[Sighs]
♪♪
I gotta pee.
Did you find
what you were lookin' for?
♪♪
You bring the gun?
No.
Used up all the ammunition,
remember?
There was still some ammo left
in the storage room.
I didn't
bring the gun, Daryl.
Wanna frisk me?
Go ahead.
Okay.
♪♪
[Sighs]
Either we're enough,
or we're not.
♪♪
Alright,
let's do it.
A plan this stupid,
might as well be us.
♪♪
So,
do I get bathed
and reborn
in her Whisper-y image,
or is this more like
a ball-trippin',
skin-themed vision quest?
Dig.
That's it?
[Spits]
I can do that.
[Grunts]
Anything in particular
we're goin' for here?
Size, depth, width?
Just dig.
[Chuckles]
Alright.
[ "Spinning Top"plays]
♪♪
♪ Talk about your yo-yo
♪ You should see
my spinnin' top ♪
♪ Talk about your yo-yo
♪ You should see
my spinnin' top ♪
[Grunts]
♪ It goes around and 'round
♪ Oh, it never stops
♪ You should see
♪ My spinnin' top
on the ground ♪
♪ You should see
♪ My spinnin' top
on the ground ♪
♪ It goes 'round and down,
round and 'round and 'round ♪
♪ Now, watch it, everybody
♪ What did I tell you?
♪ My spinnin' top is good
♪ Just line it up, baby,
like you know you should ♪
Deeper?
♪ Aw, let me show you how
Sure. Why not?
♪♪
♪ My spinnin' top
♪ Is my pride and joy
[Grunts][Pig squealing]
♪ I use it myself
♪ It's my own little
personal toy ♪
Now, let me show you
what I mean.
Now, watch it, everybody.
Now, I get it.
All these people
do the twist.
♪♪
[Spits]
Siddiq:
Watch your step.
Here we go.
Yeah. Okay.
Looks like
I'm not the only one.
Yeah.
Let's get you
a seat.
[Man groans]
Dante?
Dante: Go ahead
and grab a seat wherever.
I'll be with you
in a sec.
Dante, what the hell
is goin' on?
Hey, guys.
I-I-I think the illness
is spreading
faster than
we thought.
I-I didn't want
to bother you.
That is not a decision
you get to make.
Damn it, man, this is why I said
I shouldn't leave.
Hey, Siddiq, he's --
What?
He's tryin' to help.
Start crushing herbs --
ginger and mint
for the nausea
and oil of oregano
and yarrow for the fever.
Alright.
This is only gonna get worse
if we're not ahead of it.
You good
with these rules?
Yeah.
Don't be seen.
No tracks,
no killin' walkers neither.
Find a bunch of bodies
with holes in their heads,
we might as well leave a note
saying we were here.
♪♪
Watch, learn, leave.
Yeah, if things go sideways,
we head back.
We get split up,
you meet me
right here, alright?
Yeah.
And be safe.
We got luck on our side,
alright?
Come on.
Negan:
My porky here,
he was a bastard
to take down.
But I gotta say, this is exactly
the kind of badass shit
I will do
for my new family.
Beta: Only those
who have earned
the right
to walk among us may eat.
♪♪
Earned?
Big man,
I helped kill
and cook the damn pig.
Come on, man, alright?
At the very least,
I deserve
a piece of bacon.
[Grunts]
♪♪
Whatever you say,
boss.
♪♪
This is Tater Bug over open air,
surfin' on
these proverbial radio waves.
Any interested earholes,
come on back.
[Static]
[Knob cranks, static]
Anyone anywhere?
This is Tater Bug.
Woman: Hello?
Hello, Tater Bug?
♪♪
I receive you
loud and clear.
I-I can't believe this.
Are you --
Are you really out there?
♪♪
[Herd growling]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
Man:
Not here.
♪♪
Woman:
Keep looking.
♪♪
Well, had I considered
the prospect of first contact,
I would've prepared
proper remarks
toward the establishin'
of relations.
Over.
Woman: I don't quite know
what to say, either.
I'd gotten
to the point
where I figured
this was a waste of time.
Over.
Well, perhaps an exchange
of Q&As might grease the wheels.
A few
right off the top of my dome --
where are you located,
how long have you been there,
how many people
do you have,
and should we continue
saying "over"?
Over.
We can probably make do
without the "overs."
As for
the other stuff,
I don't think I'm comfortable
sharing that just yet.
Understandable.
Any alts more within
your zone of comfort?
Maybe talk about our lives
before all this?
My personal origin entails
a long and storied history.
Were you thinkin' prologue,
or should I skip ahead
a few chapters?
I guess, uh,
start with where you're from.
Certainly.
A Lone Star child
at heart,
I was born
in the shadows of Big D.
That's a well-worn nickname
for Dallas, Texas.
Yeah,
I picked up on that.
I grew up
in Pennsylvania,
a small town
called Strasburg.
Uh,
dubious as it may seem,
I know
Strasburg, Pennsylvania, well.
Sure you do.True as Coventry blue.
Durin' adolescence,
I went through
a significant foamer phase.
Locomotives were my jam.
As such,
my parents purchased
a pair of tickets
to the 1995 Trainfan Expo
at the Railroad Museum
in, well, you guessed it.
Strasburg, Pennsylvania.
Whoa.
I have the most vivid memory
of an ice-cream shop
with the most marvelous batch
of black raspberry ice cream.
The Inside Scoop.
Went there all the time.
Hell, you and I might've
been there on the same day.
Well,
knowin' this,
there's a critical question
needs answerin'.
What's that?
Cake cone or waffle?
[Laughs]
[Chuckles]
[Herd growling]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
Been decades
since I got this much attention
from younger men.
[Chuckles]
Well,
you're my patient,
so it's kinda my job
to keep an eye on you.
Then what's with the look
of gloom and doom?
I feel like I'm nappin'
next to the grim reaper.
[Chuckles]
Sorry.
I'm just,
um, a little concerned.
Oh, hon, in this world,
most don't get the luxury
of driftin' off
in a nice, comfy bed.
I should be
so lucky.
[ Chuckles ][Door opens]
[Door closes][Chuckles]
Get some rest.
Hey, hey,
I'll get it for you.
Oh, thanks, man.
[Door creaks]
About what I said earlier,
I, um...
No worries.
I get it.
We're stuck with
pre-industrial-age meds,
and simple shit can suddenly
become a big deal.
We'll figure it out.
[Chuckles]
Thanks, Dante.
I-I appreciate
your help.
You should.
I'm kind of amazing.
[Both chuckle]
Get some rest,
boss.
Alright, come on.
[Door creaks]
Mm.
[Coco cries]
Hey, Coco.
Hey.
It's okay.
Shh.
Aww, it's okay.
Uh, Daddy gotcha.
Oh, it's alright.
Hey.
Hey, it's okay.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, it's okay.
[Chair creaks]
There you go.
[Chair creaking, clock ticking]
♪♪
[Heavy breathing]
[Rosita groaning]
♪♪
Alpha:
Open your eyes.
[Screaming]
[Screaming continues]
[Distorted]
Open your eyes.
♪♪
[Herd growling]
Clearly,
we are not jivin'.
And, you know,
to be honest with you,
I totally understand
the position you're in.
You gotta be, like,
the tough guy
and keep everybody in line.
I mean,
hell, you know,
I had guys just like you
to keep my shit tight.
Alright,
maybe not just like you.
Uh, hell, if I had some monster
your size,
things would've
turned out different.
Look,
whether you like me or not,
I will be joinin'
this team,
so maybe we should find a way
to get along, you know,
and stop pissin'
on each other's boots.
You will never
be one of us.
You're too loud,
too weak,
too full of ego.
I mean,
it ain't ego
if I really am
that awesome.
You are a waste,
and Alpha
will see it.
So cards on the table,
then?
Cool.
I dig that.
See,
I'm not here for you.
I am here for Alpha.
So you go ahead,
and you throw
your little tests at me
and you scowl
and throw me on the ground like
a five-and-dime Frankenstein.
I don't give a shit.
See, big man,
I ain't goin' anywhere.
♪♪
Finally,
something we can
both agree on.
You won't be
going anywhere.
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
Wait a minute.
Did you just make
a Goddamn joke?
I would be impressed
if I wasn't
so pissed off right now.
[Grunts]
You have got
to be shittin' me.
♪♪
What the hell
is this?
He saw me.
We can take him back,
see what he knows.
Maybe it's a good thing.
Did you plan this?
No.
[Grunts]
What's this?
♪♪
It wasn't
in your bag.
Guess you missed it.
Come on.
We don't have time to argue.
It's done.
♪♪
Roller rinks never made much
dollars-and-centavos sense
to me, purely on
a risk/reward analysis.
Too afraid of falling?
Injury combined
with humiliation.
Not my favorite pastime.
♪♪
This deet exchange
on our formatives
has been
very enjoyable, and...
at the risk
of said humiliation,
I wonder if we could dip
our toes into some real talk.
♪♪
I...
It's been great,
honestly.
But I don't
really know you.
You might be a threat.
♪♪
Maybe it's better
if we let this be,
you know, what it is.
♪♪
What if I were
to share specifics?
Who's to say
I'm not a threat to you?
People are dangerous.
I'm well aware.
And yet,
I have a twinge in my belly
that says
you lean toward
the "good" column
of the alignment chart.
I do know you.
♪♪
My given name
is Eugene Hermann Porter,
and I propose we continue
these convos on the reg,
with the hopes
of buildin' more.
Should that meet
with your approval
and/or interest,
of course.
♪♪
Hello,
Eugene Hermann Porter.
I'd like that.
I'd like that
very much indeed.
So we're in agreement,
then.
We are.
[Chuckles]
But -- But let's just keep this
between us for now.
I wanna trust you,
but if I hear anyone else,
I'll know I can't.
♪♪
And you'll never
hear from me again.
[Chuckles]
Okay,
just you and me.
Copy that.
Over. [Chuckles]
♪♪
He was weak.
I expected more.
He will serve us better
as one of the dead.
Negan: I'm ready
for my Goddamn skin suit.
You best bring
that extra-long tape measure
on account
of my humongous balls.
♪♪
Hi.
I'm Negan.
We haven't
formally met,
but I sure as hell
know who you are.
♪♪
And whether my reputation
precedes me or not...
♪♪
...I'm all in.
Whatever you want,
whatever I got,
it's yours.
♪♪
Shh.