[Birds chirping]
[Chirping continues]
[High-pitched ringing]
[Chirping fades]
♪♪
[Wings fluttering]
[Cloth rustling]
[Snorting]
[Ringing stops,
chirping resumes]
[Chirping fades,
ringing resumes]
♪♪
[Ringing continues]
[No audio]
♪♪
[Muffled squealing]
[Muffled grunting]
♪♪
[Pig squeals]
[Leaves rustling]
[Growling]
♪♪
[Both growling]
[Muffled growling]
♪♪
[Insects chirping]
Brandon: Gotcha.
♪♪
Don't try anything.
[Laughing] Man.
The look on your face.
[Chuckles]
Dude, seriously, I'm --
I'm just messin' with you.
♪♪
You're fast.
Took me forever
to catch up.
♪♪
[Gulps]
[Walker growling]
Over there.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Indistinct conversations]
Eugene: Normally,
my chief concern
would be the hidden beauty
of the grain,
but with quantity
being of the essence,
rift and quarter sawing
it'll be.
Happy to recapitulate.
Oh, no, no, just checking in.
Y'all good?
Eugene's come up with
a zero-waste plan.
Claims he can use every cubic
inch of the tree, even the bark.
Seems as good a time
as any
to master the Pueblo art
of basket weaving.
Hey, uh,
before you head off,
Earl and I
were talking.
Instead of using the extra wood
for the addition,
what if we made
some weapons?
You know, big ones,
defensive,
couple -- couple of catapults
for the north wall.Yeah.
Yeah, no, look, I think
it's a good idea, honestly,
just not right now,
not with half the Kingdom
still in tents.
Okay. I get it.
So, the Whisperers smash
a giant hole in our wall...
Yeah, well, we don't know
it was them for sure.
...and now they're
throwin' walkers at us
every couple hours,
and we're just gonna sit here,
twiddlin' our damn thumbs?
It happened again.
Root cellar.
Middle of the night.
[Sighs]
Well, who the hell
was on watch?
♪ You're hard of hearin'
when I'm whisperin' ♪
♪ Love songs late at night
♪♪
♪ I'm used to
dinner 'n drinks ♪
♪ But now all we ever do
is fight ♪
♪ Leavin' liquor
in the laundry ♪[Volume decreases]
♪ 'Cause ya love watching me
play hide-and-seek ♪
I'm not sure
if you heard,
but someone stole
a crate of fish,
the one from Oceanside.
Third theft
this week, so...
♪ It's sad but true
Brianna said
that you were guarding
the root cellar last night.
The sickos showed up
at the breach.
♪ Oh, we used to stay up late
You know how strained
everything is at the moment.
It would really help
if we all just stuck
to the jobs we were given.
♪ ...call you up
and apologize ♪
♪♪
[Volume increases] ♪ And, oh, oh
♪ It's a cold, hard fact
♪ We've said a lot of things
you know now ♪
♪ We can't take back
♪ And, oh, oh, we used to
hold each other tight ♪
♪ Under sparkling trees
[Indistinct conversations]
[Motorcycle engine revving]
[Gate creaks]
[Engine shuts off]
[Gate closes]
No sign of Negan?
Searched all day and night,
but no sign of him.
Keep thinkin' about
what he took from us,
what we didn't take
from him.
[Coughs]
Alexandria deserved better.
Hey, you've had
your trouble, too.
Actually, we could use a hand
in the infirmary.
Much of the Kingdom's
still in recovery
from the tree fall.
We were plannin' on
leavin' tomorrow,
but, uh -- but yeah.
Of course.
Whatever you need.
You ask about Carol?
♪♪
Man: Open the gate!
[Gate opens]
Nah.
♪♪
[Gate creaks]
[Gate closes]
♪♪
She's not here?
She was
tracking something,
said she'd meet us
back here.
Should've been back
by now.
♪♪
[Insects chirping]
[Groans]
[Whistling in distance]
Was that it?
Did I get it?
[Chuckles] Nah. You woulda
totally whistled back, right?
My dad, he used to tell me
how, like,
you and the Saviors
would, like,
whistle back and forth
like that before --
You, uh -- you say you had
some granola or some shit?
[Coughs]
Sorry about the raisins
and the busted knife.
Was kinda in a rush
when I packed it all.
[Grunts]
So, you're really
not gonna tell me
how you got outta
that cell?
Alright, well, at least tell me
what we're lookin' for.
Someplace safe.
I get it.
A new Sanctuary.
Damn,
how badass was that place?
And then Rick Grimes
comes along,
talk about hypocrisy,
kills our parents,
drags us to Alexandria,
lectures us
about community.
Eh. Can't argue that.
It ain't bullshit.
Man, I heard you made him
cut his own kid's hand off,
then you killed them.
Carl Grimes --
I heard you shot him.
I never did that.
And I never did that
to Carl.
♪♪
Carl was...
I would never kill a kid.
♪♪
Yeah, no, definitely.
I'm with you, obviously.
We're both Negan.
♪♪
Who would do this?
The skin freaks.
Damn.
♪♪
Should we cross?
"The enemy of my enemy
is my friend"?
No.
[Rustling, walker growling]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Panting]
Thanks for your help.
Sorry. I just needed a second
to wrap your gift.
♪♪
There's more.
I swiped it all
from Alexandria.
Was waiting for the right time
to surprise you.
♪♪
Took me forever
to find this.
Found it in the back
of an old storage garage.
My dad said
he never saw you without it.
♪♪
Listen, uh...
why don't you just
put that in your backpack?
I don't
wanna be recognized.
You like it, though,
right?
♪♪
Does pig shit stink?
[Walker growling in distance]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
[Thud]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
I'm gonna say...
she's a seven.
What?
Isn't this
the kind of stuff
you and the Saviors
used to do to kill time?
I can't say that I remember
rating walkers on hotness.
Besides,
she's clearly a three.
Spot's not half bad,
right?
New Sanctuary.
[Woman screaming]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Thud]
You gotta be kidding me.
[Woman screaming]
♪♪
[Woman screaming,
walker growling]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
♪♪
Damn!
Classic Negan.
[Insects chirping]
It's not your fault.
Hey.
Did I ever tell you about
my brother, Merle?
Uh...
Merle.
Okay, this one time,
he takes me fishing.
Right?
Fishing, right,
on this big lake, right,
which is, uh...
private property...
right?
In this boat,
which is, uh, stolen.
Stolen boat, right?
And he's drinking,
right?
So he's fishing,
he's drinking.
He falls in the lake.
Like, ka-pssh!
Right?
I have to take him,
uh, like this...
[Panting]
...swim him
all the way back.
I save his life,
right?
You know
what he says to me?
"Dummy,
go get the beer."
[Laughs]
Idiot, right?
Yeah.
♪♪
It's gonna be alright.[Dog barks]
Come on.
[Dog barks]
Good dog. Good dog.
[Dog panting]
[Dog whines]
What?
♪♪
[Flies buzzing]
[Rustling]
[Grunts]
♪♪
Alden: So, uh, the roofing
and the gutters should be fine,
but the plumbing's
making me kinda nervous.
I have to scavenge
for more copper.
I should really
be out there with them.
♪♪
You know,
if I was lost in the woods,
it's the three of them
I'd want to come looking for me.
Somebody's gotta hang back,
deal with the plumbing.
[Chuckles]
I'll -- I'll ask Oscar
about the copper.
You really think
Kelly's okay?
I hope so.
What about us?
That tree
didn't fall on its own.
Wasn't leaning or dying.
The roots were healthy.
If you don't think they're
coming back for worse, son,
you're not thinking
at all.
I haven't forgotten about them,
you know?
Think about 'em
every day.
Well, good.
Don't stop.
[Pounding]
We've had some thefts
lately.
Took a quarter
of our medical supplies.
[Grunts]
Sorry. I --
No, no. It's, uh --
Henry forged it
during his apprenticeship.
Found it
wrapped among his things.
A gift intended for me
but never...
[Coughing]
You okay?
Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down.
[Coughs,
inhales deeply]
Uh-huh.
[Clears throat]
That doesn't sound good.
[Both chuckle]
It's nothing.
Just the regular
slings and arrows.
Uh-huh. Or smoke inhalation from
the fire might've triggered it.
Let me just --
I said I was fine.
Okay.
[Breathes shakily]
How long have you --
A month.
It's grown since then.
♪♪
Look.
It could be a lot of things,
yeah? Infection.
You know
you might've injured yourself.I know what it is.
Listen, without tests,
you can't be sure.
Siddiq,
I know what it is.
♪♪
Growing up,
my grandmother went through it,
then my father.
The pain, the coughing,
the swelling.
I watched them fight it
and win.
Did you know thyroid cancer
had a 98% survival rate?
Different times.
Times of sorcery
and witchcraft.
Chemo,
iodine radiation therapy,
thyroidectomies.
Now?
♪♪
Now we both know
what it means.
No,
you can manage it.
Acupuncture,
uh, hypnosis.
There's -- You --
♪♪
You know, I've been struggling
with my own condition...
[Exhales sharply]
...ever since the barn.
♪♪
That's why
I had to leave Alexandria.
I just --
I can't stand
how everyone looks to me
for some kinda...
♪♪
So, you know,
maybe we can't get away from it.
But we cantalk about it.
I mean,
what are we here for
if not for each other?
♪♪
Amelia:
It was just Milo and me.
We'd been walking
for days, weeks,
until the hissers
ran through our camp,
scattered everyone
to the winds.
After that, we went back
to what it was before,
what it always is
in the end --
Milo and me,
moving from place to place,
surviving.
I get it.
I've been there.
I better
stay on my feet.
Milo,
you wanna come on a walk?
Yeah.
[Coughs]
Be safe.
So, what are you
thinkin'?
We follow 'em,
see where they're hiding it?
Hiding what?
They've got a stash
somewhere,
probably
full of weapons, too.
It's a chick and a kid,
Brandon.
People are a resource.
Yeah. Not them.
[Sighs]
Alright, look.
I appreciate everything
you've done since Alexandria,
but it's only gonna get
more dangerous from here.
I think it's best
I go on alone
and you go home.
Okay.
It's just,
if I go back,
everyone's gonna wanna know
where I've been.
What am I
supposed to say?
I've never been
a great liar.
[Chuckles]
♪♪
New plan, then.
You go
wherever the hell you want.
You go back
to Alexandria,
you tell the whole world
exactly where I am.
You see,
I don't give a shit.
Just as long
as I don't have to see
that pasty, creepy-ass face
of yours ever again.
♪♪
You're just like
all the others.
♪♪
Careful, now.
Ears are the trickiest.
♪♪
You have something
for me?
I've been damming up the creek,
like you wanted.
I've just come back
for one more guardian.
A guardian taken
is another lost.
♪♪
Alpha: Patience.
Shifts in strategy
take time.
The creek,
the water, the tree --
it will crush them.
Or we could release
an army of thousands.
♪♪
Alpha: Go ahead.
Say your piece.
Instead of
these little nicks,
getting our guardians killed
at their walls,
why don't we...
cut the enemy down
all at once?
♪♪
Let us vote.
Anyone agree?
♪♪
[Chuckles lightly]
That's democracy
for you.
♪♪
[Groans]
The human body...
[Whimpers]
...is fragile.
All it takes
for it to collapse
is a few [Clicks tongue] nicks
in the right spots.
♪♪
[Groans]
Just like the enemy.
When their world collapses,
the smart ones will know
where to come to stay safe.
♪♪
We'll be waiting.
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
You said you wanted
another guardian.
[Birds chirping]
Negan: Oh, no!
We're gonna crash!
Ah.
Hey.
Don't worry, kid.
I don't bite.
Your mom,
she's inside, packin',
so we got a little bit of time
to kill.
Where'd Brandon go?
Brandon -- he went looking
for supplies.
You know what?
I'm gonna be real
with you.
Uh, I told Brandon
to get lost.
You see, uh,
it turns out,
not the best co-pilot,
if you catch my dri--
You don't catch my drift
at all, do ya?
You've never
been on a plane.
Aw, man, it's alright.
It's not your fault
that God turned this world
into an asspit
before you were born.
Alright.
Picture this, alright?
Sitting on a plane,
really nice, comfy seats,
but it feels like you've been
sitting on the runway
for Goddamn ever.
Suddenly,
there's this kinda rumbling,
a groan, alright?
The plane finally starts
to creep along, right,
and now we're moving
faster and faster.
And you look out
that window,
and everything's
turning into a blur.
And then, "Whew."
Wheels come up
off the ground.
You are flying.
It is like voodoo magic,
man, alright?
Up and up and up,
higher and higher,
until it feels like
you are floating
on top
of the frickin' world.
And you're looking out
that little window,
and you can see houses.
They look like little toy houses
and little toy cars.
[Sighing] Oh.
But the food?
Unh-unh. No way.
They served us something.
They called it beef stroganoff.
Let me tell you something.
It looked like baby shit.
And my Lucille [chuckles]
she wouldn't even touch it.
Ah, kid, there is so much
you're gonna miss
growing up
in this...screwed-up world.
You know, driving
your first set of wheels,
video games,
nut-tapping.
What, you've never heard
of nut-tapping?
Seriously? With big ol'
sausage fingers like those?
[Laughs]
Alright, man, the whole point
of nut-tapping --
catching the other guy
off guard, right,
embarrassing him,
getting even for him
calling your mom a slut
or whatever.
Wanna keep your wrist loose,
like this.
Lean in all casual like.
[Whistles]
And then -- thwack!
Snap your fingers
right on his nuts.
Now, you gotta remember,
you go low.
You go too high,
you get nothing but dick.
Alright, let's see
what you got.
You're a natural.
See, if nut-tapping
were a sport,
you wouldn't
have to 'roid up,
and you would still be
in the hall of fame.
[Laughs]
Ahh.
Alright, kid, dinner.
Not gonna happen
without fire.
Fire's not gonna happen
without wood.
Tell me something.
You get all packed up?
Yeah.
Hey, you know,
I know that moving sucks.
You know, it's like
I was telling your mom, though,
I know a place that I'm pretty
sure they're gonna take you in.
It's got really high walls,
farmland,
even has a mansion
sitting in the middle of it.
You just can't tell 'em
who brought ya, alright?
But I will get you
as close as I can.
One condition, though.
Keep those meaty fingers
holstered up
when my nuts are around.
[Chuckles] Okay.
Deal?
Yeah.
My man.
[Growling]
♪♪
[Water rushing]
[Growls]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[All growling]
[Screaming]
[Grunts]
I anoint you Gamma.
♪♪
[Grunts]
Oh!
[Groans softly]
Shit. Shit!
[Groans]
[Grunts]
[Rustling]
♪♪
It's okay.
That's for you.
I had it in my bag.
Take it.
It's okay.
My name is Aaron.
What --
That's right. You guys
don't do names anymore.
But you're from somewhere,
right?
I'm from Vermont.
Where --[Water sloshing]
♪♪
You're welcome!
[Dog barking]
♪♪
Hey.
[Whimpers]
♪♪
Hey.
[Bag rustles]
[Cap twisting]
♪♪
[Coughs]
We've gotta get her
back to Hilltop.
Nah, I think we gotta
find somewhere closer.
♪♪
Tell them what?
Did you know about this?
Hey.
What's she saying?
I said
I don't trust you.
What's your problem?
Huh?
Hilltop takes you in.
They got sick children
and mouths to feed,
and you steal from 'em?
All you're good for
is talking shit.
[Whistling in distance]
♪♪
[Whistling continues]
That's it, right?
[Thud]
You almost had me.
Back on the bus,
when you kicked me out.
♪♪
Then I remembered,
"This is Negan.
He's always messing with people,
keeping 'em in line."
So I realized
there's a test.
"It's gonna get a lot more
dangerous from here on out."
That's what you said
to me.
You wanted to make sure
that I had the balls
to do what had to be done.
♪♪
What do you think?
I passed, right?
I am Neg--
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Gate creaks]
[Gate closes]
♪♪
[Static]
Dante: I had to pop
a couple blisters.
Bill's still freaking out
about that rash.
What else?
I mean, the universe
is basically on pause
till God gets back.
♪♪
I'm assuming
your mic's out,
or else I'd hear you
laughing your balls off.
Nope, still here.
♪♪
How's Rosita?
She, uh, didn't want me
to tell you,
but she caught
a little bug.
She okay? Gabe back?
Not yet.
But she'll be fine.
♪♪
I'll leave for home
tonight.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
One other thing.
Is Carol around?
She's just outside.
Let me grab her.
[Chair scrapes,
footsteps depart]
♪♪
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Static]
♪♪
Hey, Carol.
Siddiq's on the radio for ya.
♪♪
[Breathes deeply]
[Footsteps approach]
♪♪
[Chair scrapes]
[Switch clicks, static stops]
♪♪
[Sighs]
You know,
it's scary to think, but...
Kelly probably
wouldn't have made it
if you guys hadn't have
found that stash.
Sounds like it was
pretty far off the main road.
Magna: Just say it.
You think I stole everything
and hid it out there.
Yeah, well, it wouldn't have
been the first time.
Then...
it would've been smart.
Yeah, or it would've been
a mis--
Selfish, stupid.
I was gonna say
a mistake.
No, but you were
thinking it.
For 13 years,
that's how you've looked at me.
That is not true.
Since the day
you showed up
in your -- your fancy suit,
with all your fancy --
Do you really wanna know
what I thought that day?
I thought, "Here is a person,
an innocent person
who's been locked up for a crime
they didn't commit,
someone who's never
trusted anybody
because no one's
ever trusted her,
someone who's good.
And, yeah, mad.
Mad at everyone.
Mad at the world
for being so messed up."
My cousin,
she was a little girl,
and he gets to go on
living his life?
No way.
But nobody came for him.
So Icame for him.
And there it is.
Now that
we've bothkilled --
how many people
have we killed, Miko?
And still,
that look right there.
I think you should find
another place to sleep.
♪♪
[Sighs]
The...man with the metal arm
gave it to me.
I don't know what that --
[Shushing]
Sit.
♪♪
We've all had to wear
different masks
at different times.
♪♪
Call it
a kinda sacrifice.
♪♪
Like your sister.
Your sacrifice was...
much greater.
The man
with the metal arm...
could prove useful.
♪♪
You might just
have to wear a newmask.
♪♪
[Horse grunts]
[Dog panting]
Uh, yeah.
Uh, Siddiq
has to go back.
Is, um...
Kelly okay?
Mm.
No, no, no.
I get it. Um...
Family.
Right?
Alright.
[Kickstand clanks]
[Engine starts]
[Whistles]
[Dog barks]
[Whistling]
♪♪
[Insects chirping]
Negan: Oh, you sorry,
rotten sacks of shit.
What's a fella gotta do
to get eaten around here?
What's the matter? Huh?
Y'all scared
of the Big Bad Wolf?
♪♪
Little pig, little pig!
[Rustling]
Uh-oh.
Let me in.
And there you are!
[Herd growling]
Oh, I am gonna huff.
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
I am gonna puff.
[Grunts]
[Chuckles]
I am gonna blow...
♪♪
...your...
[Growling continues]
...house...
[Grunts]
[Thud]
Ahh.
...all the way in.
[Grunts]
[Thud]
[Groans]
♪♪
[Panting]
Alright, you big-ass freak.
Let's do this.
♪♪