Man: Watch your ranks.
Watch your files.
Man: To the right.
And halt.
Drop.
Archers.
Retreat!
Right. And march.
Man: Archers, regroup.
-Formation.
-And halt.
Man: Spears.
Man: Thrust!
-And halt.
Woman: Open ranks.
Hold on, Jerry.
Jerry:
I'm tryin', boss.
Back up. Back up.
Michonne: It's about
to get real, y'all.
Everyone, steady.
Fan out!
Michonne: Hey,
stay in your formations!
Remember your trainin'!
On me.
Luke: Weirdest thing
you ever pulled outta
one of these ghost ships --
go.
Oh, that would
definitely be
the crate full
of hot-dog trophies.
Is that a euphemism?
What are you
talkin' 'bout?
No.
Literally trophies
shaped like dancing hot dogs.
-Okay.
-I mean, I guess they --
they sorta
looked euphemistic.
Okay.
Do you need help
with that?
Um, no --Look like you need
a strong woman
to help you with that --
among other things.
I mean, y-yes, please.
Thank you.
Hey, Jules, um...
a-are you --
Yes, I am flirting with you
a little bit, Luke.
Yes.
Good. That's cool.
As am I with you.
Oh. Well, thanks.
Training
was worth the trip.
Yeah, they did good.
Mm.
Tara would've been proud.
Hm. Hope so.
It's good
to bring the kids also,
let 'em see the ocean
for the first time.
Yeah, I know one idiot
that would've loved this.
Judith: ♪ 15 miles
on the Erie Canal ♪
♪ She's a good ol' worker
and a good ol' pal ♪
♪ 15 miles
on the Erie Canal ♪
It was a fun day at the river
today, huh, R.J.?
Yeah.
Let's see
what you found.
Kids found it
by the estuary.
River must've
carried it down.
Gabriel:
What does it mean?
Are they back?
We don't know.
But Alexandria should go
on lockdown just in case.
Hold on.
We don't have evidence
to justify that.
My official recommendation
is that everyone
should stay on alert
until further notice.
Eyes and ears open.
That's it.
Copy that.
Over and out.
Sounds good.
I appreciate your caution,
and I get it,
but we do not need
to start a panic.
A lot of stuff washed up ashore
from the recent storm.
Th-This might not
mean anything.
Or it might
mean something.
Look, no one saw
Alpha's herd move out,
so maybe no one saw them
move back in.
But if there's a mask,
maybe there are other signs
of them out there.
We owe it to our people
to be sure.
I'll gather a group.
We'll leave in five.
I'm-a hang back
for a bit.
I'll catch up.
Tell her not to leave again
without saying goodbye.
Alright.
Michonne:
Okay, let's split up.
You see any sign of them,
call it in.
Aaron: Michonne...
Yeah.
...are we
the good guys?
Why would you ask that?
I think about it a lot.
We're the villains
of someone else's story,
a threat
to their survival,
so dangerous they threaten
to wipe us out.
Makes you wonder
sometimes.
I don't give a shit
about the Whisperers
or where they stand.
I'm not just talkin'
'bout the Whisperers.
Anything?
Yumiko:
Nothing so far.
Luke: Nada over here.
You know, we may never
find an answer to this.
They cover their tracks.
If there's a mask,
there's a reason.
Come on.
Hey! Shit.
Whoa.
Watch their hands!
Damn it.
Duck!
Well, that was stupid.
We agreed not
to cross their borders
or to start anything
without a reason.
I lost Rick on a --
If it was them,
you could've died.
And it wasn't them,
and you could've died.
For what?
We've all been acting
like this is normal,
holding our breaths
for months.
This isn't normal.
We have to keep our cool,
or they win.
I've been keeping my cool
my whole life.
I've always been the nice guy,
the Good Samaritan.
But the thing is,
Eric is dead.
Jesus is dead.
And I'm Goddamn sick
of bein' nice.
Well, good,
'cause nice
never got me anywhere.
But smart did.
They have a nuclear weapon,
and we don't.
It's not about being nice
or good
or anything
but keeping our people alive
and not having them die
over nothing.
Believe me.
I hate this, too.
We should get back
before dark.
We didn't find anything.
We're circling back.
Yumiko: Hold on.
There's something
you all should see.
It's a campsite.
Couple people.
What am I missin'?
This is not what
we wanted to show you.
Luke: Campers must've
got into a fight
with these walkers,
right?
Or maybe the two things
aren't connected.
Looks like he's been here
for a while.
Aaron: A skin.
So at least one of 'em
has been
on our side of the border
at some point.
Yeah, but when?
And what the hell
happened here?
Michonne:
I can see what's coming
unless we stop it.
Fear is dangerous.
It can drive us apart
again.
And we're gonna
need to squash it
before it starts.
But fear
can also keep us safe.
I forgot that
on the bridge.
I was telling you
to be smart,
not afraid.
I've been thinking about
what you said earlier,
'bout who we've become,
who we are.
And the truth is,
we are the good guys.
And I know
who Rick and Carl were --
and Eric and Jesus, too.
We have to choose
to be the good guys
even when it's hard.
And...the minute
that we start
to question that
and we lose sight of it,
that's when the answer
to that question
starts to change,
and that's scarier
than any skin mask.
Judith: And the Brave Man
rode the horse very, very far,
trying to lead
the gigantic herd away.
But after a while,
the horse got scared
and ran away,
leaving the Brave Man
all alone.
So the Brave Man walked
all by himself to the bridge.
Remember how he built the bridge
for all his friends?
Yeah.
Well,
the millions of walkers
followed the Brave Man
onto the bridge,
and on the other side,
all his friends
were waiting.
The Brave Man
couldn't let the walkers
reach his friends
and hurt them,
so he blew up the bridge,
and all the walkers
fell into the water
and he saved
all his friends.
The end.
Did the Brave Man go to his
friend's house after that?
No.
He died
and went to heaven.
Will he come back someday,
like the walkers?
No, not like that.
But people,
like the Brave Man,
are never really gone
anyway.
He lives inside our hearts
and makes us brave, too.
Hey.
Is anybody gonna
say hi?
-Hi.
-Hi, Mom.
Michonne: Come on.
Hi. Ooh.
You, too, baby girl.
Come here.
I know, I know.
Mm.
Hi.
Mama, I didn't like it
when the Brave Man died.
Why did he do that?
Well...
there are some people
that you love so much
that you would do
anything for them,
just like I would do
anything for you
and for Judith.
And my dad?
Yes. And your dad.
Alright, bring it back in.
Come on.
-What is that?
-What is it?
Is that
a meteor shower?Michonne: Get back.
-I see it.
-Oh, I see it now.
Woman: What is that?
Michonne,
Eugene's on the radio.
He needs
to talk to you now.
Kids found it
by the estuary.
River must've
carried it down.
What does it mean?
Are they back?
Aaron: We don't know.
But Alexandria should go
on lockdown just in case.
Michonne: Hold on.
We don't have evidence
to justify that.
My official recommendation
is that everyone
should stay on alert
until further notice.
♪ That I hung on in there
♪ It must have been
the will of God ♪
♪ I do declare
♪ I'm so thankful
♪ That I hung on in there
♪ It must have been
the will of God ♪
♪ I do declare
♪ I'm so thankful
♪ That I hung on in there
♪ It must have been
the will of God ♪
♪ I do declare
♪ I'm so thankful
♪ That I hung on in there
♪ It must have been
the will of God ♪
♪ I do declare
Copy that.
Over and out.
♪ I was being used♪
♪ For a stepping stone♪
♪ That I could see♪
5 minutes and 16 seconds.
Not more, not less.
So if I were
to heat the milk up
for, like, 5 minutes
and 18 seconds --
I have rigged
the kitchen timer to go off
at precisely 5 and 16
so such a scenario
will not come to pass.
Furthermore,
I've taken the liberty
of chartin' her feedin's
and diaper changes.
She is very regular.
Congratulations.
Eugene, she's a baby,
not a science experiment.
You can't boil people down
to charts and graphs.
No, you know what?
I'll take it.
Might not use it all
or, like, any of it,
but thanks.
You know,
ever since everyone
got those damn
radio setups, Eugene,
this one's been doing
nothing but talking.
You gotta move that thing
outta the house.
Hey, man,
is everything okay?
Lydia:
"Yes, the girl said.
I have rec..."
"Received."
I've gone my whole life
without reading.
I don't see the point
in learning how to do it now.
It'll open
a whole new world for you.
And you're picking it up
so quick.
You're a natural.
There's nothin' natural
about this.
Gabriel:
We need the room.
Should she be here
for this?
Negan: Hey, kid.
Everything okay?
Fine.
Exactly the same as it was
20 minutes ago.
What was
the big meeting for?
And why are folks
givin' you the side eye?
Same folks eyein' you.
What have you done in the past
however many years
you've been here, huh?Brandon: Negan.
Get back to work, sir.
Hey, you're supposed
to keep your distance.
They're on alert.
Why?
Someone found a skin.
What does "alert" mean?
You've been here longer.
You tell me.
It means watch your back,
kid.
Hey, boss.
There you go.
Oh, hm?
Trippy, right?
Okay, you chill.
I'll be right back.
Dante: Jefe?
Earth to El Jefe.
There you are, Jef.
Dante.
What are you doing here?
Dude, your spawn was
screamin' bloody murder.
I could hear it
down in the infirmary.
I just --
Oh, shit.
I wanted to make sure
you were cool.
Hey.
So...
you cool?
Just, you know,
dealing with...
household pests
and shit.
Good thing I got to town
in time for you
to play house.
I reorganized the meds.
Infirmary's hummin'.
Might've earned my keep
for the day.
Though, who are we kiddin'?
We're like Gods
in the apocalypse.
By the way, this
yellow-alert bidness,
damn.
So what's with
this Whisperers thing?
You wanna get a room?
E-Excuse me?
The way
you're starin' at my mouth
is makin' me
warm and tingly inside.
Kiss me already.
Shit.
So tempting.
Yeah.
But, uh, I need
to get this kid to sleep.
So thank you
for checkin' on me.
Yeah.
Anytime, man.
Or should I say "God"?
I'm surprised you knocked off
work early.
I thought
you couldn't get enough
of the great outdoors.
It's starting.
Listen, if you've got
something to say,
can you just please
get to the point?
Because I don't
have time today.
Seriously.Aw, Gabey boy,
why don't you just
nestle in below me
and let me baby bird
a little bit of my wisdom
into that pretty little mouth
of yours?
You see, people tend
to get mixed up on
about who they hate.
Yesterday,
I was public enemy number one.
Now?
Well, now I'm the guy
that picks the vegetables
and takes out the trash.
I'm okay with that.
For now, at least.
But until
this whole thing passes,
I'm gonna keep my head down
so people don't move me
from the proverbial
semi-"us" category
to the category
of "them."
That's not
what's happening here.
I didn't say it is.
I said that it will.
You see, the boogeyman
just stuck his
gnarly skin-covered mask
out from behind
that closet door,
and people are puttin'
their shittin' pants back on
because pants-shittin'
is definitely happenin'.
Now, with this, uh,
alert shit,
all I'm seein'
is indecision.
Now, you ask me,
you gotta make 'em feel secure,
even if it's just
for show.
Sorta like
how you have a guy
followin' me around
with a spear all day
in case I suddenly decide
I'm gonna brain somebody
with a tomato.
So you're telling me
to lie?
That's your advice?
That's your regurgitated
bird wisdom?
No, not lie.
At most, I'm talkin' about
a little strategic omission,
maybe minor misleading.
Think of it as
using the truth to manipulate.
But, hell,
at the end of the day,
if that's what
keeps people alive,
what's the harm?
Lock the gates
for the night,
and let's double up security
at the walls.
Alexandria to Oceanside.
Come in, Oceanside.
Please, pick up.
Rachel:
Oceanside copies.
This is Rachel.This is Eugene.
I need
to speak with Michonne
and any of the community
leadership at O.S. right away.
Somethin' of grave importance
is about to happen.
Kids found it
by the estuary.
River must've
carried it down.
Gabriel:
What does it mean?
Are they back?
Woman: Pull!
Crap.
Heads up, Kel.
Woman: Go further!
That's further!
Heads up behind you,
Kel.
Watch your step.
Woman:
Alright, let it drop.
Sorry.
You ever wonder
why they call bird shit "guano"?
Nah.
I just call it
bird shit.
Yeah.
Me, too.
You know somethin',
when I worked in a zoo,
birds used to scare
the hell out of me.
Lions, tigers, no problem.
There's a kind of sense
to the way big cats operate.
But ostriches?
Those things'll disembowel you
for lookin' at 'em sideways.
You gotta eat more birds,
show 'em who's boss.
Wonder what seagull
tastes like.
Not chicken.
Hi. Hi, buddy. Hi.
Uh.
No, he just likes you
better.
Right?
Hi. Hi.
Good Dog.
Really?
Hey.
Carol.
It's good to see you.
You, too.
You look good.
Thanks.
Sorry. Um, excuse me.
Yeah.
Did ya miss me?
Not really.
I'll take that.
So, how was it
out there?
Work till you feel like
your back's gonna break,
then you work some more,
and at the end of the night,
you fall down and
sleep like the dead
on a deck
under the stars.
It's the best.
You find
what you were lookin' for?
Oh, then we sailed down south
to this dock
where Oceanside's been
pickin' up letters from Maggie.
Wasn't anything there.
Hasn't been for a while.
It's been a while
since I heard from ya.
I told you,
fishing's hard.
That's not what I mean.
You were lookin' for her,
weren't ya?
No.
Mm-hmm.
Honestly, no.
Tried to forget
everything that happened.
It was good.
And if we're lucky,
we'll never have to think about
those skin freaks
ever again.
What?
We found
one of their masks today.
Okay.
Michonne just took a group out
looking for signs of 'em.
You wanna go?
No.
I'm only -- I'm only here
till the next boat
heads out.
Alright.
So, what you wanna do?
Carol: Never been
through here before.
Daryl: Yeah,
we just cleared it out
to get around
the river border.
Faster.
Hang on.
I had that one.
Well, you're supposed
to call it.
You didn't call it.
Don't wanna play
with you anymore
if you cheat every time.
I'm not cheating.
Watch their hands.
Stop.
Why?
It's one of her borders.
They're walkers.
We can still get the deer.
No, it's too late.
Why are we still
respecting borders
we never agreed to
when Alpha
isn't even here?
Can we just forget
bout them already?It's too late.
That deer could've fed
200 people.
I'm sorry
I pissed you off.
I'm sorry you pissed me off,
too.
Well, there's no reason
to start shit if we don't gotta.
After the storm,
we all agreed to that.
That's why it's just as well
that I left.
Yeah, I've been
thinkin' about that.
Why don't
you come on home now?
I'm a sea dog, man.
Would you get off my ass
before I put you on yours?
Sorry if I didn't want
my best friend
to spend her whole life
on a boat.
Best friend?
What are you, 10?
Whatever.
Should we have
matching bracelets now?
Oh, God, forget it.
No, I could make some
with fisherman's twine.
Decorate 'em.
It'll be really cute
with tiny, little seashells.
Oh, my God.
I take it back.
No,
what's your favorite color?
Green? Blue?
Black.
Definitely black.
I got an idea.
Why don't we eat
and not talk?
Should we make
a matching collar for Dog?
Daryl?
Yeah?
You ever wonder
if this is all there is?
Just run into people,
kill each other
until whoever's left
says enough?
Sometimes
I think we're just survivin'
one fight to the next.
It was like that for you and me
before all this.
Yep.
There's got to be people
out there like us.
Right?
I get what Maggie's doin'
with Georgie.
I do.
Go out on the boat with me
this time.
Just run away together?
Be pirates. Heck yeah.
Nah.
Cooped up in those little cabins
all day?
That's not me.
Screw the boat.
We'll take your bike
and go out on the road.
Better.
Head out West.
New Mexico.
What the hell's
in New Mexico?
People
who weave bracelets.
No more fightin'.
Just get on the bike
and go,
see who's left.
Sounds good to me.
Magna: This is crazy.
We can't do this.We don't have a choice.
If we get caught on
their side of the border,
that's it, that's war.It's a fire.
Fires spread.
It could burn through
our hunting grounds.Or take out Oceanside.
Michonne,
are we doin' this?
-We gotta go now.
-Let's go. Come on.
We start on the outside,
push in.
It's gonna be
a long night, son.
A long, hot night.
Aaron: As soon as you clear
your area, move to the ends.
Keep digging.
We've gotta get this done
before the fire jumps spine.
-Come on.
- God damn it.
-Magna.
Yumiko: Magna.Magna: What?
You're spinning out.I'm fine.
No, you're not.
What's wrong?
Look around.
-Where we going? Where we going?
-To the fire line.
Grab your bucket.
Aaron: Alright,
everybody clear back.
Clear back.
We need to back-burn
the stray fuel
by the control line
so the fire can't spread.
Yumiko:
Let's light it up.
Yo, boss.
Not your boss, Jerry.
Pace yourself maybe.
It's gonna take a minute.
Fire was the beginning
of the end for the Kingdom.
We're not letting that happen
to Oceanside.
You okay, boss?
Let me take point
in this round, okay?
Cyndie:
I'm outta water.
Daryl: I'm out.
Man: Hey!
Walkers coming in!
Man: On your six!Daryl.
Bring the weapons.
Magna: Heads up!
Man:
Yeah, yeah, we're good.
Man: How many we got?
Woman: Come on!
Man: Let's stay on the fire.
Put it out.
Walkers!
There's too many!
Lead them to the fire!
Come on! Go, go!
Hurry!
Here!
Man: Watch your back!
There's too many of 'em!
Everyone, stay clear
of that tree!
It's gonna fall any minuto!
Get back.
Get outta here!
Michonne: Come on, come on.
Pack up and move.
Aaron:
Let's go, let's go!
Eugene, let's go.
I just need 20 minutes.You get zero.
We gotta go now.Ten. Just 10.
We should excavate and transport
this satellite to our vehicles.
I believe there may be
invaluable technological
implications for our communities
if I'm able to retrieve any of
the useful bits from inside.
I'm not askin'.
Oh, my God.
Yumiko, Luke, Magna,
everybody, come on.
We're helpin'
with the satellite.
Five minutes and out.
Hey, uh, Eugenius,
what about radiation, man?
Uh, there's radiation
all around us.
Certainly, there's radiation
from space,
but every one of us
is already infected
with some kinda nasty
that changes us into epidermis
Epicureans at point of R.I.P.
I mean, I don't understand
what you're talkin' about.I got it, man.
No one's gettin' superpowers
today. I'm on it.
Cuttin' into my 10 minutes.
Alright.
We made
the right choice.
Let's not push our luck.
Well, maybe this
buys us some goodwill.
This helps them, too.
We helped ourpeople.
That's enough good for me
for now.
Where are Carol
and Daryl?
You still wanna run away
together?
Yeah.
Tomorrow.
Look, I need you to stay.
Just think about it.
Otherwise, I'm gonna have to
punch holes in all them boats.