Look.
Open your eyes.
Siddiq: Cheryl?
Cheryl, here.
Drink.
♪ Call me back darlin'
♪ When you hear me
call your name ♪
♪ If I don't hear you,
I'll think somebody came ♪
♪ And if I can't find you,
I'll wait on down the hill ♪
♪ And if you don't find me,
I'll think you been killed ♪
I'll run on down the road ♪
♪ Find me the Sheriff,
tell him what I know ♪
♪ Find me the Preacher
and pray for your soul ♪
♪ No safe place, child
♪ We don't know why
♪ Come back, my baby
♪ Come back alive
♪ No safe place, child
♪ We don't know why
♪ Come back, my baby
♪ Come back alive
Come on.
Get out.
We need the cell.
You know him?
He's one that watches
the Guardians.
I mean,
the walkers.
So he knows
where your mother's horde is?
Probably.
You've put us all at risk.We have to find that horde
before it shows up
at our gates.
So you decide for all of us?
Knowing what it could mean?
Doesn't matter anymore.
We still gotta find them.
I'm gonna be
in there with you,
and Siddiq is gonna treat
his wounds first.
He bleeds
until he answers.
That's not your call.
None of this is.
You did what you did,
but I'm not gonna let it go
from bad to worse,
and I think the council
would agree.
Including Michonne.
Come on.
You can stay with me.
You can go on up.
Thanks for having my back
with Gabriel.
It's just the truth.
The Whisperer's not gonnagive it up easy.
If you wanna sit this out,I get it.
Whoa-ho-ho!
Down, boy.
Yeah, good boy.
Come on.
It's still yours.
This'll help
with the bruises.
I had worse.
Me, too.
The Whisperer, what else
do you know about him?
Only thathe won't betray my mom.
The ones that watch the horde
are loyal.
She gives them
no choice.
Neither will I.
What else?
People will die,
right?
I hate them.
But I know them, too.
Alpha drew a line,
and you need to choose
which side you're on.
I wish I'd left with Henrywhen he asked.
So do I.
My mom twists people.
Gets them to do
what she wants.
Makes them thinkit's what they want.
People obey 'cause they thinkthey have no other choice.
But if
you let him see...
what you have here,
that a place like thiscan survive...
An idea like that
is dangerous.
It would spread.
And there's nothing
my mom could do to stop it.
Don't try anything.
Never.
He's gonna
need stitches.
I know you.
Look.
Dante can take it
from here.
I'm fine.
Outside.
Now.
Look.
You have bread
every day.
Yeah.
Made fresh this morning.
Got some extra,
if you'd like.
How do your people
make so much?
With flour.
But...every day?
Seems like a lot of peopledoing just that.
As many as needed.
Oh.
From my daughter.
You have children?
Just the one.
About all I can handle.
And there are more?
There are.
Do you...?
Children hold you back.
Make you weak.
What about a family,
then?
Brothers or sisters?
I'm an only child.
Let's get started.
So,
what's it gonna be?
Honey or jam?
Strawberry or apple?
All of it.
Not a problem.
We have plenty here.
For lunch,
I was thinking salted fish.
I like to wrap 'em up
in a fresh piece of lettuce,
add a little --
What do you want?
Well, right now,
we're just gonna talk.
Pass.
Okay.
Then, eat.
Good?
No.
You okay?
Yeah.
Am I okay?
Yep.
Nice and pasty.
Still look good,
though.
Damn right.
I mean,
if it weren't for Gabriel,
I would be
making my move.
Don't let that
stop you.
Man doesn't havea jealous bone in him.
Oh, yeah?
Okay,
scoot over.
I've been thinking...
Mm-hmm.
...about Eugene.
Sorry.
It's your other
other man.
Yeah.
We set a date to talk,and I missed it.
I justdon't want him to think
that I was dissing him
or anything.
He'll be fine.
That guy,
he bounces back.
Not everybody does.
I did, uh, check out
a few of his baby tips.
The poop chart --
that shit was on point.
I mean, literally.
Eugene is
a bona fide shit-ologist.
We have a kid together,
Mami.
Yes, we do.
I didn't think I'd be a mamiin this world.
Try not
to think about it.
Freaks me out
every time.
I just...
wanna do it right.
Wanna be a good dad.
Freaks me outthat you're a dad, too.
Thanks.
No,she's lucky to have you.
We both are.
Here, sit up, sit up.
Okay?
Yeah.
You okay?
Just got
a lot of patients to see
and miles to go
before I sleep.
Okay, come on.
Where's the horde?
Tell me.
Lady,you have the animal in you.
If we were out there,
I would take youlike a bitch in heat.
Unh!
That's enough.
You're all weak.
Gonna start
with your fingers first.
Then both your ears.
Then we'll take
all your teeth.
You lie to yourselves.
To each other.
You fight for what?
Sandwiches?
You ignore the truth
when it's staring youin the face.
I would never
betray Alpha.
She rescued me.
She protects me.
She loves me.
She loves us all.
She sacrificedher own daughter for us.
She killed Lydia?
Oh.
She did.
And I am willing
to give my life
for her.
Stop.
This ends now.
You're not getting Lydia
mixed up in this.
He swallowed every ounceof Alpha's bullshit.
Every ounce.
If he seesthat Lydia's alive and well,
gets it that his great leader
lied to him,
then maybe
that changes something.Please.
That kid's
been through enough.
Let hermake up her own mind.
This is the only way,
and you know it.
That good, huh?
It's a little better
than last time, yeah.
Know how I know
a man's lying?
His lips are moving.
Cheryl,
you're gonna get through this.
Okay?
I'll make sure of it.
Sit down, Doc.
You look
worse than I do.
Close your peepers.
Rest.
Cheryl,
I can't -- I --
Ain't for me.
I made my peace.
But others...
need to haveyour head on straight.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
She's actually
a pretty good rider.
Mostly I think she just
uses it as an excuse
to stay out
with her friends.
Did you ever ride?
Sometimes.
Yeah,
I couldn't get enough.
Find every excuseto stay out as long as I could,
keep going, even if it was just
up and down our street.
As kids,
we'd always try
to take the long way homearound the lake.
Brother or sister?
I'm sorry.
I...
I had a brother.
Yeah, he was a couple years
younger than me.
He, uh...
He loved cars.
Only thing he loved
more than cars was people.
And...they loved him.
And I still think about him
every day.
You know,
I know what it's like
to lose someone
that you love that much,
and I know that it helps
to talk about it.
What you're doing...
these questions...
you know,
digging for intel...
I suppose I should be
doing the same,
but what's the point?
So maybe we just...
talk about nothing
worth reporting, you know?
You know, I can go on and on
about my brother,
and maybe you can --
We walk in darkness,we are free.
We bathe in blood,
we are free...
Whisperer: We walk in darkness,we are free.
We bathe in blood,
we are free...
Gabriel:
I don't know.
We came back,
and he was shaking in pain.
We walk in darkness...
Put your healin' hands on me,
Doc.
I'm burning up here.
What's the problem?
How the hell
should I know?!
Just make it stop!
I'm on this,
Jefe.
No. Come on.
All right,
his breathing's labored.
Pupils dilated,
his muscles are convulsing,
but no signs
of infection.
It doesn't make sense.
Hey, hey!
Easy!
Hold him!
Look, Dante, in my bag,grab the red bark!
Red bark!
Easy.
Hey, hey, easy.
Easy, easy.
Hey.
No, Carol.
This morning...
Did you
give this to him?
Yeah,
for pain and inflammation.
You killed him.
How?
No, that's yarrow.
It's hemlock.
I -- I didn't know.
I thought, uh --
What?
You thought what?
I never thought hemlock would bein the bag because, um...
Because what,
Dante?
Because you packed it.
One less Guardian
for our horde.
The man
with the metal arm?
Aaron.
He has a daughter.
Is that
all you've learned?
Did you ask...
after your sister's child?
There is nothing
to ask.
He is one of them.
He will slaughter
our kind.
He will search out
your weaknesses.
He will use your sisteragainst you.
Remove your mask.
We are always
being tested.
We must remain strong.
I believe in you.
Never doubt that.
You are my Gamma.
Tell me.
This Aaron...
he tempts you
with his lies.
Do not be seduced.
Gabriel: If people find out,they'll panic.
If Alpha finds out...
She won't.
I'll clean up
the mess.
I'll help.
'Cause it's not your messto clean.
Lydia: We're not going hunting,are we?
You still wanna help?
Yeah.
Good.
Cheryl?
Hey.
I was gonna come try to find youbut, uh...
Siddiq: Cheryl, you're gonna get through this.
It's hemlock. I'll make sure of it.
You killed him.
Open your eyes.
Look.
Enid!
I heard
what happened.
Don't want
to talk about it.
Go home.
You should be in bed.
No.
Start
or we go back in.
Drown together.
There's nothing to say.
He died
because of my --
Unh-unh.
No,I want the real shit.
Whatever's been eating you up
for weeks -- spill.
It's like
I'm still there...
all the time.
It's like
I never left.
But it's just pieces.
And they're all
jumbled together
like a puzzle
or something.
The screams and...
the smell...
the blood,
everything...
I can't get it
to stop.
People are dying.
Cheryl is already --
Cheryl was sick.
You're doing
everything you can.
You're not alone.
You mean Dante?
Do you know why
he bothers me so much?
Enid.
'Cause when he's there...
I just think about
how much I miss her.
But then, I get to remember
how I failed her, so...
No.
No,this isn't your fault.
What that skin bitch didain't on you.
You weren't there.
Okay? You...
Enid, Tara, the...
People that I love
died right in front of me.
And now I get to watch it
over and over and over.
And I did nothing.
I did nothing!
I just --
I didn't move.
I didn't help.
I just watched.
Now, because of me,
more people...
Look, I'm just --
I'm not smart enough.
Bullshit.
You have to
pull through.
You have to fight it.
For Coco.
Me.
And everyone else
that loves you.
And you can.
You will.
Because you're not alone.
And you're the smartest personI know.
Except me, of course.
I still can't figure out
why you're sick.
The patients,
you don't live together,
you don't work together,
you don't even eat
the same things.
There's not
a common denominator.
At least not one
that I can...
What?
Nothing.
Go home, okay?
Go home.
Yaah!
No, no.
It's --
That's yours now.
A gift.
I don't want anythingfrom you.
Take it
or I'll burn it.
All right.
No more games.
I ask questions,and you answer, got it?
Don't do this.
This isn't you.
You...
have no idea
who I am.
Now, how many peopledo you have?
Let him go.
No.
Your mother told her people
that she killed you.
You said
you wanted my help.
I did.
You used me.
Lydia, I'm sorry.
You're just like her.
Lydia...
You said you wanted me
to choose a side?
I choose mine.
You can't go out there.
It's too dangerous.
You can't stop me.
Unh! Aah.
Aaron: Wait.
They could be watching.
Dante: Hey.
I know it's late,
but I saw the light on --
Leave me alone.
Just wanna chat
for sec, Jef.
I am not your jef.
Sure you are, Chief.
Mm.
I'll go, but...
not before
saying sorry.
With Eugene gone,
I gotta...
pitch in
with the water.
I haven't
pulled my weight.
Stop.
This is my fault.
It's not yours.
It is not
anyone else's.
Yeah.
I know
you want this blame.
For a sec, everything else
makes sense, right?
Well, I'm sorry, bro --
ain't how it works.
Look,
this place is special.
And I got that
right away.
It -- It works
'cause it's a village.
It takes everyone here
to build, grow, and fight,
raise rug rats
and heal people.
Everyone carries
equal weight.
So, when something happens,
it's all our fault, yeah?
And when one of us
is suffering...
we're here to help.
You don't even
know me, man.
Sure do.
You're my friend.
It's gonna be okay.
Yeah.
Look.
Enid!
Open your eyes.
N-o-o-o!
Get off!
I didn't want this!
Not you!
Not like this.
Close your eyes.