Open.
No!
Aah!
Mama!
Hurry, Mama!
Mama, hurry!
Mama!
I'm so sorry, Mama.
You almost got us killed
again.
Mama, there's a man.
It is time that
the pack returns.
There is more gathering to be done,
Guardians to be found.
We are far from the enemy.
Their fear will subside.
They will fear us no matter where we are.
They fill fear us because of what we did.
Do you doubt me?
Our mission?
Never.
Take the sisters
when you depart.
They have a real gift, a scent for the dead.
We don't mean harm.
Can you talk?
Mama, I don't like this.
Please...
Go on and try to kill us.
But know two things -- One, I do not die easily,
and, two, you must also kill my daughter
because I will not leave this Earth without her.
One night.
Thank you.
Do not leave this hallway.
Do you think
I could wash up?
Sorry, Mama,
but the smell... Is there water?
Is he a monster?
We're all monsters now.
Beta: Be on alert.
Buildings could be full.
Male Whisperer #1:
Gather all of them?
Every last one
we can find.
Split up. We track better apart.
Did you hear me?
He's watching you.
Frances: The sun feels...
different today.
Can you feel that,
sister?
Like it's burning
right into our skin.
Stop it. Your head's in the clouds again.
He'll see that you're not committed to the cause...
to her.
Don't say that.
I should've left you behind when I had the chance.
I hear them.
Over there.
Shh.
Were you singing?
Wouldn't call it that.
Don't do it again.
You have a name?
The dead
don't have names.
And we shouldn't,
either.
Without names or a past,
those of us strong enough
to still be alive out here
can know each other
on a primal level.
They fear nothing.
They want only to feed.
They are free.
How'd you end up
in here?
Got into a tussle
with the dead,
ran me out of my camp a few months ago.
Is that why
you wear that?
Lydia: Mama, come back!
I like it...
...the sound
of the dead.
It's the only song I never want to end.
Sister, focus.
What is wrong with you?
You will pay.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel...
he's better there.
I love him, and he's gone.
He's with them
in a better place!
Alpha: Stop!
Beta: She is an uncommitted now.
Her actions threatened
the entire pack.
Leaving her child
broke her.
You will never understand how it feels to abandon your child.
You still think
of Lydia.
She was dead to me
long before I ended her.
Bring her to me
in the deeper place.
I'll be waiting.
You're gonna sleep
in here.
I'll be right outside.
It'll be quiet.
Why are there big pillows
all over the walls?
So the people put in here wouldn't hurt themselves.
People like that man out there?
These walls could never control someone like that.
You like him?
Uh-huh.
I don't want it.
You've never slept
without her --
I don't want it.
I'm not a baby anymore.
I don't want
that stupid bunny.
to be scared.
I want to be more like you,
Mama.
I've waited so long
to hear that.
And I hope
that you will...
because if you can't,
I'll have no choice but to leave you behind.
Please, Mama,
don't ever leave me.
I promise I'll do better
out there. I will.
You'll see.
I love you, Mama.
Stop calling me that.
Alpha, I'm sorry.
Please.
I won't talk about him
again.
Please.
Remove your mask.
Kneel.
Shh.
Thank you.
Alpha showed you
her grace?
I'll never stray again,
sister.
We keep thinking about
that place, too.
It looked so safe.
There was livestock.
We can all go back.
We can get --
Why?
Do not question me.
But if she strays again, I will skin her alive for all to see.
She unsettles the pack.
Then we keep a close eye, make sure her moment of weakness doesn't infect the others.
The others have already spoken of the enemy, the life they saw.
It is not a life.
It is a fantasy.
And the pack
must learn that again.
They must see it
up close.
They will.
When?
Soon.
Are you content?
I have seen you wander away
from the camp alone at night.
I am right here...
as I've always been.
I like killing
with you.
Oh, you're different.
People who knew me
before all this
would probably say
the same thing.
Never trusted
those people, anyway.
I don't hardly
trust anyone.
Neither do I.
Well done, Big Man.
"Big Man"?
Okay.
"Mr. B."
I thought we didn't have names.
It's not a name.
It's a letter.
So, if I'm "B," what does that make you?
"A."
So, you can move with them when you're covered?
It's not just about
moving with them.
You got to become them,
feel what they feel.
And what do they feel?
Nothing.
There are only two kinds of people left in this world --
the ones brave enough
to walk with the dead
and everybody else.
So, tell me, B,
which one are you?
Leave.
At sunrise.
Don't come back.
What was it like,
To be alone with her?
Just as you'd imagine.
She's powerful,
so calm.
My head finally feels right again.
So, you are no longer
thinking of him?
I'm glad I made that sacrifice.
As Alpha sacrificed
her daughter.
She said when she watched her die,
she didn't shed one tear.
She is Alpha.
She doesn't cry.
I'm so sorry...
for risking
what we have here.
I know.
Don't do it again...
ever.
Did you mean what you said before,
you wish you'd left me behind?
Go to sleep, sis.
Alpha: Pull them back.
Beta: Steady.
Do not break.
There's too many.
Stay the course.
I want them.
Bring him.
You brought a baby
out here?
No!
Aah!
Do you regret
what you did?
She was an uncommitted.
She no longer
belonged with us.
I had to protect
the Alpha.
And you did.
It was your destiny.
As the lion who smothers
her wailing cub,
we're strongest
when we kill our own blood.
It is the purest,
most honest way
to bring order to chaos.
Your purity
will never be forgotten.
Yes, Alpha.
I see greatness in you.
There's a tear.
Should I repair it?
Beta: Leave us.
Are you hurt?
I never felt more calm.
Calm?
We lost three of our own, and many more of the dead,
and you are calm?
It was mayhem.
There is clarity
amid the chaos.
She fears nothing.
Hmm.
Lydia:
We're all monsters now.
We're all...monsters now.
For your bravery
and sacrifice
and for putting the needs
of the pack above your own,
I anoint you Gamma.
To Gamma.
All: To Gamma.
To Gamma. To Gamma.
To Gamma.
You've been gone
for hours.
Are you angry with me?
I feel nothing for you.
I am also empty,
as Alpha wants.
Where is she?
I saw her moving toward the old camp a while ago.
Lydia:
We're all monsters now.
We're all...monsters...now.
Alpha: Lydia?
Lydia?
Have you
lost your way?
Have you?
I told you never to come over here.
I-I need to
find my daughter.
I don't care.
You kept that?
This is for Lydia.
You said she was dead, that you killed her.
You want her back.
You shouldn't have
come here.
Why?
Why did you lie to me?
She is never coming back,
no matter how much
you wish for it
or how hard you try to
replace her with someone else.
She is gone, Alpha!
No!
She's my daughter.
She's my baby.
I could not kill her.
They can't know.
They cannot know
Lydia's alive.
They cannot know.
They won't.
Lydia is dead.
Lydia is dead to me.
She was dead the moment she was born...
'cause she was not
like me.
Because she was not like me. Because she was not like me.
She was not like me.
She was not like me!
She was not...like...me!
She was not like me!!
I know you better
than you know yourself.
You've got demons,
yeah, just like me.
But you are not broken!
You were made for this.
Aah!
No! Stop! No!
She's trying to save you!
My baby.
Mama, I was strong. You were, baby.
And I'm so proud
of you.
But don't you dare, dare ever leave me again!
You hear me?!
The world, it went dark
so that we could
see a new path.
So come.
Come on.
Walk with me
in the darkness.
Walk with me,
and you will never
be alone again.
My "B."
I am the end
of the world.
I am the end of the world.
I am the end
of the world.
We are the end
Come with us.
I can't leave him.
You won't have to.
I saw smoke
by the border.
The enemy
may have crossed.
We must teach them
a lesson.
And the pack will watch.
We're going back.
Both:
We walk in darkness.
We are free.
We bathe in blood.
We love nothing.
We are free.
We fear nothing.
We need no words.
We are free.
We embrace all death.
This is the end of the world.
Now is the end of the world.
We are the end of the world.