[Flies buzzing]
♪♪
[Hatch door clanks]
[Match strikes]
♪♪
[Lantern squeaking]
[Fussing]
Rosita:
It's your turn.
Gabriel: [Groans]
[Yawns]
[Grunts]
Hi.
Aw.
Okay, okay, okay.
[Fussing continues]
[Crying]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
No!
[Gasps, breathing heavily]
Gabriel:
Rosita, do you copy?
♪♪
[Mask splats]
[Sighs]
I'm the one
that knows Aaron.
We know who you are.
♪♪
The people you sent out,
they're in trouble,
trapped in a cave where Alpha
has placed her horde.
Now, they could still
be in there
or they might've
gotten out.
I don't know.
You said the horde
was in a field.
It was.
Now it's in a cave.
She moved it.
The whole thing.
Right before
they got there.
[Sighs]
♪♪
I'm just telling you
what happened.
I'm not sure you are.
♪♪
I'm trying to help.
Why?
♪♪
[Sighs]
The baby that they left
at Hilltop,
he's my nephew.
♪♪
And I would do anything
to see him again.
Where's the baby's mother?
♪♪
Dead.
If I give you a map,
can you show us
where the cave is?
♪♪
Yes.
[Grunts]
You're a liar.
The cell.
♪♪
[Growling]
[Clank]
It's from
the last one.
The last Whisperer
we had in here.
You killed him?
Gabriel: No.
I did.
Rosita: It was the oneyour people sent to spy on us.
He killed my baby's fathertwo days ago.
[Sighs]
I don't know anything
about that.
Right.
Never heard of him.
I haven't.
Mm.
I don't -- uh...
[Sighs]
It's amazing how much you say
you don't know.
Let me lay it out
for you.
You're gonna work very hard
in this room.
You're gonna have to
convince us
that you're different
from the ones who lie
and walk with the dead
and eat worms.
And what if I can't?
Then you die.
No torture.
No games.
No second chances.
You'd be the third one,by the way.
All's I've doneis tell you the truth.
Gabriel:
You haven't.
This is not for show.
I am
a servant of God.
I've taken
many confessions,
and I can tell when people
are holding things back.
Rosita: Holding things backis the same as lying.
Outside at the gate,
the story you had about being
the aunt of the baby...
It's not a story.
...it does tug
at all the right heartstrings,
but you're
hiding something,
which makes the whole thing
a lie.
Ask God if I'm lying.
I've spoken to God.
He told me
to hang you.
I, uh...
[Voice breaking]
I killed my sister.
♪♪
I killed...
I killed her for Alpha.
She didn't even have to ask.
I just did it.
♪♪
You believe me now,
Father?
♪♪
Then you should get me
a map.
♪♪
[Horde growling]
[Grunts]
[Screaming]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunts, coughing]
Aah!
Where are they?!
[Screams]
Tell me!
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
Gabriel: So,14 miles inland here?
Yes.
Scott: Any other way
in or out?
There are others
in the area.
I'm not sure where.
And they'll be guarded.
Did Earl send
those new weapon sets?
Yeah.Enough for all of us.
Good.
We're gonna need them.
What about the border?
It's gonna be guarded
all the way down to --
It's clear.
It's too long
for Alpha to defend.
Most of the patrols
will be near the cave.
♪♪
Take her back
to her cell.
♪♪
[Door opens, closes]
So,
two rescue parties.
Rosita and Iwill take the first --
We don't know
if any of this is real.
Don't we?
You said you were sure
she wasn't lying.
I am,
and she isn't.
♪♪
You all
are hesitating
because you're afraid of them,right?
You shouldn't be.
That's why I brought herin here.
So you could see.Laura: See what?
That they're cowards.
We broke her.
Completely.
And if we can break her,we can break others.
If you come across one of them,keep them alive,
start pulling teeth
and taking fingers.
Get information,
because we now know
the more pain and fearyou pour over them,
the sooner
they drop the act,
which is
what it is.
♪♪
[Breathing shakily]
[Flies buzzing]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
[Clink]
[Footsteps approach]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
[Clanking]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Lid creaks]
[Footsteps approach]
You okay?
You seemed a little offin the meeting room.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Look,why don't you stay here
and look over the defenses
at the gate?
[Scoffs]
Smart thing
would be having me out there.
I don't think it is.
I'm not gonna freeze.
I'm good.
But you need to worry
about your shit.
What is that
supposed to mean?Means you're erratic.
Name one thing I've donethat's been erratic."Cut off their fingers.
Pull out their teeth."
You're itching
for a fight.
So what if I am?
[Sighs]
♪♪
I can feel
that Coco is...
♪♪
...wondering where he is.
And I don't want her --
I know.
♪♪
Right.
I'll see you out there.
You don't have to --I'll see you
out there.
♪♪
Judith: I'll make it
really fast.
I'll be right back.
What's your name?
Nobody's asked me
since I got here.
It's Mary.
What were you like
before the Whisperers?
I'm from Santa Monica.
That was
in California.
My parents' nameswere John and Alice.
I went to school and...
♪♪
I don't remember.
What do you mean?
♪♪
Alpha has a way
of, um...
making you forget.
You really don't
remember anything?
♪♪
There are echoes left,feelings.
I was ordinary.
That much I know.
And when
it all went down,
my sister and Ikept making bad decisions.
We needed someoneto make them for us,
and then we met Alpha.
♪♪
You met
the wrong person first.
If you'd met
my mom or my dad,
you wouldn't be
in that cell.
♪♪
You don't look like
a monster to me.
[Footsteps approach]
Rosita: Judith.
♪♪
We're about
to go on lockdown.
You should get inside.
♪♪
Bye.
[Shotgun clanking]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Breathing rapidly]
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Aah!
[Panting]
♪♪
How many can you see
in the herd?Man: 100 at least.
It's hard to tell,
but it looks like
there are Whisperers in it.
It's on its way.
What should we --
Echo post, say again.We lost you.
[Static]Echo post, respond.
[Static]
That watch tower's
two miles away.
We can't let this next wave
bunch up at the gate
the way
the last one did.
Why would they
send a herd now?
We have a defector
giving us information.
They're trying to stop us
before we act on it.
We're gonna have to split up
if we want to cover both gates.
Scott: That means less peopleout there.
We don't have a choice.
Show of hands --
how many people here
have been on gate duty?
Man:
I have.
Alright,
how many do we need?
Need or want?
Six, plus you, me,
Rosita, and Gabe.
Alright, you seven,
you're gonna be
on the main gate.
Hold on. New plan.
Rosita and Laura,
stay back on gate securitywith a skeleton crew.
You and I take a squadout to the outpost,
break up the herd,and then move on to the cave.
Good?
Yeah. Yeah.
[Indistinct conversations]
Gonna grab that.
I didn't want --I'm not trying to speak for you.No, it's fine.
I don't trust myself
out there anyway.
Could get us both killed,
and then Coco would...
It's okay.
I'm having nightmares
about them.
Dreams they're killing me.
Scott:
We're good to go.
♪♪
I'll see you soon.
[Crickets chirping]
♪♪
All I'm saying is
we could make it into a game.
I kill
more skins than you,
you take my watch duties
for a month.
I don't wanna mess aroundout there, man.
Aw. [Chuckles]
What, are you scared?
Remember Lydia?
My friends and I
beat the shit out of her.
She barely
put up a fight.
I'm telling you, man,
one on one,
the Whisperers
are a joke.
♪♪
[Indistinct conversations,
laughter]
♪♪
[Grunts, clatter]
[Indistinct shouting]
♪♪
[Woman screams]
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
[Indistinct conversations]
Man:
This don't make sense.
What the hell happened?
We'll go back
the way we came.
You don't see
anything coming?
No, nothing.
No sign of a herd.
No walkers.
What the hell
is going on?
[Breathes deeply]
♪♪
[Growling]
They were forced
to call.
Must've held the knife
to her throat
to make him call us
and lie.
Why?
Most of us
are out here.
There's hardly anybody...
back home.
[Growling]
♪♪
Walkers!
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
They're here.
Check Morgan Street.
Come with me.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunt, body thuds]
This place --it isn't what she said it was.
She lied.
♪♪
These are not
your people.
But she lied.
She is your Alpha.
♪♪
You think
you're still alive.
♪♪
You were dead
the moment you came to us.
♪♪
Step towards me.
Why?
She wants you.
She said your death
would be painless.
If you fight,
it will not be.
Step towards me.
♪♪
[Sighs]
All she wants
is me in pain.
♪♪
You're lying for her.
Step towards me.
♪♪
I am not afraid
of you.
Yes, you are.
♪♪
Get help.
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
♪♪
Help!
Judith: In here.
♪♪
[Door creaks]
[Doorknob rattles]
[Gunshot]
♪♪
[Doorknob clicks, door creaks]
Okay, go, go.
Fast, fast.
♪♪
[Door opens in distance, closes]
Aah!
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
[Footsteps]
Hey!
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Items clattering]
♪♪
[Coughing]
Mary: Stop!
♪♪
[Panting]
Alpha wants me alive.
♪♪
Step towards me.
[Crickets chirping]
You will fall.
You will rise.
You will walkwith your sister again.
♪♪
[Gun cocks]
No, I wasn't...
I-I didn't...
I didn't betray you.
I just -- I-I drew him out here
because he was gonna...
[Breathing heavily]
Please.
♪♪
I'm telling the truth.
[Breathing heavily]
Can you see
beyond the darkness
into the light?
No.
[Exhales slowly]
I'm tingling
with joy...
as I see the ones
who broke me...
all around us,
standing there.
[Heavy breathing
continues]
Thank you.
Thank you
for making me strong.
Pain made me.
Pain made you.
Pain made my Lydia.
You lost her.
[Breathing heavily]
You drove her away.
'Cause you didn't
love her.
What did you say?
[Wheezing]
What did you say,
boy?
I can't hear you.
I'm all ears.
♪♪
Are you really here?
[Voice breaking]
Yes, Mama.
Don't call me that.
You know better.
♪♪
You came home.
I am you,
and you are me.
♪♪
[Crying]
[Breathes deeply]
♪ Lydia
♪ Oh, Lydia
♪ Say,
have you met Lydia ♪
♪ Lydia the tattooed lady
♪ She has eyes
♪ That folks adore so
♪ And a torso
♪ Even more so
♪ Lydia
♪ Oh, Lydia
♪♪
Mama, I --
Oh, Lydia.
Mama.
Lydia, baby, push.
[Crying] Mama.
Push.
I --
You're ready,
baby.
I made sure
you're ready.
[Crying]
♪♪
They're waiting
for you to lead.
They're waiting.
♪♪
I'm not here
for them.
for you.
♪♪
They're human.
Not perfect.
Just human.
♪♪
It's all
I ever wanted.
It's what
you never gave me.
♪♪
I need you.
I want you to...
stay.
[Birds chirping]
♪♪
[Breathing shakily]
[Wincing, exhaling sharply]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Laughs]
This was Dante.
Scouts in the tunnels
are saying
the Whisperers sealed
whole sections off.
Aaron.
♪♪
You're alright.
Yeah. We, uh...
What happened?
Aaron,where are the others?
We got separated.
Most of us got out.
Most of you?
♪♪
Not everyone.
You sureyou don't want her with you?
It's a short trip.
No, I'll be back as soon asthe doctor at Hilltop clears me.
Besides,
they could still be out there.
I want her safe,
and safe is with you.
Okay.
[Indistinct conversations]
Room for three more!
[Grunts]
I'm Rosita.
Mary.
I know.
[Door closes]
[Horses whinny]
Easy, easy.
Daryl:
[Breathing heavily]
How long
I been asleep for?
Most of the day.
And you were just
out here?
Yeah.
Just watching you.
Watching them.
Deciding.
Deciding what?
Did you kill her?
If it was your father,
could you have?
♪♪
I'm no longer weak.
I'm stronger than ever.
Our horde will butcher
and consume them.
Screams will be song
to me.
[Breathes deeply]
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
We bathe in blood.
We are free.
We love no one.
We fear nothing.
We are free.
This is the end of the world.
Now is the end of the world.
We are the end of the world.
♪♪