[Indistinct conversations
in distance]
[Footsteps approach]
♪♪
Shit.
[Keys jingle]
[Door opens]
[Door creaks]
♪♪
Well,as I live and breathe.
[Door closes]
I figured
you'd be Gabey,
coming downto give me my last rites.
You want forgiveness?
♪♪
I done what I done.
I ain't getting on my kneesabout it.
So what do you want?
A T-bone, beer,
maybe a scoop
of rocky road.
Matters to you
what I want?
What if
you didn't have to die?
♪♪
Didn't know
you had a say
on the kangaroo councildeciding my fate.
I'm not here
for the council.
I'm getting that.
What I don't get
is coming down here
and dealing with me
when, seems to me,
you oughta be lining upthe ol' Skin Queen
in your crosshairs.
♪♪
What do you think
this is?
♪♪
Damn.
The stones on you...
So you in or out?
Word has it you area certified bad-ass.
But you missed
your shot.
What happens
if I muff it, too?
Could make things a helluva lotworse for every man,
woman, and child
behind these walls.
And despitewhat people may think of me,
I am absolutely
not down with that.
♪♪
I need this done.
And that'll help every man,
woman, and child here.
♪♪
And what do
I get out of it?
You've been eating
whatever shit
we throw your way,
hoping that one day,
they'll all forget.
But they won't.
♪♪
Not unless you do something
to make them forget.
♪♪
So you bring me
Alpha's head,
and that's what the people
will remember you for.
I'll make sure
of it.
[Sighs]
♪♪
I have your word?
If you do it fast.
[Growling]
♪♪
Negan: Is this
what you wanted?
♪♪
[Growling continues]
All right.
What do you,
uh...
what do you say
we get movin'?
♪♪
Alexandria.
Our deal.
Let's start
spreading the news.
♪♪
What took you
so damn long?
What took me
so long?
Doing your dirty work?
[Scoffs]
I don't know.
I guessI wanted to get out of there
with my head
still attached.
Shit like that
takes time.
I told you
to do it fast.
It's done.
All right?
I held up my end.
Now I am asking you
to hold up yours.
Just walk me
through those gates
so I can open up a new chapterin the Book of Negan.
♪♪
I'm not going back.
Not yet.
I go back there
without you,
there is a noose
around my neck
the secondI step foot in there.
Then wait.
Wait?
How long
are we talking about?
You're free now,
Negan.
Do whatever the hellyou want.
Wait, don't wait,
it's up to you.
I need to be alone.
Shit like that
takes time.
♪♪
Jerry:
The kids are good.
All of 'em.
We got lucky.
Yeah,
I'll take it.
That doesn't absolve me
from failing.
Take it easy
on yourself, Boss.
These days, the mistakes
seem to stick harder
than the triumphs.
[Baby fussing, door opens]
Hey.
Hi.
♪♪
Oh. [Chuckles]
Oh, no.
Careful.
Hey.
You're alive.
Where --
H-How did you...?
I'm so sorry, Magna.I...
Did you need anything?
Did you --
No, no, no.
I-I'm okay.
I'm okay.
[Winces]
[Groans]
Oof.
♪♪
How're you feeling?
Great.
♪♪
I can bring you
to see Alex.
When we find Alex.
Mnh-mnh.
Someone else
can do that.
You gotta go.
Dammit, Eugene.
Tell them already.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Uh...
Uh, excuse me.
Can I have your kind attention,
please?
Um...
I have some things I -- I need
to 'fess and request.
Um...[Sighs]
I've been
in radio communicado
with someone
outside our orbit.
A new person.
And we set up a time
to meet.
Yumiko: What?
Who is it?
Her name
is Stephanie and --
Wait.Is this another community?
Jerry:
Where is it? What --
What'd you tell her
about us?
And now
you're going to meet her.
She could be another spyjust like Dante.
♪♪
Uh...
Eugene, how long have you been
keeping this from us?
I have some of
the same questions.
♪♪
But if Eugene's instincts
are that this...
Stephanie...
may be a new ally,
then let's hear him out
before we jump to conclusions.
♪♪
We're all on
the same side here.
♪♪
Now, some of you
are well aware
that I relocated
to Hilltop, uh,
in pursuit of
a metaphorical fresh start.
♪♪
Uh...
I struggled for awhile.
I buried myself in work
and community duties, and...
and that work manifested
a voice from the void.
And...
she became a friend.
Some of you might claim
that I'm foolish
to believe in future friends
and new alliances, but...
after everything
we just lost,
I'm willing
to be the fool.
I simply askthat you spare me your derision,
as a hopeful expectation
of new, good people
is wholly worth
the risk.
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Indistinct conversation]
You can take
my horse.
For what?
You should
go with them.
You never wanted
to be cooped up.
You could get back out
on the road,
have an adventure.
Look forward,
not back.
I like it here.
♪♪
I think some routinecould be good for me.
Yeah?
[Chuckles]
Okay.
But someone elseshould have the adventure.
Meet the new people.
♪♪
It's okay, Miko.
It'd be leaving
at the worst time. I...
♪♪
There's nothing
for you to fix.
♪♪
Go.
[Sighs]
♪♪
Hey, buddy.
Hey, play with your sister,okay?
♪♪
Jerry.
You're really going?
♪♪
Yeah.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Because I'm sick?
♪♪
Because I'm gonna
miss you.
♪♪
But can't stop a manwilling to be foolish, right?
Or a fool willing to believe
in future friends.
Is that all it is?
It's enough for now.
♪♪
The Kingdom needs you.
Make sure
our legacy lives on.
♪♪
You got it, Bo--
Ezekiel.
♪♪
[Growling]
She was with Negan.
Did he...
♪♪
You...
You are
the Alpha now.
[Growling continues]
What did you say?
I...
She can hear you.
[Growling continues]
Take off your mask.
♪♪
Can you hear her?
Are you listening?
Yeah.
What is she saying
to you?
I don't know.
I --
Move closer.
I-I don't know...
Shh.
Just listen.
♪♪
What is she saying
to you?
[Whimpers] Aah!
♪♪
Shh.
Just listen.
[Groans]
I-I-I can hear!
I can hear!
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
[Wood creaking]
Hey, kiddo.
Sorry ab--
Shit.
[Grunts] God!
Where's Alpha?!
Look,whatever Lydia told you --
Where is she?!
She is dead.
I killed her.
You liar.
I am not lying.
I have somethin'
in my pocket.
It's not a weapon.
I am slowly
gonna reach for it.
♪♪
Her mask
ain't her head.
Oh, I know.I am getting to that.
Well, then,
get to it.
The whole reason I threw inwith them...
was so I couldget close enough to Alpha
to slit her throat.
Now, you talk about"silencing the Whisperers."
I silenced the Alpha.
Why the hell else
you think
that your girlfriendlet me outta that cell?
♪♪
Woman: Carol.
Caaarol...
[Birds chirping]
Woman: Carol.
♪♪
I'm always watching.
[Walkers growling]
[Coughs]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Grunts]
[Screaming]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Alpha growling]
[Door closes]
[Clattering]
♪♪
[Shuddered breathing]
[Glass shatters]
♪♪
You are lost.
So was your boy.
You sent him away.
♪♪
And he never
came back.
He died out here,
alone and afraid.
Just like Sophia.
♪♪
No taking this head.
Unless you take
your own.
♪♪
I respect
what you did.
It was Negan
drew the blade,
but it was you
who ended me.
Like a true alpha.
Stop it.
Oh, I see.
You regret it.
No.
You feel guilt.
People were hurt
in the name of vengeance.
And now
you can't go back.
They won't accept
what you've done.
Maybe they will
if you say you're sorry.
♪♪
"I'm sorry
you're mad at me.
P-Please don't be
mad at me.
I'm sorry!"
Being out
on your own --
you've tried it before.
They always
pull you back.
Always wanting more.
Love.
Motherhood.
Death.
But they don't knowwhat you truly want.
Admit it.
What do you want?
Say it.
[Walker growling]
♪♪
[Whimpers]
[Sobs]
I want to be alone.
Yeah.
That's not it.
Do you think
they'll have candy?
The new community,
I mean.
What on earth
made you think of that?
I was remembering
my mother,
who grew upnear train tracks like this.
My mother was a pistol,
as they say,
so I was trying to remembersomething kind about her,
and I settled onthese chocolate bunnies
she used to buy
at Easter time.
I was macking on them,and they were delicious,
though eating the headsdid upset me as a child, and...
still, I came toassociate them with...
family.
Eugene, please tell me
we aren't really on a journey
to find
chocolate bunnies.
Well,
of course not.
We're on a journey forthe future hope of mankind.
But candy
would be nice.
Ezekiel,
are you okay?
Or shall I delve intomy arsenal of impressions?
I'm sorry, Eugene.
I'm not the best audience
at the moment.
[Walkers growling in distance,
horse neighs]
[Growling continues]
Whoa.
♪♪
Whisperers?
Not their
modus operandi.
So we're not alone,
but we don't know
who would do this.
Worth taking a few moments
to investigate?
In case
this is a warning.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Whoa.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Coughs]
[Grunts]
[Body thuds]
[Coughs]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Groans, coughs]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
Yumiko:
All clear!
Ezekiel?
I'm coming!
All clear here.
Negan: This whole"follow the leader" routine,
it's kinda déjà vu
for me.
It's the same wayit went down with Alpha.
You know,
I get it.
All right,
you're pissed
your gal pal didn'tlet you in on the plan.
Nobody asked you.
Look,
I'm pissed, too.
Lone wolves, they're notthinking about the pack.
Maybe I'm pissed
'cause of Hilltop.
Whole bunch of children
almost died 'cause of you.
Keep walking.
♪♪
[Cheers and applause]
Man: How's everybody
feeling tonight?
[Cheers and applause continue]
♪ I'm a miser when I'm rich
but a gambler if I'm broke♪
♪ And if
we're gonna be laughin'♪
♪ I would want to be in
on the joke♪
♪ Sometimes I think
you show me scabs♪
♪ Just to tempt me
to tear 'em away♪
♪ Makin' me draw blood will
never make me want to stay♪
♪♪
Alpha:
Is this your plan?
Get back on a boat,
take the river out?
♪♪
Ed was right
about you.
You're just
a brainless clam.
♪♪
There was no peace
on the ocean.
You were thinking
about me.
Wondering where I went.
Lookin' for a sign.
You even wrote that letterto Maggie about me.
[Grunts]
Give it up,
Carol.
If I know the truth,so do you.
♪♪
Do you hear me,you empty-headed slit?!
[Grunts]
♪♪
You stupid cooze.
It was right here.
I swear to God,it was on that spike.
Look, we, uh --
We -- We sit here,we can wait for Carol.
Or I can take you
to find the --
Oh, come on, man.
We're talking about
Lydia here.
Why would I stash her
out in banjo country
unless the whole point
was to keep her safe?
Unless the whole
freakin' point
was just to use her as bait
so I could get Alpha alone?
You sure took your sweet-asstime, though, didn't you?
What is with you guys thinking
I didn't do it fast enough?
You didn't kill her.
I did.
It took a minute.
I had to get her to trust me.
Because I wasn't on some
half-cocked suicide mission.
No, it's because
you liked it.
♪♪
[Gun cocks]
[Thunder rumbles]
♪♪
Alpha's dead.
Because of you.
♪♪
We kneel...
to the new Alpha.
♪♪
[Negan laughs]
♪ 'Cause if I knew
they'd lock me up♪
♪ Then I would surely run♪
♪ Killed so many in your name,
girl♪
♪ That I'd never see the sun♪
♪ Was invited down to Hell♪
♪ Drank from the glass,
it felt just fine♪
♪ I asked him,  "Where's that girl of mine?"
♪
♪ The Devil just smiled
and left me behind♪
♪ I smiled back and finished
my beer and said adiós♪
♪ I didn't shed a tear♪
♪ Joy descended with the flames
all around♪
♪ 'Cause the Devil,
he sure likes to gamble♪
♪ I tried to stand tall♪
♪ And knock down
that big old wall♪
♪ I tried to stand strong♪
♪ But suppose
I guessed all wrong♪
Sing it now.
♪ I tried to stand tall♪
♪ And knock down
that big old wall♪
♪ I tried to stand strong♪
♪ But suppose
I guessed all wrong♪
[Cheers and applause]
Negan: Oh.
Sorry, man.
I am, uh...
just savoring
the moment.
Oh.
Taking my sweet-ass time.
♪♪
All right, fellas,first order of business.
[Thunder rumbles]
Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
One damn minute.
I'm supposed to be
the Alpha, right?
I mean,the only reason I'm asking
is I'ma little bit confused.
If I'm the Alpha,
why is someone who ismost definitely not the Alpha
holding
the badass shotgun?
[Thunder rumbles]
♪♪
See, that iswhat I'm talkin' about.
That feels good.
Right?
I mean,I never had a kid of my own,
but if I did,
I would imagine
this is what it's likeholding your baby
for the very first time,except for it turns out,
my baby can kill peopleby spitting bullets at 'em.
[Thunder rumbles]
Daryl,
kneel to the Alpha.
♪♪
[Chuckles]
Damn.
It is starting to get real now,ain't it?
Daryl,
you were right
when you said
that I liked it.
[Sighs]
The fact is...
I like it a lot.
You should probably
shoot me.
Don't threaten me
with a good time.
♪♪
Shit.
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Thunder rumbles]
Untie me, asshole.
[Chuckles]
[Horse neighing]
[Distressed horse whinny]
[Thud]
What's wrong?
What's going on? Hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa.
Lookit, hey, hey.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Hey, hey.
What's going on?
[Sighs]
♪♪
Oh, no, no, no.
Shh.
It's okay.
♪♪
Nothing's got to hurt anymore.
[Sighs]
[Inhales deeply]
♪♪
It's okay.
Shh.
♪♪
You're all right.
I'm sorry.
Ezekiel.
♪♪
I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have come.Why?
This was just
an accident.
♪♪
If I fall in there...
promise meyou'll leave me behind.
No.
He wasn't strong enoughto make the journey.
Maybe I'm not,
either.
I'm okay with that.
But I'm not okaywith putting you at risk.
So you want
to turn back?
Because of
what might happen?
♪♪
It's for the best.Hey.
You don't know
what lies ahead for us.
No one does.
I had all these plans
for my life,
and I clung to them
so hard.
And f-f-for what?
No one cares what I have in mindfor the future.
I'm here to find out
what's possible --
what none of us
could predict
or imagine.
♪♪
And you know
who we need with us?
That man that built a Kingdom
in the apocalypse.
♪♪
[Walker growling]
Alpha:
My mom used to say,
everything works outthe way it's supposed to.
Oh,
just shut up already.
[Growling continues]
It's finally time.
♪♪
This way, friend!
We're ready for ya.
You always knew
how this would end.
No one's coming
to save you.
Not Ezekiel.
And certainly
not Daryl.
[Grunts]
Not after what you didto Connie.
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
Stop fighting.
♪♪
No matter what you do,you lose people.
Sophia, Lizzie, Mika,
Henry, Ezekiel...
And if you go back,
Daryl could be next.
I could never
let that happen.
Your track recorddoes not inspire confidence.
♪♪
You know
what you gotta do.
I could've been anyone,
but you chose mebecause I get the job done.
I don't want this.
♪♪
[Grunting]
Just look at the flowerslike you're supposed to.
One...
two...
three.
♪♪
[Screams]
[Panting]
[Groans]
♪♪
It's never too late.
Whoa.
♪♪
[Sighs]
Not to spin
a broken record,
but I don't think
she's comin' back.
You know, I'm --I'm not bullshitting you.
I know.
When I said
that I liked it...
that wasn't
part of the act.
Yeah.
I know.
You know,
when your people locked me up,
I lost everything.
You know,
seven years spent
staring outthat little window...
man,
it sucked.
It got so bad
that even my memorieshad bars painted on 'em.
So when Alpha
took me in...
I admit it,
I -- I liked it.
It was...
[Sighs]
It was nice
feeling like I mattered again,
like I was respected.
But she took it
too far.
You don't kill peoplethat don't deserve it.
And you never
kill kids.
Is that supposed to
make me like you?
No.
Good.
But what aboutmy winning personality?
[Sighs]
What about Carol?
[Groans]
♪♪
[Gate creaking]
Yumiko: What are the chancesof a city like this being empty?
More improbable than a baby bornwith a full set of teeth.
Hellllooo?
[Walker growling]
[Walker growling in distance]
[Laughing]
[Laughing continues]
[Sighs]
[Footsteps approach]
Oh, my God, hi!
♪♪
♪ Just stickin' to a path♪
♪ You're like a monkey
in the trees♪
Two eyes, one truth.
♪ I love the way you move♪
♪ You love the way
I rock n' roll♪
♪ But if our worlds collide,
it's bound to take its toll♪
♪ Oh, oh, it's sad but true♪
♪ Love is never enough♪
♪ And after just a few months,
we're not immune♪
♪ Oh, we used to stay up late♪
♪ Starin' in each other's eyes♪
Thank you.
♪♪
I see now.
Thank you.
♪♪
[Gasps, breathing heavily]
[Walkers growling,
glass squeaking]
♪♪