[Walkers growling,
indistinct shouting]
[Walker growling]
[Walkers growling]
Daryl:
We gotta jam 'em up.
[Man shouting indistinctly]
Man: Come on!
Move it!
Take that, you bastards!
[Shouting continues]
[Walkers growling]
Daryl: It's workin'.
They're slowin' down.
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Coughing]
Lydia!
Hey, you can't
go back out there!
You know
what Alpha wants.
I'll never
walk with her.
Man: Over there!
Over there!
[Walkers growling]
Ezekiel: Stay with me,
everybody!
It's all right!
It's gonna be fine!
Wait, wait, wait!
[Children coughing]
Where's Judith?
[Explosion]
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
Aah! Please.
Please...
Okay, Judith.
Okay, okay.
Let's get to
a safe place.
[Explosion]
[Walkers growling]
Man:
Hold the line!
Hold them back!
Steady!
[Indistinct shouting]
Eugene!
[Walkers growling]
Fire!
[Explosion]
Back!
Daryl:Wall's down. Follow me.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Explosion, screaming]
[Indistinct shouting]
♪♪
[Explosion]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Groaning]
[Coughing]
♪♪
[Bat thuds, bones crack]
Through the heart.
Aw, shit.
My bad.
Do not miss again.
Many Guardians
were sacrificed.
We must gather.
Replenish.
Well,
I really need
to show you allhow to savor a victory.
It is not a victory
if I do not have
everything I want.
Lydia.
Not your concern.
Then you have seen her?
She's not
amongst the dead.
But I will not stop
until I bring her home.
To you.
[Sighs]
[Chuckles]
I am at your service,
Frowny McTwoKnives.
Gather.
Wait, wait, wait.
You want me
to herd walkers?
Such a dick.
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Chuckles]
Screw this.
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Chuckles]
Aw.
[Walker growling]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Breathing heavily]
All right, Aaron, hold --
hold on one second.
I said hold on,
dammit!
Don't go
and do something stupid.
The only stupid thingwould be to not kill you.
No, look,
I can explain. Just --
Shut up.
[Walkers growling]
Aaron, I am not --
Enough of your bullshit!
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Grunts]
Stop.
Sorry, kid.
This shit is done.
[Adam crying]
Hey,
let me take Adam.
It's all right.You need to --
No, hey, I'm fine.You need to rest.
It's okay.We just gotta keep moving.
Earl and the others could beat the rendezvous already.
[Crying continues]
Hey,
it's okay.
We're almost there.
Yes, we are.
Oh, yes, we are.
Why don't you should try
talking normal?
Oh, I am talking normal.Aren't I?
I'm talking normal.
[Crying continues]
That's the creepy baby voice,
Alden.
Nobody likes
the creepy baby voice.
Not even babies.
Let me see
if I can help.
Thought I told you
to stay back.
I can help with Adam.
Yeah,
the hell you can.
Come on.
She knows him.
No,
she knew him.
And her and her peopleleft him to die, remember?
[Crying continues]
Shh, shh.
It's enoughthat I let her come along.
There's no way she's gettingher hands on this kid.
Move away --
now.
Just try rubbing
the back of his head --
I thought I told youto be quiet!
Just try rubbing
the back of his head
very gently
and very slowly.
And keep making shushing noises
right into his ear,
over and over.
[Crying continues]
Shh.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
[Crying continues]
Let me try.
♪♪
[Adam coos]
[Birds chirping]
What was her name?
Your sister.
You never said.
♪♪
Frances.
Her name was Frances.
♪♪
And he meant everything
to her.
And she was everythingto you, right?
♪♪
[Adam coos]
If I had to do it
all over again...
♪♪
She should be the one sitting
here holding him, not me.
♪♪
Let's move.
What's going on?
They're coming.
[Adam crying]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Crying continues]
Follow me! Follow me!Come on!
[Growling continues]
[Crying continues]
Come on!
[Grunts]
♪♪
No! No!
[Crying continues]
[Screams] Come on!
[Growling continues]
Hey! Over here!
♪♪
Come on!
[Grunts]
[Walker growling]
♪♪
[Panting]
[Chuckles]
♪♪
Unh!
[Grunts]
[Coughing]
♪♪
You. Will. Walk.
With. Us.
[Grunts]
Never!
[Coughs]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
It's -- It's you.
Shh.
Your voice
sounded familiar, but...
Unh!
♪♪
[Growling]
[Growling stops, body thuds]
♪♪
[Tools clattering]
Connect the circuit boardto the transponder.
No, no, no.
TNC antenna connection...
♪♪
Magna:We killed the skins.
Then we crawled
back into the cave.
The sickoswere either dead or...
trapped under rocks
from the...
♪♪
We kept pushing.
Searching.
♪♪
Took a turn,
and before we knew it,we were in the horde.
Connie and I
moved together.
The sickos
pushed forward.
♪♪
Got between us.
And her hand...
♪♪
...her hand just...
slipped out of mine...
And I...
couldn't find her again.
♪♪
You're leaving?
Just wanna get there
before dark.
You know,
she's been through a lot.
Might need some more time
to rest.
Stay as long
as you like.
So you're just gonna
leave her behind?
Again?
I didn't say that.
You know,maybe instead of ignoring her,
you try begging
for forgiveness
after the shityou put her through.
You think
that's what she wants from me?
Like it'll fix anything?
We go through shit
to go through shit --
Unh!
What the hell
is wrong with her?
I didn't ask you
to do that.
You're saying
I should've just
let her
treat you like that?I'm saying -- I'm say--
Well,
I am so, so sorry
if I'm just not gonna sit here
and take that.
Things don't alwayswork out the way you want, Miko.
I never said they did!
I can't
do this anymore.
I thought a lot aboutlast time we talked.
And I was so pissed.
[Inhales sharply]
But now I get it.
You were right
to kick me out.
[Chuckles]
At leastI don't have to worry about
someone stealing my pillow
no more.
[Both laugh]
Well,
all I'll say is,
the nights have been
a lot more peaceful.
I don't snore.
Yeah, right.
[Laughs]
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
[Walker growling]
♪♪
I, uh...
[Sniffles]
I didn't mean
to intrude,
but I felt itincumbent upon my person
to give you
a once-over
after seeing you takea cherry cheesecake like that
to the kisser.
[Sighs]
Do you know
what it feels like
to want something
so bad...
and to go after itwith everything that you have...
...piss off everyone --
literally everyone --
maybe get people killed --
and still,you have nothing to show for it?
I do.
[Sniffles]
[Grunts]
You see, there's a meetin'of extraordinarily...
momentous,
do-or-die,
Brobdingnagian proportions.
It's the --It's a big meeting.
It's the biggest meetingof my life.
And it's coming up quickon the calendar,
and unfortunately,I can't share details.
But now,with the grimness at hand,
vis-a-vis Hilltop,
I obviously can no longer attendsaid meeting.
♪♪
It's just not oftenyou meet someone you...
Another someone,
in general, I mean.
If it's important,
it's simple.
You go.
Well, sure,but I also have obli--
Eugene,
just go to her.
[Chuckles]
♪♪
I sincerely hope you getwhat it is that you want.
Nabila's been askingabout her kids.
You sure
Ezekiel has them?
They should be
at the rendezvous.
♪♪
It feels like
it's still burning.
We're almost there,
baby.
Almost there.
♪♪
[Walker growling]
[Sighs]
♪♪
This is the spot,
right?
Yeah.
Nabila: My babies?
Where are my babies?!
Where are my babies?
No.Where are my babies?
Nabila, they're with Ezekiel,
all right?
They're with the king,
they're with the king.[Sobbing]
♪♪
Come on,
spread out.
Come on, let's go.
I'm gonna find them.
[Crying]
[Walkers growling]
Judith: Earl,think we'll be safe here?
Did they see us?
Earl:
No, we're safe.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
Do you think
Ezekiel's okay?
There was just so much smoke,and I couldn't see,
and then
he was just gone.
He'll be here,
honey.
He will.
He's one of the bravest menI know.
Okay?
Wow.
You are all
doing great.
You all are so good.
You're so good.
Your folks are gonna be so proudwhen they get here.
So proud
when they get here.
Soon?
Oh, yeah.
Soon.
Real soon, sweetheart.
Okay, now.
Shh.
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Groans]
You lied to us.
♪♪
I did.
But I did it
to protect you.
You can't do this.
I don't have
much choice.
I can stay here
with you.
So you're not alone
when it happens.
Oh, honey,
I'm not alone.
I have Tammy
and my son.
♪♪
Alden will take
good care of Adam.
And you, Judith...
you're so strong.
You're so brave.
♪♪
But now I need you
to keep those kids safefrom me.
Please.
[Voice breaking]
Go back out there,
and don't come near me again,okay?
[Shuddered breathing]
♪♪
[Shallow breathing]
Ezekiel: Jerry.
The kids...
Earl's got the kids!
[Breathing deeply]
♪♪
[Head thuds]
[Birds chirping]
♪♪
[Growling]
Daryl!
Hey, hi.
[Laughs]
Boy: Daddy!
Hi, buddy.
♪♪
Is Judith in there?
[Door creaks]
♪♪
Judith?
Come here.
♪♪
Alpha.
That thingyou've been looking for...?
I found it.
♪♪
[Chair creaks]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
It is beautiful.
[Walker growling]
Pure.
[Scoffs]
All I see
is a bag of bones
and some
gnarly-ass teeth.
You will see.
Maybe soon.
And I will
meet you there.
♪♪
You know, I ain't exactly readyto meet my Maker,
if that's
what you're saying.
♪♪
You proved yourself again
by finding her.
And like the young lion cub
who must leave his pride,
it is time
to roam the Earth.
Build a new pride.
Do you want me out there,preaching your gospel?
♪♪
I want you
to become a lion.
[Chair creaking]
♪♪
[Grunting]
You know,
I may not be hip
on the whole
Greek alphabet,
but Beta is no Alpha.
And if we're going stickwith the whole lion thing...
then isn't it
the young lioness
who takes
her mother's place?
♪♪
Walk.
[Grunting]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
A long time ago,
before meat-lovers like himstarted showing up, I, uh...
I lost somebodythat was close to me.
Pancreatic cancer.
If the disease wasn'teating her up from the inside,
then the chemo was kickingthe ever-loving shit out of her.
And yet...
I don't know.
Maybe, uh...
Maybe the cancer justput things in perspective.
She was, uh...
She was never
more beautiful.
♪♪
Didn't matter
how frail she got.
Even when
she lost her hair.
♪♪
Be grateful.
Death...
set her free.
The thing is,
when she was gone,
I just -- I didn't feelmuch of anything anymore.
You know?
I didn't feel scared,I didn't feel happy.
I, uh...
I didn't feel anything.
I was just...here.
And that
is my strength.
Now, me?
I am dead
to this world.
But you?
See,
you are pretending.
You thinkthat it makes you strong
to saythat emotions aren't real,
that we are animals.
That is bullshit.
And you know it.
And now you claim
that you have to killyour own daughter --
your own
flesh and blood...
[Sighs]
It is her destiny.
♪♪
That disease...
took your wife...
because that was
what nature intended.
She could not
take you with her.
But you live every day
wishing she could.
♪♪
Lydia was made
for this.
♪♪
To be free.
With me.
[Chair creaking]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
You still love her.
♪♪
I have to do it
because I love her.
♪♪
She will always
be my baby.
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
Thank you.
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Chair creaks][Panting]
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Door creaks]
[Panting]
[Chokes]
♪♪
Took you long enough.