One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Wear me
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three, one, two,
three, one, two, three...
♪ Wear me out
Michonne:
Ketchup face.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three.
♪ It's all
It's very good.
It's very good. Here.
Judith: On my -- Wait.
Right here.
No.
Actually, no.
♪ Strung out
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ You found
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three...
♪ What carried you
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three,
♪ Fall out
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three, one, two,
three, one, two, three...
♪ Everyone fall out
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Get lost
One, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three,
one, two, three...
♪ In this town
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three, one, two,
three, one, two, three...
♪ 'Cause I got older
♪ And we got tired
One, two, three, one, two.
♪ Heaven, I know that we tried
♪ Heaven, I know
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Yeah, Heaven,
I know that we tried ♪
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Heaven, I know
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Yeah, Heaven,
I know that we tried ♪
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Heaven, I know
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three,
one, two, three.
♪ Longer still
♪ Withstanding the most I will
♪ Still be the most I can
♪ Drying out,
dragging down now ♪
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three,
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three,
Man: Jesus!
Woman: Come on!
We need some help!
Watch out!
Luke: Oh, my God!
There's people in there.
Jerry:
It's our people.
Alden: Hey, stop! Stop!
Everyone, get back.
The structure
might not hold.
Earl:
Alden's right.
Too many of us
jostling around in there
could bring the whole thing down
on their heads.
You guys,
get the horses out of there.
Go to the infirmary.
Get Alex.
Luke: What?
You think
it was them?
It was them.
Of course it was.
I mean, they already cut off
our hunting grounds.
'Cause why? 'Cause we crossed
their boundary
to put out
a damn forest fire?
We're already at war.
We just
didn't know it yet.
Nine are injured.
Roof's collapsed.
Half are trapped
under it.
It's gonna take a hell of a long
time to get 'em all out.
What do you wanna do,
boss?
Man:
How many of them?
You feeling okay?
Come on. Let's meet
at the house --
No. No, no.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
They need help.
You said
nine were injured?
Dianne: Yeah.The infirmary's only got
beds enough
for four, maybe five.
We could empty out
a couple trailers.
Well, we can use
Maggie's old office.
Marco, Connie, Kelly,
grab anything
we can use as stretchers
and gather mattresses
from the bedrooms, yeah?
Take her.
Let's go.
Alden: Hey, stop.
Two at a time.
Man:
Get a head count!
Aaron: Stop!
You're dead.
Your eyes
were on the ground.
Track from
head to hands always.
Lose focus,
and you will get killed.
Remember, these people
took our friends.
They took our land.
They must
be stopped again.
Gage:
Hey, Lydia!
You think Mommy
will take me in?
Oh, right. No.
She -- She kicked your ass out.
Now you're just
a freak.
Get the hell
out of here.
Hey, you three.
Up here.
Let's run it again.
You're worried.
I'm focusing.
I saw
Carol's bandages.
I know the skins
shot at her.
Carolshot at them.
Is that why
they took more land?
I don't want you
to worry about this.
That's my job,
and I happen to be
very good at my job.
Okay.
But I can be
a fresh set of eyes.
Or a pair
of friendly ears?
Alpha said
that she would release the horde
if we ever
crossed her border.
Carol took a shot at her,
and she only took land.
Maybe their rules
are changing.
Maybe.
But when you start negotiating
with a bully,
there may be no end to
how much they try to take.
Some bullies
you can live with.
Others,
you gotta fight.
Can we live
with the skins?
Well,
theysaid we could.
But you never take your enemy
at their word.
You measure them
by their actions.
So, when their actions
are unexpected...
You know how when we want RJ
to go to sleep,
the fastest way
is to let him run around?
Right.
'Cause then
he'll be so tired
that RJ will
put himself to sleep.
Maybe the Whisperers
wanna keep us fighting back
until we get so tired
that they have the advantage.
That is not bad,
kiddo.
I knew RJ would eventually
be good for something.
So, am I right?
Is that
the kind of bully they are?
You're thinking on it.
Whoa.
Scott:
You see something?
It's Ezekiel.
Why's the King
out here?
I don't know.
You guys keep riding
to Hilltop.
Good luck, Mom.Thanks, baby.
I'll be
right behind you.
Whoa. Whoa!
Ezekiel?
You should go.
Can you step away
from the edge?
Then I'm not
going anywhere.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
You looking
for a job, kid?
Just trying
to clear my head.
It's your third visit
in a week.
You keep it up,
you're gonna find some socks
with your name on 'em.
Gage and his friends
started again today.
Again?
Jesus.
Alright, kid, look,
obviously you're having a day,
but, you know, what happened to
rolling with it?
I'm not just
gonna smile and take it.
I didn't say that.
But I also didn't say
run and hide.
I mean, shit.
You said to
kill 'em with kindness.
I did say that.
Look, they are trying
to get a reaction out of you.
They wanna
see you upset.
Don't give that to 'em.
Screw 'em.
Let's go.
I'm good.
Now.
She is just trying
to fit in.
Yeah.
Well, that ain't ever
gonna happen
if she hangs out
with you, now, is it?
We were just talking.
He ain't your friend.
He gets me.
Just stay away
from him, alright?
You know
I didn't mean to --
We never would've
worked out anyway.
Both too damn stubborn.
Maybe in
another universe.
Mm.
I lost my Kingdom.
I had a reign,
and what did I do with it?
I failed.
Benjamin, Shiva, Henry,
then the Kingdom,
now Hilltop.
And Carol.
I don't even know
how to talk to her anymore.
I didn't know
what I was gonna do
when I came out here.
I've been here before.
Not here...
but here.
A long time ago,
when I was on my own,
I was in
a dark place.
And I started
to envy walkers.
Every time
I ran into one,
I'd tell myself,
"I'm gonna let it bite me."
Next thing I know,
my sword
was chopping off its head
like it has a damn
mind of its own.
So I put the sword down,
kill 'em
with my own bare hands.
Eventually...
I just gave up.
And what
that feel like?
It feels like
a mask...
until it doesn't.
My old mask
saved my life.
But I could only wear it
for so long.
Mm.
Just like that,
you lose it all,
all over again.
Hmm.
And somehow...
it's harder
the second time around...
especially when you get used to
having someone there...
that...
partner in crime...
that sounding board...
that walk.
Now it's all on you...
just you.
Yet I smile.
For what it's worth,
you're not
a half-bad kisser.
I was a mess.
That was not
the top of my game,
just so you know.
Well, I haven't kissed anyone
over four feet
in the last six years,
so...
Listen.
The next time
that you --
Act like an idiot?
Just promise me you won't
ride out by yourself again.
Thank you, Michonne.
Yumiko: How many left?
Jerry: Three.
I'm going back in.
I'll go with you.
Jesus.
There's more of them
out there.
Well,
that's not good.
Will it hold?Alden: Barely.
Walkers keep
pushing in,
it's gonna bring
the whole tree down.
Might bring the whole damn
barn down with it.
We got anything
to brace it with?
We got some timbers
up at the house.
How much time
before it comes down?
How much time?
Enough, I hope.
Uh, guys?
We'll take the walkers.
Alfred:
It's not happening.
Gage: No.
Not at all.
Tastes good to me --
Give us some room,
please?
Oh, my God,
what is wrong with you?
You're crazy!
Is this
why Ozzie and Alek died?
So she could
make a fool out of us?
Not here.
Shh.
You do wanna
live here, right?
They deserved it.
I know.
But you can't be doing
shit like that.
But they can just
write whatever the hell
they want on our door?
I'll talk to 'em.
I'll set 'em straight.
No, please.
I don't want you
to fight my fights for me, okay?
They want me to give up.
I know that.
But I'm not gonna,
okay?
I can't.
I get it.
Can't you just
avoid 'em?
Great.
Shh.
Ugh!
Why do you hate me?
You put my friends
on spikes.
I wasn't there.
Ugh!
Ozzie was always
a fair man.
So in his honor,
I'm gonna give you
one last chance.
If you run away now,
we'll play dumb
when they ask us.
This is my home.
You're my people.
Get in there, kid!Ozzie was
my best friend!
What about
your friend Addy?
Get up! Get up!And Rodney?
Aah!
Come on!
I loved Henry.
You know I loved him. Please.
Please.
Ugh!
Get off me!
Ugh! Ohh!
Hold her down.
Get her.
Ohh!
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
We were just
trying to scare her.
Brandon:
Yo, Negan!
What the hell's going on
back here?
Holy shit.
Margo.
Shit.
Man: Should have never
let 'em out.
Man #2: Yeah, man,
just heard...
You freak.
This is your fault!It was Negan!
Negan killed her!
Lydia:  No, he didn't
do anything wrong.
No, it wasn't --
He didn't do anything.
Now get him
out of here!Please.
Move!
No, he didn't
do anything wrong!
I know. I know.
I know. I know. I know.
He didn't
do anything wrong.
No, please!
Oh, please, no.
Please.
Hold that
right there.
Easy, now.
Hey.
Okay.
All good?
I'll be back.
I'm so sorry
this happened to you.
Lydia.
He was so sweaty.
Never liked deodorant.
Said it --
it made his armpits itchy.
So I got used to it.
Sometimes he smelled like
garlic and onions.
I miss him.
Who's that?
My dad.
My dad
would've protected me.
Tell me what happened.
Negan saved my life.
Man:
...on the wall there.
Negan:
How's the kid doing?
She's banged up,
but she'll be alright.
You know,
the people out there
are talkin' about
puttin' you down,
sayin' Rick ain't around
to save you no more,
maybe they should have done it
a long time ago.
If you came here looking
for a confession...
just keep walking.
It was an accident.
And for the record,
screw her.
She was a goddamn asshole
beating on a kid.
World's better off.
But you already know that,
don't you?
You came down here
to look me in the eye
because you don't know
what to do with me.
Shit, all that time you spent
fantasizing about my death,
all that time
you actually tried to kill me,
and now look at you.
You're not so sure.
You listen to me
real close.
You and I ain't never
been in a room before,
not toe to toe.
And there ain't nobody
to save you right now.
What do you want me to do,
Daryl?
I mean,
the people out there --
they are out
for blood.
Guys like you and me --
we can smell that
from a mile away.
Why help Lydia?
You ain't no hero.
No.
No, I'm not.
I'm a sucker.
See, I started believing in
your way of life,
your moral code.
Hell, you even gave me
a little taste of freedom,
just so
you could yank it away
when I actually did
the right thing.
You gotta admit,
that is pretty messed up.
And we both know
I appreciate
some messed-up shit.
You're gonna get your chance
to tell your side.
Who's the sucker now?
Daryl: Hey.
Carol: Hey.
How you feelin'?
Sore.
I bet.
I heard
what happened.
Yeah.
It's a mess.
Everybody's talking about
Negan again.
It's like
time never moves.
What do you think?
I don't give a shit
about him.
I believe her,
though.
I do.
This is
a distraction.
Hilltop's got a tree
through its walls.
Alexandria was attacked.
Oh, we don't
know that yet.
Our real enemy
is out there.
There's enough
bad stuff happening here.
I'm afraid
if we don't fix it,
it ain't gonna matter
what she does to us.
There won't be
anything left.
Should have gone
to New Mexico.
Yeah.
Man: Put together
the last one now!
Jerry: Yo!
We got all our peeps!
Get back in here!
Alright.
Just keep coming!
We got to
get out of here.
Luke!
Magna, let's go!
Come on!
We have to
protect the wall!
We need help!Yumiko: No,
there's no time.
Hey!
If we stay out here,
we die.
Everybody, let's go!
We've got to
get out of here!
Come on!
Miko!
Close the gates!
Come on!
Close them!
Defend the breach!
Everything alright?
I've been tryin' to reach you.
Rough day,
but things are looking up.
What's going on?
Something happened.
Gabriel:
Lydia lured you there?
Gage: Yeah. You saw what she did
with the squirrel.
She's psycho.Alfred: And Negan
was with her.
If you thought
Lydia was crazy,
why'd you agree to meet her
back there in the dark?
Well, um...
Well --
Hey, we're the ones
who were attacked here.
But she's the one
laying in the infirmary.
And our friend
is in a grave.
Negan's on the right side
this time.
I don't know if it's gonna make
any difference, though.
Should I come home?
No, not if Hilltop
still needs you.
How's Lydia?
Not good.
Daryl,
you have to protect her.
Yeah, well,
I'm trying.
No.
You have to protect her
for all of us.
When we went
to the border,
we went there
to de-escalate the conflict
and buy time
and strategic advantage.
And it was working
till Carol took her shot.
Alpha could have killed us
right there.
Why didn't she?
You think she won't attack
if we got Lydia?
Alpha wanted you
to protect her.
Look, Lydia's presence
might not help us,
but if Alpha thinks
she isn't safe with us
or if Lydia runs off
because of all this,
it'll definitely
hurt us.
She has to stay
at Alexandria.
Alright.
I'll make sure.
Let's just keep this
between us for now.
How's RJ?
He's great.
He won't eat
his vegetables,
so I'm a little
afraid for him.
Hey, the council's meeting
right now.
Daryl...
I want you to be my proxy
when they vote.
Alright.
I should go.
I know you'll do
the right thing.
Rachel:
Oceanside to Hilltop.
Come in, Hilltop.
Pick up, please.
Hilltop copies.
This is Michonne.
Aaron: I get why people might
think Negan's been redeemed.
I've...
I've wondered it myself.
Hell, he --
maybe he has changed.
But a man like that,
who's done
the things he's done,
killed the people's
he's killed --
something inside him
is broken.
We need to face
that fact.
Siddiq: Yes, but killing him now
over this
undermines the civilization
that we have built.
What about the people who
never got to witness that
civilization because of him?
And what the hell
are you even talking about?
The Whisperers
are attacking us.
Okay,
let's take a break.No.
Let me finish.
Look at what's going on
at Hilltop.
We're taking our eyes
off the ball.
The council wasn't made
for this,
deciding on a man's life
in the dead of night
because people are carrying
pitchforks and torches.
I -- Look,
if you can't make a decision,
the people out there
are gonna make one for you.
Well,
what'd Michonne say?
She wants me
to be her vote.
Lydia said Negan saved her,
so he saved her.
I'm a "no."
So we're tied.
Gabriel,
where do you stand?
I'm gonna take the night
to clear my head
and consider my vote,
and I suggest
you all do the same.
Michonne: I'd like to head out
right away,
two wagons,
some supplies.
Yumiko: Rachel's sure
it was them?
"Sure" is a strong word,
but she swears
that one of those creepers
were watching them,
too damn close to where
that mask washed up.
It might be nothing,
but in case it is one of them,
you know as well as I do
they move as a pack.
Where there's one,
you can bet your last dollar
there's a hundred more,
much like the order
of Blattodea.
Ah, the illustrious
cockroach family.
So, you think they're planning
another attack?
Walkers at Alexandria,
the tree here,
and now Oceanside?
First time,
coincidence.
Second time
might be bad luck,
but the third time,
we should check.
Michonne?
Uh, if -- Uh,
if you don't mind,
I-I'd love
to join you.
I'm feeling the ocean
calling to me.
And, um, by "ocean,"
you mean Jules?
What are you
talking about?
Never even heard of her.Mm-hmm.
Oh, yes, of course,
the very tall woman...
Yeah.
...with the f-face
and quiet -- Yeah.
Count me in, too.
In that case,
Eugene,
you'll need to lead a wagon
back to Alexandria.
Actually,
I'll be staying put.
Much like
my amigo here,
I feel an energy
calling to me,
urging me on
to help our good neighbors
by employing my expertise
in architecture and engineering
to plug
the metaphorical gap tooth
in the
metaphorical smile
that is
the Hilltop's fortification.
You want
to fix the wall.
Yes.
Fine.
We'll bring back
some supplies
so you can
do it faster.
Apologies.
The only caveat being
that I cannot escort Judith
back to Alexandria.
Oh, Judith?
She's coming with me.
I am?
Well, yeah.
Who else is gonna be
my pair of friendly ears?
Man: Yeah.
I'll see you later.
Hey.
We did it.
We got everybody out
in time.
We could've have taken
those walkers.
We had a split-second decision
to make --
Youmade the decision.
Look,
when shit hits the fan,
somebody's got to
step up.
So, yeah,
I -- I listen
to what everybody has to say,
I weigh it all up --
And then you do
what you were gonna do anyway.
Where the hell
is all of this coming from?
You're not
my lawyer anymore.
Daryl: What?
He's gone.
Gabriel: The guards say
the keys are missing.
Whoever stole them
must've let him out.
Who was on watch
last night?
Laura was,
but she said she didn't do it,
and I believe her.
Man:
I'd be worried.
I did it.
I let Negan out.
Come on.
You didn't do this.
Yeah, I did.
I kept watch
last night.
You never
left the house.
Does it matter?
This is
where they want me.
Doesn't matter
what they want.
You know,
for a long time,
I blamed myself
for what happened last year.
Kept thinking,
what if I just stayed
in that cell at Hilltop?
If I never
let myself be taken alive
by you people
in the first place?
Never went off
with Henry?
Never said
what I said to my mother?
You're not to blame
for her.
My mother was right.
She said you people
put on these polite faces,
but it's just a mask
'cause when things
get bad...
when you get scared...
you pick a target,
aim, and shoot.
Me, Negan,
anything but you.
Negan's different.
You didn't know him.
The Negan I know
stood up for me
when he didn't have to.
I tried fitting in.
I wanted
to be like you.
You don't belong
in a cage.
I'm better here.
I feel safe.
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three,
One, two, three...
I mean it,
Jerry.
I'm good.
Okay, boss.
Glad to hear it.
♪ Wear me
Hey,
I gotcha.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one two.
♪ Wear me out
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
one, two, three,
one, two, three.
♪ It's all
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Strung out Aww. Alright.
Oh!
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ You found Thank you.
Mm. Yes. You, too.
♪ What carried you
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Get lost Don't go too nuts,
alright?
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
Okay.
♪ In this town
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
Namaste.
Alright.
♪ Some road that's
♪ Getting worn
Okay. I'm coming.
I'm coming.
♪ At our feet
Alrighty. Hiya!
♪ At our feet now
♪ 'Cause I got older
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three...
♪ And we got tired
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three...
♪ Heaven, I know that we tried
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Heaven, I know
One, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
♪ Yeah, Heaven,
I know that we tried ♪
♪ Heaven, I know
♪ Yeah, Heaven, I know
♪ And, Heaven,
I know that we tried ♪
♪ Heaven, I know
♪ Oh, Heaven, I know
♪ Yeah, Heaven,
I know that we tried ♪
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
One, two, three,
one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two.
Whisperer: Shh!